bat strikes ball @@ crowd cheering
announcer line drive @@ right field
man solemnly swear @@ truth @@ testimony @@ give
marion jones @@ ever failed @@ drug test @@ never
olympics
160 drug tests
never failed @@ test
ever used human growth hormone @@ woman @@ record
enhancing substance @@ performance
lance armstrong
make sure @@ trying @@ testimony @@ man @@ clear
many times @@ say @@ armstrong
never taken drugs
tour de france @@ winning @@ man
clear @@ armstrong
tour de france @@ man win
time greats @@ big event @@ like @@ ever
armstrong extraordinary accusations
extraordinary proof @@ must @@ followed
extraordinary proof @@ come
bryan fogel see
mountain bike
thule rack @@ loading
entire life @@ car right
set @@ ready @@ insanity
single hardest amateur cycling event @@ getting ready @@ world
miniature tour de france @@ insane people @@ basically
well @@ qualify @@ man @@ anything
fogel yeah @@ stupidity
laughing
28 years seriously @@ riding @@ professional @@ never
massive amateur events @@ professional @@ going
serious guys @@ mean @@ laughs
man laughs @@ foot fetish @@ tickles @@ max @@ loves @@ got
started @@ know @@ fogel @@ certainly
gonna lead
first tour de france @@ lemond
seventh grade @@ think
000 miles @@ man @@ believe @@ 2
world ," @@ french means @@ name
paris today @@ greg lemond @@ world
first american @@ win @@ fogel
really brought @@ sport
wheel going @@ 40 miles @@ hour @@ ate
entire freshman year @@ plastic teeth @@ spent @@ mouth @@ college
kept racing @@ would
really hurting @@ man
armstrong came along @@ fogel later @@ whole @@ wax @@ ball
back wheel @@ man @@ armstrong
man 2 @@ respond @@ pressure @@ gap
going faster @@ faster
greatest comeback @@ sport @@ man
conquer cancer @@ armstrong managed @@ unbelievable @@ fact
tour de france like @@ trojan @@ riding @@ front
half younger @@ year @@ think @@ lance @@ fogel
kind @@ hero
oprah winfrey @@ yes @@ like
ever take banned substances @@ cycling performance @@ enhance
yes
always suspected @@ fogel @@ doping
really wanna know @@ felt
raced @@ lot @@ guys
years @@ raced @@ known @@ guys
friends
never doped @@ would @@ choice
fogel ever @@ mutters
directly affected
probably clean ." @@ think lance @@ like @@ chuckles
dave zabriskie @@ know
messy
nobody understood @@ way @@ got @@ fogel
last six years @@ armstrong 150 times @@ tested
race @@ home @@ competition
whatever @@ seven @@ night @@ morning @@ clean
never failed @@ drug test @@ fogel
indistinct chatter
man solemnly swear @@ truth @@ testimony @@ give
turned @@ teammates @@ fogel
federal investigation @@ part
crowd cheering
500 doping tests @@ entire career @@ whatever @@ passed @@ guy
work @@ system @@ clearly
test lance @@ many times @@ career
record @@ laboratory @@ catlin
50 times @@ would @@ tested @@ estimating @@ 5 @@ 0
tested lance 50 times @@ never caught @@ fogel
correct
ucla olympic laboratory @@ 25 years @@ operated @@ developed
known mostly @@ developing tests
athletes get caught @@ using drugs
personally feel every year @@ fogel
lance @@ believe
think @@ doping @@ --
every single one @@ em
drugs work @@ unfortunately @@ chuckles
get around @@ certain knowledge @@ time @@ testing
really easy @@ beat
easy
fogel originally @@ idea
test athletes @@ system @@ prove @@ place @@ bullshit
hardest amateur cycling race @@ read @@ planet
day race @@ seven
haute route @@ french alps @@ called
tour de france @@ hardest seven days @@ take
together back @@ back @@ put @@ em
haute route course @@ would @@ like
totally clean @@ first year
440 masochists
top 100 @@ goal
seven days @@ 000 miles @@ 000 feet @@ climbing @@ 75 @@ 1
destroyed
coughing
finished 14th
ten guys @@ seems
everybody else @@ another level
next group
think @@ phone @@ idea @@ fogel
certain senses @@ catlin well @@ like @@ idea
depends @@ dangerous @@ consider
fogel right
catlin testing @@ drugs
know @@ going @@ curious
willing @@ might @@ help @@ advise
avoid positives
gonna take drugs @@ zabriskie
yeah @@ go @@ basically
entire doping program @@ scientist @@ overseen @@ go
catlin design @@ program @@ gonna
every single one @@ gonna get @@ doping controls @@ world
clean
could get away @@ could
would mean @@ pretty much @@ athlete could
athlete could get away
body fluids @@ test @@ need @@ laboratory @@ going @@ catlin
lab yet @@ gonna get @@ sure @@ samples @@ fogel
test professional athletes @@ labs
accredited labs @@ wada
world anti @@ doping agency @@ catlin wada
set @@ labs @@ go @@ fogel
somebody could @@ send @@ samples @@ lab
anybody could figure @@ system @@ game
could damage @@ years @@ worked @@ reputation @@ catlin
started getting worried @@ legacy @@ fogel
gonna work @@ involvement @@ catlin
fogel @@ backed
god bless @@ know @@ catlin
told @@ knew @@ guy
olympic lab @@ grigory rodchenkov @@ moscow @@ director @@ catlin
great old friend
times @@ talk @@ moscow @@ fogel
whole chain @@ set @@ events
ringing
woman speaking indistinctly
grigory rodchenkov tell something
hi
oh @@ great
secret window @@ hmm @@ clean
look good @@ yeah
go ahead @@ yes @@ chuckles
protocol @@ prescribe @@ met @@ like @@ least @@ guy @@ gonna
beat doping test @@ would like @@ ultimate purpose
would like @@ hormonal program @@ start
prove negative @@ give sample @@ yes
yes
ha
serious advisor @@ traps @@ need @@ lot
normally drug -- okay @@ toy squeaking
speaking russian
playing @@ english @@ dog
much excited @@ came back
special toy
toy squeaking @@ yeah @@ hear
wanna see @@ hey @@ dog
yes @@ let @@ get
oh @@ chuckles
rodchenkov @@ male @@ female
male
castrated
chuckles
rodchenkov @@ balls
got @@ balls
yes @@ yeah @@ balls
laughing
rodchenkov max @@ max @@ yeah
yeah @@ max
testosterone @@ prescription
yes @@ uh @@ injectable
right @@ injectable
huh @@ clever
like lance armstrong
send
names @@ long @@ doses
orchestrated @@ everything
gonna take @@ send @@ fogel @@ everything
month schedule @@ rodchenkov yes @@ yes @@ one
got three medications @@ take @@ injection
regimen sheet @@ five times @@ yeah @@ week
half @@ draw @@ cc
tiny needle @@ looks like @@ big needle
yeah @@ really
testosterone comes ready @@ viscous @@ go
thick substance @@ big needle @@ need @@ draw
gonna pull
2 cc
one goes also @@ top @@ thigh
inhales sharply
little nervous @@ right @@ okay
scott brandt give @@ thigh
muscle @@ hurt @@ flex
gonna go @@ muscle @@ brandt
gonna go @@ skin @@ pinch
gonna put @@ underneath @@ skin
hurt @@ fogel @@ bad
go away @@ time @@ see @@ mean
shit @@ oh @@ hcg @@ brandt
right next @@ testosterone @@ brandt
skin @@ pop @@ looking
real thick @@ skin
whoa @@ pumped
long till @@ bumps go
half hour @@ go quick @@ within @@ whoa @@ okay
begin
brand new @@ go day @@ day @@ think @@ brandt @@ ability
injection @@ going
fogel exciting
one trainer @@ work @@ lot @@ fitness @@ brandt
nutrition coaching @@ well
ben stone almost @@ come @@ bryan
20 improvement @@ see @@ brandt @@ able @@ 15
name @@ fogel @@ dog
rodchenkov vrangei
start @@ program @@ okay
fogel
popping routine @@ morning pill
testosterone @@ prepare
testosterone propionate @@ rodchenkov yes
fogel yes
really thick
grigory might help @@ think @@ made
without @@ well @@ difficult @@ answer
saying things @@ kind @@ grigory
think @@ okay @@ let
two weeks @@ dog pants @@ already
fogel laughing @@ fucking
speaking russian @@ fucking
urine today @@ pee @@ english @@ collect
freezer @@ drop
urine @@ take @@ put @@ pee @@ freezer
freezer
day ten @@ day eight
needle
testosterone @@ hgh
weird feeling @@ feel like @@ anything
little bit stronger @@ training @@ feel
really felt stronger @@ yeah
good
good protocol @@ forty milligrams @@ day
wada lab director @@ still @@ idea @@ fogel
sochi olympics @@ testing
would agree
catch athletes @@ supposed @@ job
one month @@ 000 units @@ want @@ 24
yes
fogel fuck @@ man @@ lot @@ epo
common fears @@ rodchenkov @@ paranoia
reproducing lance armstrong @@ scenario @@ imitating
getting kind @@ legs @@ bruises
thigh @@ stop @@ disturb
thigh muscle @@ inject @@ better @@ ass
fogel stammers @@ ass
rodchenkov much
fogel okay
get ridiculous @@ starting
ow
inhales sharply okay @@ wow @@ bleeding
really bleeding @@ one @@ oh @@ fuck
let @@ get @@ alcohol
um @@ one @@ okay @@ half
inhales deeply
oh @@ fuck
sighs
um grunts
okay
russian accent @@ subcutaneous @@ like
right @@ put @@ ass
go one inch @@ laughing @@ buttocks
show @@ bottle @@ ."
stone @@ kidding
seen movie @@ rodchenkov
separate movie
movie
russia @@ man @@ doping @@ athletes
rodchenkov @@ mr @@ athletes
get positive tests
internationally recognized @@ research @@ narrator @@ laboratory @@ german
outstanding scientist @@ head scientist @@ considered
grigory rodchenkov
russian dr @@ woman @@ rodchenkov @@ informed @@ everything
drugs need @@ long @@ knows @@ disappear @@ body
important specialist @@ instructs @@ aware
ard documentary regarding @@ russian whistle @@ fogel @@ blowers
think @@ hearing @@ allegations
inflammatory enough @@ run @@ afraid
whistle @@ still @@ russia @@ blowers
russia @@ ran @@ program @@ got
bombshell
russian athletes @@ man 99 @@ guilty @@ doping
recent german documentary aired @@ ard @@ according
woman wada @@ craig reedie @@ promised @@ president @@ investigation
effective immediately
craig reedie @@ wrong @@ make @@ kind @@ assumption
media @@ allegations
proven guilty @@ athletes must @@ presumed @@ innocent
wild allegations @@ check
richard mclaren reedie @@ something
independent commission @@ created
investigative experience @@ half @@ decade
big investigations
like us olympic committees @@ major league baseball
bonds hits one high @@ man @@ ding
track @@ russia @@ mandate @@ field @@ athletics
wada chairman named @@ independent commission
said @@ let @@ get @@ ."
doping agency wants @@ year @@ report @@ man @@ end @@ anti
athletics officials say @@ cooperate
actions might @@ unclear @@ though @@ taken
thomas daigle @@ cbc news
gonna pass @@ gonna @@ okay @@ fogel
gonna cause @@ --
growing
tornado coming @@ like
many units @@ receiving @@ okay
moscow scientist @@ fogel grigory @@ showing
testing @@ sochi
big russian doping scandal @@ center
russia @@ doping @@ athletes @@ 80s
never stopped @@ really @@ apparently
richard pound @@ crazy thing @@ fogel
15 years @@ wada @@ head @@ guy
lead @@ investigation @@ hired @@ grigory @@ actually
want @@ um @@ know
meaning
shit @@ know @@ die @@ computer
know
power cord @@ right @@ let @@ grab @@ charger @@ back
someone else @@ better decision @@ might @@ choice
comfort level @@ using @@ guy @@ coach
find someone else @@ looking
would label grigory @@ doping doctors ." @@ know @@ guess @@ call
even know @@ biochemist
even matter @@ shit @@ like
finding someone else @@ fogel look
numbers look great @@ brandt
pretty much right @@ want @@ testosterone
typical wash @@ urine @@ negative @@ grigory @@ go
full treatment @@ testosterone
take usually @@ many days @@ seven
two weeks @@ rodchenkov @@ nice @@ bryan
could test @@ way @@ states
gotta go back @@ frozen urines @@ test
heavy control @@ way
wada @@ inquiry
brandt yes
dangerous person @@ see @@ like
test done @@ best way @@ basically get @@ think
maybe @@ hopefully
would like @@ maybe @@ la @@ come
smuggle something @@ urines @@ russia
um stammers
salt lake city @@ another lab @@ send @@ em @@ could
strictly prohibited
indistinct chatter
speaking russian @@ skinny
skinny
urine @@ unfreeze @@ freezer @@ fogel
rodchenkov yes @@ unfreeze @@ homogenize
make sure everything @@ melted
took special bottles @@ smuggling urine
scenario like @@ urine @@ make @@ collecting
morning ." @@ grigory one
grigory two ." @@ evening @@ 28th
recode
perfect
urine @@ source @@ otherwise
right
week period @@ two @@ three @@ goal
chronic level @@ push @@ extreme @@ acute
fogel max @@ okay @@ --
loves
max -- @@ fogel yeah
kick max @@ okay
go away @@ max
good time
laughing @@ later
second acceleration whenever @@ want @@ stone @@ good @@ fifteen
need girls @@ cheerleaders
stone right @@ poms @@ pom @@ maybe @@ get @@ exactly
right @@ like
big power @@ working @@ rodchenkov @@ catlin @@ 1989
ucla @@ located @@ laboratory @@ campus
catlin twenty years ago @@ way @@ get @@ develop @@ decided
actually friendly @@ soviets
would invite soviets @@ us @@ come
choose athletes @@ wanted @@ test @@ pick
watching @@ test @@ soviets @@ em @@ bring
first representative @@ grigory
bright orange shorts @@ second day @@ work @@ shows
santa monica marathon @@ gonna enter @@ announces
darn thing
good athlete
running @@ rodchenkov @@ professional @@ almost
moscow university @@ five kilometers @@ 500 meters @@ 1
mother always pushed @@ swim @@ ski
using something @@ realized @@ people
next year @@ last year @@ nobody @@ muscles
also started @@ use @@ course @@ best
stanozolol
mother @@ injections @@ done
simple thing @@ 50 milligrams @@ course
mother injected @@ fogel wait @@ wait
yes @@ course
national team level @@ like olympic
training camp @@ cannot afford
moscow university @@ chemical department @@ graduated
liked doping control @@ liked sports
top field @@ since 1985 @@ world @@ worked @@ laboratories
moscow laboratory @@ mistake
wada ." @@ new director @@ upheld @@ need
became director
testosterone @@ taking @@ hgh @@ fogel
rodchenkov let @@ protocol @@ look
new year @@ starting @@ sketch @@ schematics
yes @@ sit @@ piece @@ paper
tubes @@ piss
take @@ fraction
took @@ coded @@ analysis
day two @@ day one @@ okay
day three @@ day four @@ day five
rodchenkov seven @@ nine @@ eight
nine urines @@ okay
starting -- @@ took @@ one @@ fogel
need @@ enough
okay
fogel okay
real code @@ three @@ hear @@ got
mafia
laughing
wada @@ chased
best laboratory @@ puzzled @@ piss @@ imagine @@ could
russia @@ evil @@ empire
propaganda
mutters
oh @@ god @@ fantastic
flakes
clicks tongue @@ sins
top
september @@ race @@ moscow @@ fogel @@ drink @@ come
next time @@ survive @@ okay
keeping laboratory @@ short leash @@ leash @@ wada @@ lab
asking many questions
sort @@ bullshit
like
underground laboratory @@ testing @@ pre
shadow laboratory ?"
laboratory @@ fully @@ course
everything @@ computers @@ cameras @@ barcodes
something @@ looking
secret lab @@ yes @@ underground @@ like
yes @@ batman
owns @@ lab
state
yes
terminal one @@ departing flight @@ okay
fogel yeah @@ woman @@ love
grunts
keep @@ donation
see @@ lot
full collection @@ presenting @@ people @@ pens
remember
gonna see @@ nice @@ --
yes @@ thanks @@ grigory @@ coming
recording @@ careful
like pornography @@ permitted @@ erotics
sports pornography @@ erotics
laughing
uh @@ september @@ see
rodchenkov yes @@ definitely
moscow @@ go @@ fogel
dick pound
wada specialists @@ moscow lab @@ investigative group @@ wanted @@ send
safe position @@ last fail @@ right @@ lab @@ director
potentially positive @@ sample
stop @@ reported
lab
provide us @@ much information @@ interviewed
fogel please tell @@ frozen piss @@ explode @@ bag
rodchenkov laughs
big secret
urines @@ bryan
steroid profile @@ analyzed urines
kept frozen @@ everything
full agenda @@ worry @@ okay
preliminary tests @@ rodchenkov @@ much
wada @@ leave
leaving tomorrow night
maybe monday @@ maybe friday @@ anyway --
fogel wada @@ bothering
rodchenkov @@ much @@ challenging
asking tons @@ wada @@ sniffing @@ questions
dick pound @@ yes @@ know
prove something @@ understand @@ starting @@ difficult
solution @@ see @@ outcome
see
racing @@ focus
keep digging @@ come
two @@ one @@ got @@ four @@ come
taking
last time @@ already better
250 watts @@ 100 watts @@ last year @@ year @@ 349
power right @@ last year @@ fogel @@ 20
yes @@ progression @@ gains @@ gain @@ finally
wait @@ moscow @@ come
fantastic @@ bryan
right @@ fogel @@ europe @@ epo @@ bring
fogel okay @@ rodchenkov
complete everything @@ rodchenkov @@ 17th
us soil @@ last injection @@ okay
rodchenkov @@ passing @@ customs @@ border
taking urine
biological passport @@ complete
woman words cannot describe @@ week @@ living
gonna shut @@ gonna break @@ entirely @@ body
french cycling federation calendar @@ man
doping policy @@ anti
race says @@ testing @@ peds @@ fogel @@ far
may come @@ test @@ aware
learn @@ fogel @@ came
worry @@ rodchenkov @@ grigory @@ fogel
helped @@ dope
wada lab @@ gonna test @@ samples @@ moscow
rodchenkov @@ clever
urine sample since @@ done
pioneer @@ like
little bag @@ gonna pee @@ fogel
victim @@ rodchenkov @@ ideas
august 21st
good luck tomorrow @@ see @@ end
announcer start time tomorrow morning @@ 7 15
fogel right @@ rodchenkov @@ priest @@ like
doping paranoia @@ healing
enough power @@ god @@ free
win @@ sentenced
scheme @@ place @@ fogel
announcer raise @@ arms
ready
start
ninety
crowd cheering @@ announcer pouly
indistinct shouting
stone @@ great
half minutes behind pouly @@ three
fucking great @@ fogel @@ bad
hauling ass @@ guys
top ten guys @@ group data @@ bryan
top ten @@ incredible @@ guys @@ fogel
rodchenkov @@ good
pro @@ fogel @@ could
rodchenkov @@ monster @@ laughs
sized monster @@ medium
stone bryan fogel @@ hear
come back @@ walkie @@ talkie @@ raise @@ bryan
stone bryan @@ yeah
stone speaking indistinctly
stone @@ charged
needed @@ dead @@ charged @@ battery
totally dead @@ dead @@ see @@ go
fogel fuck
shifting @@ fogel @@ derailleur @@ broke
yes @@ rodchenkov @@ bike
cannot shift @@ rodchenkov @@ gears
100 kilometers @@ fogel
rodchenkov @@ goodness
dropped ten places @@ rankings @@ okay @@ hmm
god
really stronger @@ year @@ fogel @@ feel
brandt yeah @@ recovering @@ like
hauling ass @@ mean @@ fogel
different -- @@ em @@ beating
best day @@ know @@ guys @@ could @@ beat
whole plan @@ fogel
substantially better performance @@ year
get separated @@ stone
neutral descent
better last year @@ year @@ man @@ hurt
21 years old @@ mean @@ could
blood bags @@ world @@ taken @@ epo
tour de france champion @@ still @@ going
matter
stay optimistic @@ rodchenkov
change nothing
peter pouly @@ winner @@ announcer
crowd applauds
felt pretty good @@ rodchenkov @@ fogel @@ --
bad luck days @@ fogel
rodchenkov bryan @@ look
stop
turning point
fantastic material @@ happy
ten times @@ dick pound @@ armstrong together @@ information
fogel really @@ worry @@ continue
first floor @@ reception @@ like @@ enter
second
second floor @@ fogel
see @@ rodchenkov @@ moscow @@ go
fogel @@ cool
20 blood tests @@ many tests @@ probably @@ 15
rodchenkov @@ okay @@ enough
yes @@ laboratory @@ fogel
bloody rusada @@ see @@ oh
bringing samples @@ show @@ good @@ camera
want us @@ fogel oh @@ yes @@ hide
fogel okay
material @@ careful
sensitive also @@ fogel yes @@ people @@ know
director place
famous laboratory @@ world
cannot say explicitly @@ analyzed
already solved everything yesterday @@ coming
say within two weeks @@ let
done still @@ table @@ say
clears throat @@ fogel okay @@ okay
rodchenkov smile @@ go downstairs @@ race
scientists @@ fogel
wada laboratories today @@ working
suspect could @@ corrupted
rodchenkov @@ like @@ laboratory @@ director
sign @@ ethics @@ code
harmful @@ detrimental
whole anti @@ doping society
emergency exit @@ go
russia @@ fogel
hiding blood passports @@ athletes
rodchenkov let @@ talk @@ office
hide fight @@ 50 honest @@ doping @@ cannot
honest @@ hide @@ ends
orwell @@ 1984
cannot escape @@ wada @@ religion @@ like
cannot steal money @@ money @@ think
women @@ think
prostitution @@ married @@ go
almost everybody @@ sinners @@ period
answer
last five months @@ took urine @@ blood -- @@ fogel
rodchenkov yes @@ good database
wanna show @@ go @@ analysis
put together
bigger story arc @@ optimistic @@ bryan
smile @@ chuckles
vodka
yes
best vodka @@ kind
mordovia
drink vodka @@ oh @@ awesome
like -- @@ like vodka @@ vodka @@ yeah
gonna leave russia @@ gonna stay @@ decided
would like @@ stay
relaxing country @@ world @@ russia
think
laughing
fun @@ fogel
yes @@ fun
smile
speaking russian
bryan
singing @@ russian
indistinct chatter
man ladies @@ welcome @@ members @@ media @@ gentlemen @@ geneva
serious doping allegations @@ year ago @@ almost
german television channel ard @@ first raised
sir craig reedie @@ wada president
thorough inquiry would @@ full @@ conducted @@ announced
world anti @@ founding president @@ doping agency
dick pound @@ mr @@ commission @@ chair
overwhelming portions @@ ard program @@ allegations made
independent commission @@ true @@ found
found cover @@ worse @@ ups @@ thought
found destruction @@ samples @@ laboratories
conceal doping tests @@ found payments @@ order @@ money
among others
happened @@ could @@ conclusion
without @@ knowledge @@ happen @@ continue
state authorities @@ implied consent @@ either actual
reading @@ fogel
forty pages @@ report @@ grigory
imagine @@ hard
russian state interest @@ urine would @@ athletes
big concerns @@ tests @@ one @@ destroyed @@ 400 @@ 1
moscow laboratory @@ director
recommendation @@ laboratory @@ fact @@ director
wada accreditation @@ withdrawn @@ removed @@ position
russian federation @@ suspended
line ringing
veronika bryan @@ fogel hi @@ hi
grigory go
crying
yes
think maybe @@ want @@ speak
little bit nervous @@ maybe
rodchenkov bryan @@ sorry
understand @@ trying @@ sorry @@ saying @@ --
absolutely saying @@ rodchenkov @@ overturn @@ bullshit
upside
hardly could talk @@ tonight @@ bryan
line disconnects
woman @@ details @@ damning
russian athletics @@ profound impact @@ future @@ could
accused russian athletics @@ wada commission @@ man
sponsored doping @@ state
explanation needed @@ russian @@ response @@ provide @@ preparing
say @@ point
could potentially miss next year @@ olympics @@ mean
potential outcomes @@ certainly one @@ well
international olympic committee @@ statement @@ released @@ man
see athletes @@ sanctioned @@ iaaf
see athletes @@ officials @@ excluded
action led @@ see @@ ioc
tolerance policy @@ zero @@ apply
man decision time @@ iaaf
whether russia @@ field athletes @@ track
rio olympics @@ compete @@ allowed
athletics federation @@ want @@ russia @@ hear
actually saying @@ answer @@ allegations
vitaly mutko @@ sports minister @@ said @@ man
necessary measures ," @@ russia took @@ doping problem @@ says @@ fight
doping lab @@ moscow @@ anti
world ." @@ recently recognized @@ one @@ best
want @@ us @@ talk
well @@ tight @@ lipped @@ lab @@ employees @@ clearly
world anti @@ doping agency @@ report
great detail @@ goes
alleged activities inside @@ describing @@ building
around 50 correspondents @@ rodchenkov
fence @@ behind
talk @@ supposed
stay quiet @@ bryan
lucky man @@ knowing
skype call ends
holy shit
doping agency suspended russia @@ world anti @@ testing lab @@ sports drug
lab resigned @@ head
russian grisha @@ veronika @@ tell @@ careful
tell @@ rodchenkov @@ --
veronika @@ phone @@ holding
call back -- @@ sounds serious @@ rodchenkov tell @@ veronika
five minutes @@ call back @@ rodchenkov
veronika okay @@ rodchenkov yes @@ go away
veronika fine
rodchenkov bryan
english @@ disaster
killing people
cutting heads @@ without @@ know @@ guilty
minister mutko @@ yesterday @@ went @@ know
started @@ discuss
talking @@ football @@ blah
formula 1 @@ uh @@ blah
bloody doping @@ say
yes ." @@ resign ?" @@ say @@ go @@ could
today ?" @@ today ." @@ yes
resigned
lost director
telephones @@ lot @@ changing @@ calls
almost empty @@ people @@ looking @@ laboratory @@ job
empty
know @@ going
reading @@ press @@ newspaper @@ know
know
really @@ oh
mean @@ come
gonna arrest @@ gonna
would @@ try @@ put @@ jail
jail
reason @@ jail
know
danger
yes @@ know @@ jail @@ could
mean -- @@ moving @@ know
security man
security guard
security guard @@ home
home @@ coming @@ car
following behind
week @@ recommended @@ end
sides @@ man @@ kill
wada @@ russia
stay quiet
vitaly mutko @@ russian let @@ say
independent commission @@ report @@ reality
statements made @@ pound @@ mr @@ exaggerated
even built @@ doping laboratory @@ art anti @@ state @@ modern
testing @@ renowned
paralympics @@ olympics @@ championships
highest merits @@ received @@ contributions
merely financing @@ laboratory operation @@ government
independent commission @@ rodchenkov @@ english @@ accept
deliberately lying
bryan
fogel okay @@ look
bus anytime @@ tossed @@ rodchenkov @@ means @@ could
connecting freely @@ sure
sure @@ radar
know snowden
yeah @@ course
clicks tongue @@ see
still @@ know
whether russia @@ olympic games @@ participating
much cautious @@ outcome @@ life
purged
russia @@ olympics @@ okay @@ go
clicking tongue @@ survive @@ problem
yes @@ uh @@ listen
seriousness aside @@ stop @@ know @@ joking
worried
yes
tomorrow @@ drop
say clicks tongue
los angeles ?" @@ anything related @@ weather
20 minutes @@ talk @@ means @@ 15
talk @@ ready
sebastian coe tonight @@ sport finds @@ shameful situation
overwhelmingly voted @@ council @@ confirm
russian federation @@ immediate effect @@ suspend
22 votes @@ uh @@ one @@ done
strongest sanction continues indistinctly
russian regarding @@ recent events
field team @@ track @@ connected
sports minister @@ sports colleagues @@ urge
number one priority @@ make
first step
internal investigation @@ vital @@ secondly @@ conduct
clears throat sport @@ fair
responsibility @@ personalized @@ absolute
rodchenkov bryan
need wait @@ look
yeah
walk @@ need @@ escape
go wherever @@ want
sitting @@ okay @@ home @@ doggy
wanna get
yes @@ simply
want @@ uh
way ticket @@ suspicious @@ one @@ know
round trip @@ yeah @@ right @@ book
watching us @@ veronika @@ russian
rodchenkov bryan @@ yeah
rodchenkov @@ nothing
okay
stammering
flight options @@ send @@ okay @@ let @@ figure
okay
gonna get @@ right @@ fogel @@ flight
rodchenkov yes @@ right @@ okay
rodchenkov go
security measures @@ set @@ also
okay @@ made @@ know @@ fogel
rodchenkov um
know
okay
rodchenkov bryan @@ yeah @@ right
security man @@ fogel okay @@ okay @@ left
much dizzy @@ rodchenkov @@ paranoid
get @@ fogel
children decided maybe @@ wife @@ stay @@ russia @@ rodchenkov @@ better
gotta make sure @@ okay also @@ us @@ fogel
rodchenkov @@ daughter
fogel yes
getting married @@ rodchenkov
fogel right
rodchenkov married @@ everything
time
fogel okay
rodchenkov cross fingers @@ fogel
rodchenkov remember orwell
darkness ." @@ meet
year ago @@ first interviewed @@ fogel
thought @@ investigation @@ asked
defining moment @@ would @@ sport @@ history
would @@ question @@ answer
defining moment @@ yes @@ think
number one olympic sport @@ got @@ crosshairs
major olympic countries @@ got one @@ world
crosshairs
moment @@ even @@ crosshairs @@ athletics
sport @@ potential @@ credibility @@ affecting
continued viability @@ therefore @@ sport
would @@ watch @@ fixed @@ event
indistinct announcement @@ pa
fogel
yes @@ escaped
escaped alive @@ -- yes @@ chuckles
come
laughing
fogel
working place @@ rodchenkov destroyed @@ computer
took hard disk @@ three copies @@ also
historical moment
phone grigory @@ dan cogan @@ want @@ know
visible @@ understand @@ desire
think @@ safe @@ important
phone yesterday @@ edward snowden @@ lawyer
recommendations
office computer @@ everything @@ destroyed @@ also
safe place @@ put @@ like @@ dummy @@ dropped
talk @@ hours @@ cogan
rodchenkov uh @@ uh @@ huh @@ fogel
like @@ labyrinth
fogel yeah
place @@ okay
rodchenkov good @@ um
bed @@ bathroom
rodchenkov secure place
good thing
least till @@ work @@ plan @@ get @@ fogel
gonna
since may @@ rodchenkov @@ remembers @@ goes
learning russian
learning russian @@ soon
missing dogs
one thing @@ ic report @@ noticed
kgb people hanging around @@ lab
real
nice people @@ kgb people @@ know
home
suspicious reputation @@ interpreter @@ banish
russian athletics @@ leadership
renewed athletics @@ new people @@ 60 days @@ present
kgb @@ guess @@ fsb @@ fogel @@ called
lab
else could finance @@ vitaly mutko
think vitaly mutko finances @@ oh @@ fsb
state security operation @@ putin
state security apparatus @@ whoever finances @@ well @@ runs
sport minister
man officials @@ essentially saying @@ problems @@ may
already taken steps @@ trying
problems ." @@ address
essentially rejecting @@ officials @@ idea
major problem @@ still
russian honey @@ hi
far away @@ darkness
see
wearing fancy suits @@ making speeches @@ tv @@ ties
farce
english @@ disappointed @@ course
laboratory @@ closed
ic report @@ watching @@ reading @@ eyes @@ another
could change @@ truth @@ telling @@ past @@ know
like telling @@ would @@ truth @@ annihilated
george orwell @@ reading @@ first @@ 1989
soviet union @@ time
book 1984 @@ strictly prohibited @@ strictly
totally shocking
strength ." @@ ignorance @@ especially
powerful thing
weapon
gave @@ definitions @@ coordinates
life @@ apply
road map @@ like
reintegration ,' said @@ three stages @@ brien @@ "'
understanding @@ learning
acceptance
first stage .'" @@ enter upon @@ time
thinking @@ start
yes @@ questions @@ ask @@ answer @@ ."
statewide doping system @@ systematic @@ russia @@ place
olympics @@ cheat
yes
statewide system @@ mastermind
olympics @@ cheated
yes @@ course
2008 beijing olympics @@ 73 medals @@ total @@ russia
many @@ dirty @@ athletes
thirty
81 total medals @@ russia @@ many @@ london @@ dirty
oh @@ even
sure @@ let @@ 50
earned using special program
state @@ sponsored @@ course
russian doping system @@ putin aware @@ existence
yes @@ name @@ aware
special affair @@ took @@ prison
yes @@ prison
redeem
one sec @@ okay @@ let @@ back
would use @@ something @@ discredit @@ concern
oh @@ course
first criminal investigation
happened
say @@ oh @@ happened @@ easy
biggest producer @@ china @@ anabolics @@ 2008
produced @@ pharmaceutical
good manufacturing practice @@ well @@ equipped
high qualities @@ contamination
united states @@ europe @@ coming @@ anabolics
russia @@ like
time @@ russia @@ laboratory @@ head @@ course
system @@ part
level witch doctors @@ four top @@ three
like portugalov
russian national team @@ famous anabolic coach @@ portugalov
soviet time
portugalov @@ conveyor @@ athletes
great success @@ really @@ protocols
became olympic champions
problem began @@ 2008
jacques rogge @@ president @@ olympics
told government @@ china
producing anabolics @@ olympic country @@ bulk
stop @@ like @@ cannot @@ anymore @@ ."
stop @@ officially
supplying steroids @@ national team
concern
buy stanozolol @@ stanozolol
portugalov @@ confident
providing things @@ tested @@ proven @@ offering
impurities @@ detectable @@ could
oh ," portugalov say @@ much money @@ spent
could advise @@ maybe @@ ?"
trash @@ drop @@ advice
moscow laboratory
detection limits @@ best sensitivity
long term metabolites @@ test @@ proud @@ created
detection window @@ caused
three weeks @@ six months @@ two @@ enlarge
portugalov suddenly @@ many positives
national team @@ people
steroids @@ get @@ came @@ ask
knew one source
whole steroid program @@ suddenly @@ coordinating
portugalov @@ fogel @@ cutting
rodchenkov yes
saving national team @@ purchasing dirty steroids
know whether @@ purpose @@ eventually
portugalov @@ fight
became enemy
criminal narcotic police came @@ took @@ home @@ computer
monday ." @@ said @@ arrest
paralyzed @@ depression
know @@ escape @@ decided
took @@ knife
wife @@ sharp @@ kitchen
drank whiskey @@ sit @@ bath
smooth @@ goes
water @@ see @@ like @@ blood
strong @@ lock
wife opened door
siren wailing
seared @@ heart
good surgeon
suicide @@ since @@ considered
psychiatric clinic @@ sent
seeing @@ depressed
crazy drugs @@ started @@ give
totally @@ reality
something happened
criminal police
another psychiatric clinic @@ sentence
sadist
worst criminals @@ totally worst
professor ." @@ respected @@ much @@ chuckles @@ called
get better @@ better
use computer @@ funny thing @@ allowed
psychiatric clinic like @@ laboratory director @@ working @@ head
whole russian national team @@ advising
time
olympic committee @@ received @@ london @@ invitation
2012 olympic games @@ director
little bit uncertain @@ russian ministry @@ full @@ criminal
wada said
see @@ russia @@ rodchenkov @@ candidate
london another director ." @@ london @@ send
important @@ imagine
national team @@ london laboratory @@ information
london laboratory @@ testing @@ information
understand @@ much @@ danger
russian doping situation @@ without @@ collapsed
mutko understood @@ thanks @@ god
moscow investigators @@ received @@ call
grigory
dropped ." @@ case
took care @@ charges dropped @@ got
putin @@ course
sochi instead @@ success @@ redemption @@ prison
two workers @@ russian @@ rodchenkov @@ kamaev
mission @@ mind
revolution @@ mission
wada strategy @@ course @@ anti
doping agency rusada @@ former head @@ woman @@ russia @@ anti
unexpectedly died
two months @@ nikita kamaev @@ death comes @@ resigned @@ post
rocked russia @@ doping scandal @@ obviously @@ following
world @@ sighs @@ rest @@ athletics
see
told @@ rusada @@ man
doping agency @@ head @@ formerly
massive heart attack @@ appears
rodchenkov @@ course
bryan
know @@ friend
friend
died
show
previous history @@ heart problems @@ man @@ got
rodchenkov speaking russian
nikita died ." @@ means @@ grigory
enormous shock @@ man @@ died
friend since school time @@ rodchenkov
never complained @@ heart
health problem
young wife
talking @@ dreamed @@ day @@ children
cannot understand @@ still
like @@ cannot
wrote book
write book @@ russia @@ dangerous
gotta figure @@ know @@ fogel
course
would @@ think
danger game @@ sport @@ playing @@ history @@ bryan
pay everything @@ wada @@ ready @@ disappear
past @@ future @@ destroy
bad man still @@ mentioned @@ know
deputy minister mutko
could kill everybody
kgb man
moral @@ dangerous
writing book @@ oh @@ nikita
two @@ tired @@ oh @@ fifty
desperate
next week ." @@ prepare obituary @@ please @@ oh
imagine easily @@ imagine
much careful
reporting @@ fogel
yuri nagornykh @@ vice minister
practically involved @@ everyday routine
would report @@ rodchenkov yes @@ yuri @@ fogel
fogel yuri would report @@ rodchenkov yes @@ mutko
mutko reported @@ yes @@ rodchenkov @@ putin @@ fogel
rodchenkov @@ rest @@ paranoid @@ know
around 12 30 @@ one @@ night @@ fogel @@ clock
two @@ rodchenkov @@ know
hanging around
rodchenkov yes @@ fogel somebody @@ courtyard
two strong men knocked @@ door @@ darkness @@ appeared
let @@ came @@ asked
many relevant @@ auxiliary things @@ talking @@ sport
nikita kamaev @@ knew @@ death
minister mutko @@ first @@ boss
mutters @@ inspection
nerves @@ exhausts
finally gave @@ subpoena
united states district court
grigory rodchenkov ." @@ see
grand jury @@ front @@ fogel @@ commanded @@ appear
two fbi agents @@ ed stier @@ approached
new york @@ want @@ go
grand jury @@ provide @@ information @@ appear
whole series @@ triggered @@ made @@ decisions
two guys @@ checked
everyday agent @@ guys
come @@ cogan
something else @@ want
come
trying @@ make @@ case
la @@ found
mutko @@ guy @@ boss @@ actually
survive @@ lawyer @@ able
sports ministry @@ best friend @@ putin @@ head
uh crime @@ sort
us legislature @@ like @@ example @@ done @@ could
united states justice department loves @@ charge broad conspiracies
favorite charging instrument
others @@ mutko @@ conspired @@ --
conspiracy since 1980 @@ conspiracy
reconsider moscow olympic games @@ let
united states @@ reconsider situation @@ 1984
right @@ lawyer
cooperation agreement @@ plea @@ looking @@ called
happens @@ end @@ day @@ cooperates
judge generally @@ likely @@ incarcerate
stier first @@ know whether
point @@ interested @@ bureau
could indict @@ turn @@ lawyer
talk @@ shitting @@ guys @@ gotta @@ fogel
sent back @@ important thing @@ stier @@ russia
would certainly @@ assassinated
grigory @@ fogel @@ discussing
go public @@ whether @@ way
prior @@ olympics
stier prior @@ saying @@ olympics
cooperating witness @@ established
may @@ able
right @@ lawyer @@ downside
much less danger @@ think @@ stier @@ public @@ grigory
russians @@ hurt @@ anything
makes @@ look @@ guilty
lawyer except @@ heart attack @@ say @@ like
fogel grigory @@ look
best interest @@ story @@ break
uh
mean @@ disclose
automated voice please enter @@ participant id @@ thank
strongly suggest @@ 36 athletes @@ stay @@ rodchenkov @@ list
fogel okay @@ publish
sochi list @@ asking us @@ verify @@ authenticity
rodchenkov yes @@ authentic document @@ important
table @@ sochi
go behind @@ creation date @@ list
list came @@ ministry @@ fogel
rodchenkov @@ course
rebecca @@ fogel @@ file
see @@ properties @@ file @@ created
january 21st @@ tuesday @@ ministry
fogel oh @@ unrecognizable @@ god
recognizable
psychological @@ mirror @@ looking
new york times @@ breaking tomorrow
tomorrow
need sighs @@ need @@ oh
intravenous injections
tomorrow @@ relax
rodchenkov @@ okay @@ happening
justice yet @@ spoke @@ fogel @@ department
told @@ phone @@ lawyer
reacted like @@ would @@ expected
upset
right
wanted @@ provide @@ know @@ documents
provided lists @@ doped athletes @@ fogel
fsb file @@ testing @@ sochi @@ provided @@ arranged
gonna terminate @@ yeah @@ whole @@ unfortunately
gonna cancel @@ turned @@ documents
gonna prosecute
second stage ." @@ enter upon @@ time @@ rodchenkov
international olympic committee @@ jacques rogge
honor @@ announcing
22nd olympic winter games @@ 2014
sochi @@ city @@ awarded
cheering
russia @@ future @@ everything @@ country
olympic dream @@ united @@ russia @@ millions @@ citizens
national pledge @@ best choice @@ choice @@ sochi
level decision @@ top @@ rodchenkov
mean @@ know
vladimir putin @@ big boss @@ saying
best result @@ sochi @@ show
must show @@ others @@ ."
man hurrah @@ crowd hurrah
hurrah
could make team clean @@ one month @@ sochi @@ rodchenkov
crowd cheering
use peds @@ sochi @@ decided
top level @@ could @@ competition
right
announcer vladimir putin
announcer speaking french
using @@ science @@ instead @@ fogel
get around @@ system @@ science @@ developed
science @@ abandoned
yes
yes ." @@ important @@ forget
ladies @@ gentlemen
international olympic committee @@ 126th session @@ let @@ declare
open
audience applauding @@ thank
rodchenkov opening ceremony @@ heartbreaking day
sports history
story @@ hi @@ bryan @@ broke
stammering @@ published @@ mean
yes @@ published @@ gasps
story @@ published
new york times @@ tv according @@ rodchenkov @@ man
okay
photo @@ bottles
nikita kamaev @@ given @@ bottles
grigory rodchenkov @@ ran @@ laboratory
handled testing @@ thousands @@ olympians
drug cocktail @@ banned substances @@ three @@ said @@ developed
russian athletes @@ provided @@ mixed @@ liquor @@ dozens
facilitate one @@ helping @@ elaborate
successful doping ploys @@ sport history ."
sighs deeply
thomas bach join @@ fair play @@ support @@ fight
athletes deserve
fellow olympic athletes
play fair @@ say @@ rules @@ respect @@ clean
crowd cheering
sochi @@ fogel @@ 2014
russia swap @@ dirty urine @@ clean urine
always
dramatic music playing
little bottle @@ information contained @@ narrator
level playing field @@ helps keep sport
created adams
management system @@ free anti @@ doping administration @@ wada
security typically used @@ financial institutions @@ operating @@ level
centralized clearing house @@ effect @@ becoming
doping information @@ anti
play true @@ everyone @@ adams
fogel walk us @@ collection process
doping control officer @@ dick pound @@ sample @@ provided @@ front
two @@ divided @@ container
b sample @@ sample @@ fogel
catlin bottles @@ kits @@ fogel @@ called @@ bereg
one particular company @@ yes @@ switzerland @@ makes
berlinger bottle @@ mclaren @@ called
berlinger bottle @@ state @@ art
like device @@ vice @@ tight @@ sealed
watching @@ right @@ collector
lab @@ goes
pulled aside @@ b bottles @@ put @@ lab @@ freezer
analytical work @@ sample @@ done
olivier rabin @@ way @@ sample @@ collect
trustability @@ sample
b sample @@ got @@ fact
safe system @@ uh
mclaren @@ caps @@ bottles
way @@ taken @@ need @@ destroyed @@ designed
cracks open @@ sample @@ lab @@ device @@ catlin
way @@ get
sample tests positive @@ b gets analyzed @@ pound
confirm @@ b
enormous protection
sochi @@ rodchenkov @@ preparation @@ nagornykh
strict order @@ new bottles @@ develop procedure
open cap @@ new caps
fsb officer
gave closed bereg @@ responsible @@ kit @@ day
receive @@ opened @@ hour @@ half
cap @@ bottle
imitates pouring
little bit rinse @@ pour @@ close
imitates lid locking
like bereg @@ kit
unbelievable @@ could
named operation sochi resultat
achieve positive results ." @@ russian @@ resultat @@ means
need clean urines @@ fogel
need clean urines @@ rodchenkov @@ candidate
every single russian athlete @@ sponsored doping @@ state @@ fogel
clean samples @@ urine @@ held
yes
could swap @@ athlete needed @@ swapped @@ fogel @@ em
rodchenkov yes
double control @@ sochi @@ olympics
wada @@ know @@ ioc
unbelievable @@ stunning @@ security @@ level
foreign scientists @@ rabin @@ delegation
laboratory @@ embedded
substitutions @@ manipulations
people would @@ front line @@ observe
sochi @@ like @@ laboratory
entrance
fire exit @@ behind
kgb building @@ another building
clean urines @@ kept @@ bank
final two heats @@ man coming @@ man bobsleigh @@ four
pilot alexander zubkov @@ brakeman alexey voevoda
crowd cheering
russia @@ gold
oldest man ever @@ man bobsleigh @@ win @@ pilot @@ making @@ four
many fsb officers @@ working @@ sochi @@ fogel
hundred
kgb officer @@ throughout @@ day
clean urines @@ athletes selected @@ testing @@ brought
secret operational room @@ laboratory
urines collected @@ meanwhile @@ day @@ athletes
olympic village @@ 2 00 @@ 1 00 @@ transported @@ held
received @@ call
15 minutes ." @@ samples @@ grigory @@ delivering
samples arrived @@ make sure @@ time @@ gave
ioc observers left snooping around @@ wada @@ laboratory
samples @@ checked
operation entered @@ dangerous phase
two different carts @@ b bottles @@ split
storage room @@ b bottles @@ assistant wheeled
russian athletes @@ lab coat @@ b bottles @@ slipped
highly illegal @@ dirty urines @@ replace @@ need
wheeled @@ cart @@ bottles
per procedure @@ aliquoting room
supposed @@ opened @@ fogel @@ cause
yes @@ samples @@ rodchenkov
video recording @@ aliquoting room @@ like @@ escape
room @@ hole
little bit @@ take
uh @@ thing @@ say @@ --
something @@ like
take @@ table @@ like
power outlet blocked without @@ uh socket @@ like
take @@ right @@ okay
power outlet without @@ looks like @@ socket
hole
taking @@ samples @@ rodchenkov @@ hole
samples @@ immediately
pour away @@ clean
b sample @@ fogel
rodchenkov b samples @@ whew @@ taken @@ kgb
trash fire exit @@ people coming @@ darkness
imitating footsteps
b bottles opened @@ two hours @@ came back @@ swap
advance clean urine @@ course
urine swapping @@ b samples @@ finished
taken @@ kgb @@ --
term storage @@ b samples @@ taken @@ long @@ ioc @@ held @@ fogel
rodchenkov yes
ioc retest @@ would @@ wada @@ samples @@ fogel @@ clean
rodchenkov reanalysis @@ return negative
level cheaters @@ top @@ know
chuckles
cheat us @@ much @@ experienced
experience @@ comes
chuckles
evidence brought forward @@ fogel
wada lab @@ showed @@ country
collection bottles @@ way @@ found @@ break
entire testing system @@ would say @@ think
would say @@ gone @@ depths @@ corruption
would @@ process @@ part @@ disturbing
would @@ uh
serious act @@ serious @@ obviously @@ manipulation @@ lab
would @@ work @@ done
testing system @@ done successfully
catch drug cheats today @@ wada @@ fogel @@ ability
choir singing russian national anthem
whole steroid program @@ rodchenkov
13 gold medals @@ pulled
unbelievable
never @@ chuckles
much happy @@ made clean @@ putin @@ everything
anthem continuing
woman russia came @@ medals board @@ top
winning 33 overall @@ olympic high @@ 13 gold @@ including
crowd cheering
started war @@ ukraine @@ rodchenkov @@ immediately
olympics @@ man
popularity rating @@ falling steadily @@ years @@ russia
games began
personal guilt @@ rodchenkov @@ felt @@ event
would russia @@ putin would @@ less medals @@ aggressive
tom clancy novel @@ man @@ lifted @@ hear
john le carr @@ elegant prose @@ borrowed
robert ludlum @@ work @@ adapted
protagonist @@ believed
vladimir putin @@ ultimate handiwork @@ drama
intelligence successors @@ kgb
mother russia @@ lot safer @@ la may @@ recent @@ given
fogel yeah @@ bryan
incredible @@ good @@ article
reading twice @@ shocked
russia even cannot breathe @@ know
still even @@ respond
fogel let @@ stop @@ midnight @@ course @@ --
spoke @@ lawyer @@ happened
returning @@ fogel @@ calls
arrested
know yet @@ holding pattern @@ fogel
little bit afraid @@ sitting locked @@ home
fogel let @@ okay @@ get @@ done @@ come
putin @@ kill
man 2 allegations @@ man 1 rodchenkov
sochi medal winners @@ woman dozens @@ secret @@ part
rodchenkov nine @@ seven @@ one
overlapping chatter @@ russian
exhales sharply okay
since fled russia @@ said @@ man @@ life @@ feared
woman russia @@ sports minister @@ nonsense @@ dismissed @@ claims
russian sport @@ continuation @@ attack @@ adding
deputy sports minister @@ backed
russian @@ everyone @@ clear
doping program @@ never
woman vladimir putin calls @@ turncoat ." @@ slander @@ claims
collar attorney @@ white @@ meeting @@ fogel
criminal cases @@ lot @@ handled
phone @@ man @@ lawyer @@ happened
moscow office @@ lawyer @@ fogel
firm got cold feet due @@ said @@ interest @@ conflict @@ appears
man thomas bach @@ said @@ ioc @@ heads
true
unimaginable level @@ criminality ."
worrying ." @@ ioc calling @@ woman @@ report
world anti @@ doping agency @@ man @@ ask
investigate immediately ."
man 2 @@ justice department @@ opening @@ investigation
russian government officials @@ coaches @@ athletes
doping authorities @@ anti
wada @@ sent @@ letter @@ fogel
new york times @@ recent declarations @@ dear grigory @@ light
would like @@ better understand @@ meet
proposed way forward @@ basis @@ allegations
olivier niggli ." @@ david howman @@ sincerely
talking tomorrow @@ another lawyer
seems credible @@ word @@ russia @@ course
older questions @@ russian @@ man
regarding rodchenkov @@ mental health
four years ago @@ failed suicide attempt
mental institution @@ placed
first stages @@ diagnosis described @@ schizophrenia
wife @@ rodchenkov @@ know @@ children
go crazy @@ disappear
howman bryan @@ go ahead @@ want @@ olivier @@ meeting @@ david
call us back
ready @@ answer
need something lucky @@ wonderland @@ like @@ alice
sit @@ rabbit @@ hole
wait @@ rodchenkov @@ know @@ fogel @@ ends
wanna chuckles @@ know @@ fogel
trying @@ right @@ make @@ get
trustful @@ rodchenkov @@ lawyer
big one @@ rodchenkov @@ fogel
rodchenkov yes @@ fogel yeah @@ top
digging deeper @@ russian @@ man @@ identity
exclusive documents @@ obtained
russian grigory rodchenkov @@ woman
american movie director bryan fogel
talked many times via e @@ wrote @@ mail
russian @@ man @@ following @@ fbi @@ closely
recent skype call @@ grigory rodchenkov @@ sister @@ mentioned
sit tight @@ russian grish @@ marina @@ impulsive
rodchenkov @@ course @@ anything
marina @@ course @@ absolutely
rodchenkov without @@ protection @@ fbi
speaking russian
man speaking russian
sorry @@ russian @@ refuse @@ make @@ comments
intelligent people @@ sure @@ explain
russian honey @@ already spoke @@ rodchenkov @@ fine @@ children
veronika grisha @@ another problem
worried
take care @@ rodchenkov @@ hold
worried @@ veronika
turning us @@ monster
trying
radchenkov @@ okay @@ get
want @@ veronika @@ come
rodchenkov @@ past @@ future @@ english
time @@ thought @@ free
undone ." @@ truth exists @@ done cannot
jim walden @@ interested @@ evidence @@ everyone
terms @@ documents @@ computer
cell phone @@ using @@ time
two people connected @@ russian doping program @@ dead
seem highly suspect @@ circumstances
first things @@ one @@ learned @@ authorities
came onto @@ case
russian government @@ resources
stage protocol @@ multi @@ develop
minimize @@ intercepted @@ conversations @@ chances
main concern @@ would @@ able
try @@ triangulate @@ location @@ communications
united states @@ harm @@ agents
84 days away @@ man
rio de janeiro @@ summer games @@ till @@ brazil
hard evidence @@ woman @@ athletics
whole range @@ sports @@ pointing @@ finger
justice investigation going @@ know @@ fogel @@ department
lawyer @@ grigory @@ advised
security reasons
six months @@ worked @@ grigory
russia @@ record @@ happened @@ compile
every single athlete @@ spreadsheet
mandated protocol @@ state
every single athlete @@ taking @@ london
sample numbers @@ including @@ collection
christiane goes back @@ samples correctly @@ tests
basically find @@ positive
london games @@ protocols
beijing
russia @@ outlines @@ collecting
clean samples @@ thousands @@ swapping
ask question @@ want @@ saw
understanding -- @@ well @@ done
increase specific gravity @@ sodium chloride @@ sample @@ added
samples @@ many @@ gonna
sodium content @@ hundred times @@ urine @@ somebody
make sure @@ understand @@ let
opened secretly @@ taking @@ b
yes
paralympic games @@ said @@ removed
paralympic games @@ happened also @@ mean
yes
swapped urine @@ paralympic games @@ olympic
urine swapping operation @@ vancouver @@ really @@ impetus
medals @@ handful
sochi @@ see @@ happen
find @@ --
time @@ terms @@ sensitive
sensitive @@ sense @@ london
next rio games @@ going @@ athletes
winter ones
sochi @@ london @@ fogel @@ beijing
way back @@ goes @@ 1968
russia @@ period @@ never @@ ever @@ doping @@ anti
summer sports @@ across
every sport
christiane ayotte @@ sorry
ayotte grigory
want @@ man @@ get
think @@ sochi @@ scientist @@ happy
gave credibility @@ lab @@ everything
feel good today @@ think
cheated feel good @@ think @@ athletes
one thing @@ guys might @@ think @@ fogel @@ angry
grigory risked @@ risking @@ life
wife behind @@ children behind @@ left
financial security behind @@ belongings behind @@ left
get everything
okay
dear mr @@ rodchenkov @@ fogel @@ dr
full confidence @@ ioc
professor richard mclaren @@ authority
comprehensive inquiry @@ respects @@ judgment @@ ensure
necessary measures @@ act swiftly @@ take
thomas bach @@ president ." @@ sincerely
automated voice transferring @@ richard mclaren
actually orders @@ orders @@ speak @@ mclaren
ordering grigory @@ ordering @@ nagornykh @@ lab
matter
ordering grigory @@ yes @@ nagornykh
soccer players @@ mails @@ like @@ explicitly @@ e
mails explicitly @@ weightlifters @@ know @@ e
essentially
swimmers @@ rowers
positive @@ grigory @@ found
mclaren @@ concerned
right profile @@ pick @@ one @@ find @@ bank
run @@ one @@ analysis
got
see @@ mclaren
quite mind @@ proved @@ blowing
sooner @@ okay @@ better
people around @@ world @@ mclaren @@ lot @@ important
fogel yes @@ rodchenkov
russian athletes could @@ international competition @@ credibly return
without undermining @@ public @@ confidence @@ competitors
russian sport @@ pride @@ man @@ joy
vaulter yelena isinbayeva @@ like pole @@ field stars @@ track
rio olympics @@ next month @@ gold @@ going
high places @@ friends @@ despite
yelena isinbayeva speaking russian
truly important @@ us
sniffles
audience applauding
field team finds @@ dire situation @@ track @@ today
olympics @@ banned
without @@ proof @@ evidence @@ aggressively
moscow wada lab @@ russian rodchenkov @@ man @@ director
resign @@ position @@ forced
even though @@ brilliant doctor @@ think
united states @@ somehow ends @@ fired
new york times @@ subsequently took @@ story
smallest paper @@ exactly @@ earth
turns @@ information @@ gets
entire doping program @@ stated @@ finally
run system @@ fact part @@ state
whatever @@ claims
government @@ confusing
see @@ government @@ claims
solo act
swapping @@ samples @@ destruction
farce
see @@ possible @@ could
please let @@ repeat
speculations @@ rumors @@ facts @@ allegations
mclaren independent commission @@ english welcome @@ woman
news conference @@ toronto
world anti @@ professor mclaren @@ doping agency @@ may @@ mandated
allegations made @@ respect
accredited moscow laboratory @@ former director @@ wada
grigory rodchenkov @@ dr
findings set @@ report @@ investigation @@ established
reasonable doubt @@ beyond
experts @@ determine
bottle caps @@ scratches @@ samples @@ marks @@ inside
tool used @@ representative @@ open @@ cap
samples suspected @@ swapped @@ set
confirm @@ able
tampering @@ evidence @@ 100
forensic analysis @@ conducted cyber
secured data @@ hard drives
reviewed thousands @@ pages @@ documents
moscow laboratory operated @@ doped russian athletes @@ protection
safe system @@ within @@ state @@ fail @@ directed
sport yuri nagornykh @@ deputy minister @@ sport @@ ministry
doping agency @@ russia @@ rusada @@ anti
moscow testing laboratory @@ former director
operation @@ involved
active participation @@ assistance
russian federal security service @@ formerly known @@ kgb
sochi lab @@ fsb @@ access
building maintenance contractor @@ guise
identified @@ evidence
alex mihailovich @@ rt
russia currently @@ rodchenkov @@ person @@ investigation
took @@ russia
seems @@ rely @@ really @@ character
rodchenkov @@ relies @@ lot
work @@ compromise
person @@ investigation
say without @@ truth @@ telling @@ rodchenkov @@ dr @@ doubt
truthful witness
corroborate @@ able
forensic information @@ scientific
system beyond @@ reasonable doubt @@ team @@ existence @@ demonstrate
richard mclaren @@ report @@ reedie @@ clear
independent commission @@ contained
proven @@ offenses @@ committed
think anybody @@ sitting back @@ accuse us @@ nothing
man president putin condemned @@ findings
dangerous recurrence @@ world @@ seeing @@ saying
politics interfering @@ sport
man russia @@ government says
collectively punishes @@ unacceptable @@ decision @@ competitors
richard conway @@ bbc news
sighs
hands like @@ rolling @@ gonna
work @@ makes @@ let @@ everybody @@ easier
today @@ russian @@ rodchenkov
worrying @@ veronika @@ day
today @@ paying @@ everything @@ etc @@ bills
rodchenkov nika @@ get
new glasses @@ oh
veronika @@ new
sad news @@ tell
yes
witness protection program @@ going
mm @@ hmm
current situation @@ unclear
yes @@ serious
yesterday @@ thinking
one thing @@ well @@ visa @@ --
keeper @@ family @@ dogs @@ bride
worrying @@ trying @@ top @@ reach @@ grigory @@ day
tell anyone anything
see much @@ even tell @@ would @@ days @@ anyone
time @@ sit @@ prison @@ pay @@ officials @@ maybe
formality
get going
yes @@ veronika
contact information @@ wrote @@ lawyer @@ everything
talking @@ know
understand @@ sad @@ course
english whatever packing @@ getting dressed @@ need @@ man
rodchenkov okay @@ okay
speaking indistinctly
uh @@ know @@ gonna @@ fogel @@ able
still @@ rodchenkov @@ organized @@ know
means protection @@ protection @@ organized @@ know
point @@ foresee @@ fogel
start writing book @@ chuckles
first floor @@ oh
exit
wonder @@ see @@ going
worry @@ laughs @@ back
sized monster @@ laughing bryan @@ medium
remember
inaudible
russian athletes @@ decided today @@ rio @@ compete
international sports federations @@ thomas bach
individual analysis @@ taking @@ carry @@ account
woman anti @@ doping officials @@ fuming
doping agency recommendations @@ world anti @@ ioc going
starter gun sounds @@ crowd cheering
man olympic champion @@ vlasov @@ gold
winston sank @@ sides @@ rodchenkov @@ arms
slowly refilled @@ lungs @@ air
mind slid away @@ labyrinthine world @@ doublethink
know
telling carefully constructed lies ." @@ complete truthfulness @@ conscious
announcer thomas bach
repudiate morality @@ laying claim @@ rodchenkov
forget whatever @@ forget @@ necessary
fair play @@ bach join @@ support @@ fight
play fair @@ rules @@ respect @@ clean
rodchenkov @@ memory @@ draw @@ back
needed @@ moment
justice @@ decision @@ bach
politics @@ justice @@ independent
hurrah
crowd hurrah
rodchenkov @@ promptly @@ forget @@ ."
man fails @@ gold medal @@ drug test @@ stripped
rodchenkov @@ process @@ apply @@ ."
man trying @@ make sure @@ testimony @@ clear
never taken drugs @@ many times @@ say @@ clear
man okay @@ think @@ clear
others accepted @@ rodchenkov @@ lie
became truth ." @@ lie passed @@ history
doping program @@ russian @@ russia @@ never
would never @@ something like @@ unthinkable @@ impossible
even recall @@ name @@ defected @@ citizen
russian anti @@ doping lab @@ ran @@ one
word @@ understand @@ rodchenkov @@ even @@ english @@ doublethink
doublethink ." @@ use @@ involves
first report @@ put @@ mclaren @@ findings @@ able
clearer focus @@ sharper
years @@ spectators @@ deceived @@ confirm
win medals @@ desire
olympic values @@ ethical compass @@ collective moral @@ superseded
parallel two things @@ rodchenkov
fully contradictory @@ canceled
doping @@ anti
exact doublethink @@ pure
slave @@ like
slavery @@ freedom
till @@ end
truth