theme music playing
thrones season 07 episode 06 title @@ wall @@ game @@ beyond
right @@ mm
north @@ ever
never seen snow
eh @@ beautiful
breathe
air smells like pig shit @@ south
south @@ never
winterfell @@ north
live
keep @@ freezing @@ balls
keep moving @@ secret @@ got
walking @@ good @@ fucking @@ fighting @@ better @@ best
living woman within @@ hundred miles
make @@ got
smart @@ one @@ maybe
strong fighter @@ davos says
smart @@ important @@ good
smart people @@ looking @@ dead @@ come
dragon queen @@ met @@ huh
fight beside us @@ knee @@ bend
much time @@ free folk @@ spent
like kneeling
mance rayder @@ brave man
proud man
wall never bent @@ knee @@ king @@ beyond
people died @@ pride @@ many
still mad @@ us @@ boy
witch @@ sold
priestess
subtle distinction @@ admit
wars cost money @@ great war @@ fighting
wanted @@ one
wanted @@ sold @@ join @@ brotherhood
slave @@ like
know
strapped @@ bed
stripped @@ sounds @@ right @@ naked @@ far
put leeches @@ naked
needed @@ blood
yes @@ thank @@ know
worse @@ wanted @@ kill @@ could
would @@ killed @@ davos
whinging
something @@ moving @@ lips @@ complaining
killed six times @@ one
hear @@ bitching
good lad
went north @@ first time @@ wall @@ father
good man
better son @@ deserved
end
wildlings @@ prisoner
avenged
want @@ know
every mutineer found justice
worse way @@ think @@ go
watch @@ night @@ life
protect every one @@ would @@ men @@ died
butchered
way @@ hate @@ died
honorable man @@ ever met @@ father
way @@ good
executioner @@ died @@ block
father wanted @@ know @@ execute
heard
right @@ course
make @@ less @@ hate
glad @@ catch
father gave @@ sword
wolf @@ pommel @@ changed @@ bear
still longclaw
lord commander mormont
never come back @@ westeros @@ thought
back
family @@ centuries
right
gave
son
brought shame onto @@ house
heart @@ father @@ broke
sword @@ right @@ forfeited @@ claim
well @@ serve @@ may
children
watch us @@ father used
say much
remember @@ probably
inside knitting @@ time
remember
shooting arrows @@ ser rodrik @@ one time @@ boys
came
bow behind @@ left @@ bran
lying @@ ground
ser rodrik would @@ saw @@ cuffed
one arrow @@ target
one around @@ like
stop @@ one
started shooting
every shot @@ go
walk back @@ one arrow @@ shoot @@ get
good
hit @@ finally @@ eye @@ bull
20th shot @@ could @@ 50th
remember
hit @@ heard @@ eye @@ bull
looked
standing right
smiling
rules @@ knew
wrong @@ smiling @@ knew
wrong @@ rules
meant @@ knew
dead
lannisters @@ killed
help
pretty handwriting
septa mordane used @@ knuckles @@ crack
write @@ well @@ cause
heavy heart @@ write @@ today @@ robb
good king robert @@ dead
boar hunt ." @@ wounds @@ took @@ killed
remember @@ read
treason @@ father @@ charged
beloved joffrey @@ robert @@ conspired @@ brothers
tried @@ throne @@ steal
well @@ treating @@ lannisters
every comfort @@ providing
landing @@ king @@ come @@ beg
swear fealty @@ king joffrey
great houses @@ strife @@ prevent
stark @@ lannister
sansa ." @@ faithful sister
forced
throat @@ knife
stretch @@ rack @@ put
bones started @@ pop
like @@ know @@ child
would @@ let @@ kill @@ family @@ betrayed
save father @@ way @@ told
stupid enough @@ believe
standing @@ remember @@ platform @@ joffrey @@ cersei
dragged father @@ block
pretty dress @@ wearing @@ remember
fancy way @@ remember @@ hair
crowd near baelor @@ statue @@ standing
come running @@ rescue
save father @@ lannisters @@ fight
wanted @@ like
betray robb @@ betray
entire family @@ beloved joffrey @@ betray
thanking @@ knees
winterfell @@ standing
win @@ jon @@ back
lost @@ battle @@ bastards
vale @@ knights @@ battle
rode north
world @@ traveling
training
well @@ training
could never imagine @@ suffered things
imagine quite @@ oh @@ lot @@ know
never would @@ survived
never know @@ guess
letter @@ going
know yet
show @@ find
scared
crimes @@ commit
well @@ one @@ hang @@ going @@ arya
show @@ scared @@ jon @@ angry
understand @@ jon
scared little girl
wicked lannisters @@ alone
saw us fighting @@ happy cersei would @@ right @@ know
wants @@ exactly
always wanted
tear us apart @@ scared
northern lords @@ read
think much @@ lady sansa
knew @@ cersei @@ bidding
would little lyanna mormont say
younger @@ wrote
child ?" @@ say @@ going
angry
sometimes anger makes people @@ unfortunate things
sometimes fear makes @@ unfortunate things
go @@ anger
dog ." @@ one @@ call
fuck
told @@ mean
hate wildings @@ born mean
give two shits @@ wildings
hate @@ gingers
gingers @@ beautiful
like @@ kissed @@ fire
fucking finger @@ point
trip @@ fire @@ baby
trip @@ pushed
ever since @@ mean
fuck
truly mean @@ think
sad eyes
want @@ suck @@ dick
dick @@ cock
dick @@ ah
like
bet
pussy @@ nope
beauty waiting @@ winterfell @@ back
ever get back
yellow hair @@ blue eyes
tallest woman @@ ever seen
tall @@ almost
tarth @@ know @@ brienne
fucking tarth @@ brienne
yet @@ well
way @@ see @@ looks @@ look
wants @@ liver @@ like @@ eat @@ carve
know
met
make babies @@ want
great big monsters @@ think
world @@ conquer
mad fucker like @@ long @@ live
killing people @@ good
look much like
father
suppose @@ mother @@ favor
knew
course
hand
sent @@ mountain @@ hunting
wildling friend told
red woman brought @@ back
back six times @@ thoros @@ brought
serve @@ lord
serve @@ north
raise @@ north @@ dead
light never spoke @@ lord
know anything
wants @@ know
wants @@ alive
know
know ." @@ tell @@ anyone
serving @@ point @@ god
us knows @@ wants @@ none
time @@ think
understand @@ think @@ purpose
except one thing @@ soldiers
know @@ fighting
barely know @@ woman @@ man @@ fighting
throne made @@ swords @@ sit
fighting
life
enemy @@ death
first enemy @@ last
die
enemy always wins
still need @@ fight
know
find much joy
keep others alive
defend
men ." @@ shield @@ realms @@ guards
understand @@ need @@ maybe
maybe @@ enough
aye
saw @@ fire
mountain like @@ arrowhead
sure
getting close
like @@ know
honestly @@ hero
oh
well @@ occasion @@ heroic
mud gate @@ landing @@ king @@ charged
want @@ hero
stupid things @@ heroes @@ die
jorah @@ drogo @@ daario
jon snow @@ even
try @@ outdo
bravest thing @@ stupidest
name @@ interesting @@ heroes
jorah @@ drogo @@ daario
jon snow @@ even
love @@ fell
jon snow @@ oh @@ mistake @@ love
suppose @@ stares @@ longingly
successful military alliance @@ hopeful
little
mean
quite little @@ heroes go
know @@ brave
hand @@ coward @@ chosen
goes well
finally get @@ sister @@ meet
told @@ everything
rather murder @@ speak
horrible way @@ torture @@ oh @@ first
murder
sister less @@ nobody trusts @@ believe
go @@ capital
two armies @@ three dragons @@ go
landing burns @@ foundation stones @@ anyone touches @@ king
trap @@ thinking @@ set @@ right
course
wondering @@ trap @@ laying
traps @@ laying
better world @@ want @@ new @@ create
sure deceit @@ mass murder @@ best way @@ start
without deceit @@ mass murder @@ war
yes @@ ruthless @@ need
win @@ throne @@ going
need @@ inspire @@ fear @@ degree
fear @@ cersei
joffrey @@ father
power brittle @@ makes
everyone beneath @@ see @@ longs @@ dead
aegon targaryen got quite @@ long way @@ fear
wheel @@ spoke @@ breaking
aegon built @@ wheel
want @@ queen @@ kind
tyrants @@ different @@ came
walk @@ lions @@ den
brother promised @@ keep @@ grip
lannister forces
lannister promises @@ forgive @@ care
except
promised
anything impulsive @@ keep
impulsive
difficult negotiation
see us @@ want @@ sitting @@ people @@ headless
say something provocative @@ sister @@ likely
known
time @@ temper @@ lose
great leaders
temper @@ lost
tarlys @@ instance @@ burning
impulsive
necessary
perhaps
father needed @@ son @@ perhaps @@ die
needed time @@ perhaps @@ mistakes @@ contemplate
cold cell @@ solitude
time @@ possibilities @@ discuss
possibilities @@ ended
one could @@ thinking @@ taking @@ forgiven
side @@ family @@ debate
taking @@ side
take @@ side @@ need @@ enemy
see things @@ way @@ going
see things @@ way @@ need
going @@ anticipate @@ actions
respond effectively @@ beat
want @@ much
world @@ want @@ build @@ believe
world @@ want @@ build
get built
single lifetime @@ probably
vision endures @@ ensure
stays broken @@ make sure @@ wheel @@ break
iron throne @@ want @@ sits @@ know @@ dead
say @@ children
ways @@ successor @@ choosing
one method @@ watch @@ night
many flaws @@ ironborn @@ another
wear @@ succession @@ discuss @@ crown
saw hundreds @@ grace @@ arrows
fly towards @@ blackwater rush @@ fought
saw hundreds @@ arrows miss
one @@ heart @@ found @@ ended @@ could
death quite @@ thinking @@ bit
one @@ items @@ discussed
landing @@ king @@ brother
long term @@ trying @@ serve @@ planning
short term @@ planned @@ perhaps
lost dorne @@ highgarden
wear @@ succession @@ discuss @@ crown
look
bear
big fucker
blue eyes @@ bears
get @@ eastwatch @@ back
flask
go
right
got bit @@ dead bear
aye
funny old life
right
know @@ get
seems @@ resourceful
worried
asking 20 @@ 000 men
worst winter @@ ever seen @@ us @@ fight
weather @@ problems @@ least
good reason @@ go home @@ many @@ happy @@ find
question @@ loyalty @@ jon
weeks @@ jon @@ heard
winterfell @@ lady
king chose @@ rule @@ absence
rule
wisely @@ ably
see @@ respect
may even prefer
yes @@ turned @@ jon @@ backs
retake winterfell @@ time @@ named @@ king
turn @@ ready @@ backs
trust men like @@ far would
bloody wind vanes
wrote @@ letter @@ found
already married @@ woman
two enemies @@ one @@ house
time jon comes back @@ army left
like @@ arya
sister
may @@ disagreements
would never betray @@ family
betray jon @@ would @@ thought @@ going
thinks
thinks @@ know
know @@ anymore
perhaps lady brienne could help
catelyn stark @@ sworn @@ protect @@ girls
way @@ planning @@ one @@ harm
honor bound @@ intercede
would
always wanted @@ something @@ right @@ know
pyke @@ drunk @@ charged @@ breach
remember charging @@ honest @@ breach
next morning @@ lads told
sounded like @@ good scrap
aye
proper scrap
ironborn thought @@ kind @@ god
flaming sword @@ way @@ waving
ever saw @@ bravest man @@ thought
drunkest
rest
wait long enough @@ find
run back @@ eastwatch
tell @@ raven @@ happened @@ get @@ daenerys
leaving @@ go @@ fastest
faster without @@ hammer @@ give
give
run @@ come
come
stop
go
happened
others
send @@ raven @@ need
maester @@ get
thoros
better ways @@ say @@ one @@ go
show us @@ way @@ lord @@ light
us @@ servant @@ light @@ lead @@ darkness @@ come
burn @@ body
close behind
send us @@ kind enough @@ unless @@ lord @@ light @@ fire @@ bit
lord @@ light
us @@ darkness @@ come
terrors @@ night @@ full @@ dark
freeze soon
water
white walker @@ killed
followed @@ fell @@ dead @@ almost
turned @@ one @@ maybe
walkers @@ go
stand @@ maybe @@ chance
thing back @@ us @@ take @@ need
raven flying @@ dragonstone
daenerys @@ chance
another
kill
turned
understand
lord brought @@ back
brought @@ back
one else @@ us
watch us freeze @@ death
priest @@ lost @@ careful @@ beric
last life
long time @@ waiting @@ end
lord brought @@ maybe @@ find
every lord @@ ever met @@ cunt
see @@ lord @@ light @@ different
lady
landing @@ king @@ invitation
winterfell @@ lady
represent @@ interests
see @@ gathering
want @@ invited
set foot @@ landing @@ king
cersei lannister @@ queen
want another stark prisoner
take @@ come
remain @@ belong
work
safe
ser jaime
treated @@ said @@ honorably
worried
safe leaving @@ littlefinger
would happily @@ many guards
imprison @@ behead
whether
trust @@ loyalty
trust @@ speaking @@ behind @@ back
least leave podrick behind @@ watch @@ let
competent swordsman @@ become
watched @@ need @@ minded @@ cared
child
winterfell @@ lady @@ home
safest place
lady
swore @@ sister @@ protect @@ oath @@ abandon
lady brienne @@ trip @@ long @@ landing @@ king
summer roads @@ traveling
time @@ sooner @@ making @@ leave @@ chances @@ better
yes @@ lady
important person @@ world
dangerous place @@ world @@ fly
one @@ else
risks @@ left @@ knew
win @@ throne @@ dead
wheel @@ dead @@ break
would
nothing
sometimes nothing @@ hardest thing
lost @@ die
everything @@ everyone
told @@ nothing @@ listened
nothing
dumb cunt
oh @@ fuck
fuck
yah
fall back
fall back @@ come
help
go
jon
leave @@ go
uncle benjen
ride @@ pass @@ come
time
go
meet @@ clegane
fucking hope
time @@ grace @@ go
bit longer
rider approaching
open @@ gate
looking
winterfell @@ men @@ loyal @@ hundreds
faces
get
faceless man @@ training @@ braavos
mean
braavos @@ back
first face @@ got
used @@ play @@ game
game @@ faces
simple
question @@ ask
make lies sound like @@ try @@ truth
win @@ fool
lose @@ lie @@ catch
play @@ let
want @@ play
king @@ jon @@ feel
someone else @@ north instead @@ think @@ rule
faces
want @@ asking
sure
well @@ turn @@ game @@ faces
last person @@ questions @@ asked
tell
younger @@ wanted @@ people
wanted @@ queen
young king @@ sit next @@ iron throne @@ handsome
wanted @@ knight
sword like father @@ pick @@ go @@ battle
us got @@ person @@ neither
let girls decide @@ world @@ going
faces @@ choose
become someone else
voice @@ speak
skin @@ live
could even become
would feel like @@ wonder
pretty dresses @@ wear
winterfell @@ lady
need @@ find
face
sorry
could take @@ wish @@ back
never gone @@ wish
seen @@ gone
see @@ know
know
dragons @@ children
ever @@ children
understand
night king @@ going @@ destroy @@ army
together
word
thank @@ dany
dany "?
last person @@ called
sure @@ brother
want @@ mm @@ keep @@ company
right
dany ."
queen "?
uh @@ knee @@ bend
swore allegiance
see @@ come
hope @@ deserve
rest @@ get
synchronized @@ srjanapala