talk @@ meaning
terrifying
simple request @@ president
tell us @@ see
environment strikes @@ bit odd @@ bit @@ anything
pick @@ phone
whether @@ seems @@ place @@ person @@ package
let us know @@ love
noise @@ lot @@ days
noisy press @@ past @@ dwell @@ choosing
happening right @@ instead
want @@ protect @@ husband
two weeks @@ ballot box @@ time @@ heading
want @@ live @@ kind @@ decide @@ country
profound choice
work together @@ wins @@ need @@ matter @@ going @@ election
watch
yes @@ watch
keep us @@ sound @@ safe
tell us @@ see
claire underwood @@ name @@ message @@ approve
indistinct chatter
one
democrats show @@ frank
almost every member @@ sir @@ doug @@ disappoint
frank almost @@ list
washington herald @@ fellow congressmen @@ need
white house @@ scoundrel lives @@ tell
see @@ democrats
eager @@ debate
side @@ say @@ gentlemen @@ aisle
frank go @@ thank
congressman 1 @@ president @@ investigate
vice president @@ crimes committed
congress murmuring @@ yes @@ say @@ let @@ debate
night @@ miscreant @@ let @@ debate @@ day
indistinct chatter
congressman 2 madam speaker @@ parliamentary inquiry
mccarthy @@ georgia @@ gentleman
parliamentary inquiry @@ may state @@ nature
congressman 2 @@ rules @@ require @@ house
formally invited @@ president @@ order @@ attend
congressman 3 madam speaker @@ may
speaker recognizes @@ south carolina @@ gentleman
congressional pin today @@ wearing @@ president
thereby welcome @@ proceedings
congressman 2 madam speaker @@ madam speaker
gavel banging @@ clamoring
house state @@ rules
former members @@ floor @@ allowed
matter @@ interest @@ debate
madam speaker
debated today @@ president @@ opinion @@ matter @@ interest
gavel banging @@ clamoring
house suspend @@ suspend @@ house @@ mccarthy
madam speaker @@ still @@ hard @@ floor @@ find @@ believe
president @@ opinion @@ matter @@ discussed
florida would yield @@ good gentleman @@ time @@ portion
satisfy @@ query @@ clamoring @@ assure
yield three minutes @@ leader
south carolina @@ former congressman @@ yield @@ time
united states @@ president
gavel banging @@ cheering @@ applauding
parliamentary inquiry @@ point @@ order
parliamentary inquiry
parliamentary inquiry @@ gavel banging
president @@ norm @@ mr @@ beyond
care
investigative committees @@ care @@ also
today @@ clamoring @@ care
gavel banging @@ mccarthy @@ house @@ cease
today @@ care
american patriot @@ way @@ funeral
congressman 4 groaning
good man @@ husband
american soil @@ father @@ beheaded
chamber chooses @@ debate
cheering
suspend @@ speak @@ mccarthy @@ house @@ asked
full session @@ requests @@ denied @@ chamber
must yield @@ madam speaker @@ president @@ mr @@ floor
madam speaker @@ yield @@ cheering
cannot wait @@ applauding
gavel banging
one @@ murderers
killed mr @@ jim miller @@ one @@ murderers
still
large
people need @@ proof @@ much
cheering
house take @@ every member @@ stand @@ demand
like fdr @@ wilson
demand @@ congress
formal declaration @@ war @@ ico @@ declare @@ abroad
congressman 1 motion @@ adjourn
congressman 2 second @@ house @@ adjourn
president @@ frank @@ cease
never cease
congress declare @@ war @@ state @@ demand
united states @@ ico @@ existed @@ exist @@ america
house stay @@ every member @@ demand @@ chamber
vote @@ takes @@ request @@ long @@ bring
history @@ go @@ cowards
cowards
sergeant @@ remove @@ president @@ arms
madam speaker @@ vote @@ repeat @@ demand
yield
gavel bangs @@ yield
theme music playing
alleged terrorist zachary hawthorne @@ killed @@ fbi
joshua masterson @@ still @@ large
missing terrorist continues @@ miller family mourns @@ hunt
running high @@ tensions
president may @@ war @@ asking
seems war @@ declared @@ already
chanting @@ arabic
fans
multiple shooting @@ looking @@ fbi @@ chattanooga
gang related @@ reports
private plane went @@ west virginia @@ mechanical failure
set @@ series @@ homes @@ georgia @@ fire
likely arson
uh convenience store @@ north carolina exploded @@ 4 00 @@ morning
suburb outside @@ uh @@ store @@ raleigh
still @@ investigation @@ cause
yes @@ make @@ appearance
time @@ schedule @@ put @@ mobilize @@ media
yes
joshua masterson @@ declared war @@ take @@ president
never @@ kicked @@ call
politics @@ morning
sighs @@ right
show @@ need @@ living @@ compassion
respect @@ dead @@ conway
moment @@ family @@ doug @@ agreed
pull something @@ speeches @@ press @@ able
president @@ mr @@ governor
realize @@ done @@ already
sir @@ pointed
moment @@ medicated @@ fragile @@ daughter
right
frank mrs @@ miller
thank @@ sorry
promise
terrible tragedy @@ everyone responsible @@ stop
justice @@ brought
witness @@ swear @@ god
family ever @@ ever harm @@ one
nation mourns @@ mrs @@ miller @@ daughter
thank @@ mind @@ course
conway mr @@ president
right along
busy day @@ today @@ sir
sad day @@ sad
shame things @@ turn @@ differently
yes @@ well @@ us @@ two @@ things @@ bigger
want @@ melissa
please @@ melissa @@ calm
fault @@ dead
please @@ killed @@ dead @@ daddy
minute @@ knocking @@ give @@ door
yes @@ take @@ okay @@ medicine
yes
day like today @@ would say @@ think
day like today @@ happen
sniffles @@ pass @@ let
left ahead @@ much @@ know
inhales sharply
together @@ much
think 40 minutes @@ think @@ sniffles
sniffles
late 40 minutes @@ claire crying
two @@ one
went somewhere else @@ eat inhales deeply
exhales deeply
past @@ live @@ ifs @@ dwell
husband
us
please @@ honey
okay @@ come
sniffles
need @@ exhales
wanted @@ say @@ father
sighs
strong @@ brave
taking us @@ father
father
okay @@ father @@ come @@ baby
reason @@ killed @@ father @@ died
gasps melissa
sniffles
shutters click @@ understand @@ right @@ melissa
becomes president @@ whispers @@ hope @@ die
girl say
said @@ president @@ hopes @@ die @@ become
deputy director michaels @@ nsa @@ mr @@ macallan
office @@ meeting @@ literally @@ believe
new york @@ raids @@ panhandle @@ far @@ doug
north carolina @@ virginia @@ green @@ focusing @@ border
statement ready @@ seth @@ afternoon
best statement @@ statement
want claire @@ voice @@ ready @@ besides
yes @@ sir
better bring birch @@ well @@ quite @@ first @@ crowd
door opens @@ congressman birch
bob
little bit @@ well @@ morning @@ history
way @@ see @@ certainly
disagreement
well @@ republicans @@ know
decision @@ anything
mistake complaint @@ leadership
well @@ investigate @@ instead @@ committee
got one @@ discuss @@ declaration
election day @@ way
republicans @@ handful @@ even
spit @@ put @@ grit @@ fight
conversation @@ control
goddamn article @@ talking @@ get @@ anything
side @@ right
womack @@ need @@ massage
declaration caught @@ keep @@ guard
damn thing @@ actually fight @@ constituents
honorable gentleman @@ well @@ missouri @@ let @@ call
doug yes @@ bourbon man @@ oh
claire charlie @@ yes @@ stunt @@ may @@ calling
tom @@ please @@ implying
yet another distraction @@ war @@ request @@ declaration
today @@ prouder @@ president @@ never
tragedy @@ millers @@ happened @@ denying
tragedy @@ denying @@ claire
pattern @@ inhales
underwood @@ mrs @@ husband @@ administration
tom @@ shadows @@ operate @@ continues
understand @@ importance @@ believe @@ article
today @@ talk @@ come @@ agreed
country safe @@ keep @@ fighting
release one piece @@ white house @@ yet @@ underwood @@ mrs @@ information
domestic terrorists @@ attempted capture
ico terrorists @@ yes
saying north carolina @@ hours ago @@ virginia @@ reports
getting closer @@ well @@ circling
tell @@ stutters
real heroes @@ intelligence community
sources confirmed -- @@ could get back @@ point @@ charlie
claire tom
heather dunbar @@ mine @@ husband @@ friend
president @@ looked @@ cleared @@ charges
please @@ cleared
single press briefing @@ white house
herald ran @@ since @@ article
white house @@ keep saying @@ speaking
sitting right @@ talking
remy danton @@ jackie sharp
lucas goodwin @@ either
rose excuse @@ lucas goodwin @@ mouthing @@ meaning
saying
times @@ many @@ know @@ go
tom hammerschmidt article used @@ know
would look @@ washington herald @@ first thing @@ opened
longer campaigning @@ underwoods @@ marshall
want @@ scoffs @@ conway @@ call
well @@ think @@ last @@ days @@ air
one handshake @@ bad idea @@ us @@ time @@ take @@ might
call
abroad ." @@ home
essentially asking @@ president @@ permission
push back @@ war @@ soil @@ hard @@ fight
look soft @@ terror @@ afford
way @@ look @@ either @@ brockhart
talk leads @@ people know @@ kind
united states @@ tv ico @@ frank @@ america
make sure @@ committee dealing @@ war @@ declaration
never gets @@ vote
war
want @@ speaker @@ reach
putting @@ find @@ committee
get back @@ president @@ need @@ crimes
story
anything else
script
yield @@ tv @@ frank
harry
want @@ says @@ know
taking orders @@ used @@ general
thing @@ one
wife
pollyhop @@ opened @@ okay @@ know @@ campaign
time @@ might @@ least @@ close @@ careful
well @@ find
terrorist @@ one @@ mother @@ looking @@ know @@ home
vandalized last night
garage set @@ broken windows @@ fire
uh @@ hannah
well @@ posted
mother online @@ defending
afternoon
timing @@ good
show
scattered applause
brockhart thank
governor conway @@ honored
miller family @@ closest friends
big part @@ vfw @@ life @@ knoxville @@ know @@ jim
hotline @@ homeland @@ help
southwest corner @@ virginia @@ think @@ masterson @@ crossed
washington @@ scott
doug
assistant director green
local law enforcement @@ aerial support @@ sightings @@ relying
fairly confident
next 24 hours @@ pinned
president wants us @@ absolutely sure
getting away @@ stake @@ careers
fully aware @@ everyone around @@ table @@ situation @@ gravity
president @@ hear @@ happy @@ good
hannah softly okay @@ want @@ kiss @@ kind
charlie whispers eskimo
right back
angry
sighs @@ question @@ asked @@ answered
least
well @@ want @@ talk @@ right @@ okay
trying @@ lose @@ election
stop @@ oh
cut someone @@ woman @@ son @@ head @@ defending
still @@ somewhere
looks like @@ understand @@ stop
want @@ son @@ sleep @@ know
eight years old @@ sleep
nightmares
big black dog running around @@ thinks @@ hotel
yes @@ dog
hear @@ growling @@ eyes @@ closes
scared
woman @@ victim @@ said
stop
win @@ want
right back @@ get @@ drink
sighs
response @@ mother @@ leann @@ hannah
son @@ sins @@ punished @@ criminal
rhetoric @@ reject @@ know
troubled young men @@ damaged @@ actions
time @@ reflection @@ mean
aggression
sympathetic @@ condoning
zachary @@ plays @@ joshua @@ idea
troubled kids looking @@ pair @@ cause
school shooter @@ different
000 times @@ shared @@ post @@ 100
want @@ talk
mother @@ hannah
inhales @@ careful @@ appear
excuse us @@ moment @@ leann @@ course
door opens
door closes @@ terror @@ need @@ dial
help us @@ mother
locate masterson @@ also means
soon
waiting @@ tom
well @@ go
francis
funeral @@ cried
played beautifully
come
tell @@ late @@ come
right @@ president @@ officer @@ mr
scope @@ may
scope @@ promise @@ gun @@ give @@ back
thank @@ come
ways @@ scope @@ little @@ hold @@ face
lawn right @@ straight @@ look @@ gate @@ across
see @@ hmm
people want @@ voice @@ frank
looking back across @@ windows @@ toward @@ lawn @@ house
thinking
first lady @@ wonder @@ tonight @@ president
protect us ?" @@ able
got shot @@ wish
maybe @@ could
protected
people want @@ see
someone @@ know @@ keep @@ afraid
first lady @@ tonight @@ president @@ francis
believe thomas @@ well @@ waiting
officer thank @@ sir
see @@ morning @@ frank
whispers @@ smoke
frank thank
thinking tonight @@ singing @@ people @@ know
wander @@ shadows @@ home
secret delight @@ everyone smiling
stare @@ ponder @@ castle
wind blows @@ whenever @@ way
almost hear everyone say
wonder @@ tonight @@ king
looking
got hungry
main kitchen @@ went
lovely group @@ people
need @@ brought @@ anything
needed @@ know @@ eating
president @@ heard @@ declaration
compelling
really think
real thing @@ almost like
good people @@ good @@ sighs @@ nsa
good
good enough @@ find @@ algorithms
using @@ mean @@ knew
one second @@ send @@ next @@ home
come back !" @@ tell
way @@ watching @@ trap
god damn
want
leann
illegal things @@ done
campaigns
possible @@ nsa @@ get
system @@ fix
listening
underwoods @@ know
gonna survive @@ way
win
win @@ sighs @@ help
know
paper right around @@ time @@ left @@ got
tom @@ style @@ start
metro desk
street fashion @@ piece
street thing @@ kids
inhales deeply @@ surprised @@ asked
moved around @@ team @@ people
masterson story @@ war @@ good @@ ?"
chuckles
investigative journalism @@ ever interested
journalism @@ investigating @@ ask
word around @@ get anybody @@ talk
8 00 @@ hands @@ drink
yeah
inhales deeply
say @@ one @@ called
know
little nervous @@ sorry
stutters @@ sort @@ president @@ legend @@ articles
work @@ honor @@ capacity
part
find
another moment
done
told @@ know @@ everything
know
underwood @@ mrs
speak @@ ms @@ masterson @@ hoping @@ claire
us @@ two
whispers inaudibly
problem
bit extreme
fly list @@ extent @@ expanding
visas alone @@ unprecedented @@ restrictions @@ justify
white house counsel
white @@ black
virtually closing @@ borders
hard evidence @@ without @@ coming @@ back
innocent people @@ trying @@ lot @@ get @@ country
hurt @@ could
done right @@ want @@ policy @@ change @@ big
world know @@ want @@ let @@ inhales
continue coming @@ want @@ hospitals @@ country
golf courses @@ god knows @@ else @@ colleges
burning stick @@ head @@ going @@ end @@ deliver
earned relationships @@ well @@ look @@ know @@ cathy
standing @@ long
holding back @@ reached @@ francis
want actionable intelligence @@ reach @@ need
want @@ least @@ know @@ ico
looking @@ everyone
clear
thank @@ let @@ know @@ cathy
dead
still looking @@ --
want @@ touch @@ see @@ dead
trying @@ help
please @@ ms @@ masterson @@ contacted
would @@ wish @@ understand @@ stutters @@ calm
sighs
monster like @@ say
somewhere @@ lost @@ inhales
still @@ monsters @@ exist
want @@ lawyer
sorry @@ said @@ know
say anything anymore @@ chuckles nervously @@ know
simple question @@ wanted @@ see @@ ask
know @@ home @@ going
knew @@ excuse
went @@ pakistan @@ even
raised @@ mean
got lost @@ problems
nothing like @@ saw
would @@ see @@ like
show @@ like
please
inhales deeply
man @@ family
person would @@ thing @@ sort
son @@ crying
sniffling
sobbing oh @@ god
know @@ awful
breathing shakily thank
leave today
reporters @@ cameramen
say @@ need @@ much
ask josh @@ turn @@ need
many hardworking mothers @@ fathers
happened @@ could
son @@ ms @@ masterson @@ close @@ capturing
see @@ best
breathing shakily
want @@ go
one @@ keeping
speaker put @@ put @@ committee
secure seats @@ mostly lifers
two weeks @@ war @@ say @@ hard
breathes deeply
things @@ common
still @@ president @@ dislike @@ democrat
right @@ leans @@ chuckles
actually lean @@ right @@ little @@ alex
look @@ commander @@ chief
needs @@ got @@ fight @@ authority
well @@ speak @@ right @@ one
american law enforcement @@ big fan @@ well
soon enough @@ find
let francis underwood turn us @@ nation
always looking @@ shoulder
onto @@ get @@ committee
time @@ need @@ got @@ give @@ feeling @@ chair
take @@ driver @@ congressman @@ car @@ back
chance
think @@ know
crowd cheering
thank @@ much @@ coming
thanks @@ see @@ great @@ coming @@ cheering
reporters clamoring
go away @@ roseanne
idea @@ homes @@ happening
reporter @@ mrs @@ masterson @@ idea
please @@ josh
please turn @@ please
reporters clamoring @@ stop @@ got
keypad beeps @@ door unlocks
indistinct chatter
keypad beeps
sighs
keypad beeps @@ buzzes
scoffs @@ buzzing
indistinct chatter @@ distance
ten years @@ waiting @@ treasury
man sighs yeah
sighs heavily
mouse clicks
exhales heavily
sighs
reporters clamoring
underwood @@ mrs @@ clamoring
underwood @@ mrs
administration believe @@ explosion @@ connected
joshua masterson somehow @@ sure yet
strong evidence @@ uh @@ suggest
owner @@ foreign @@ establishment @@ born
ico overseas @@ connection
deputy director clark @@ better equipped @@ think @@ answer
set @@ meantime @@ looking @@ hotline
republican candidate @@ community @@ anyone @@ --
party refuse @@ rest @@ acknowledge
threat made @@ seriousness @@ home
know
currently gathering @@ words @@ list @@ images @@ fbi
please -- @@ devices @@ coworkers @@ children @@ appear
man war whore @@ people gasp
officer 2 car @@ officer 1 move
camera shutters clicking @@ agents clamoring
breathing heavily
right @@ paint @@ doug
taste @@ spit @@ else @@ doug @@ bad
sir @@ know @@ disagree
director green @@ team @@ location
takedown @@ ready @@ act
right location @@ positive
adamant
hours
situation room @@ coordinate
gonna meet @@ person @@ oh
strongly advise @@ sir
duly noted @@ site
yes @@ sir
door closes
ready people @@ amazing @@ afraid
history would prove @@ right
sirens blaring @@ distance
water @@ lucky @@ coming
worse @@ could
way behind @@ found @@ ear
smart @@ afraid
stole something
matter
wanted something
well @@ put @@ back
waterfalls
nsa marked @@ day exploits @@ zero @@ waterfalls
get us
popular social media @@ backdoor
insert anything @@ think @@ sites @@ imagination
underwoods @@ otherwise
laptop reports coming @@ variety @@ sources @@ reporter
local police enforcement @@ fbi agents @@ stating
ground @@ currently
receiving reports @@ great deal
virginia border @@ police activity
cannot confirm @@ time
manhunt @@ connected @@ believe
domestic terrorist joshua masterson
joshua masterson may @@ hand @@ close @@ capture
aerial view @@ still @@ look @@ fbi @@ commenting
armed men making @@ wooded area @@ see heavily @@ way
indistinct radio chatter
fbi agent sir
loose domestic connections
perverse idolization @@ ico overseas
ranging homegrown network @@ wide @@ refuses @@ confirm
longer valuable @@ interrogators @@ confident @@ asset
longer tenable @@ risk @@ reward
breaking point @@ sir @@ reached
think @@ already
would @@ somewhere @@ left
thought @@ knew
josh
joshua
want @@ live
tell us @@ want
tell us @@ want @@ hear
martyr
scoffs look
remember @@ one @@ heaven @@ either @@ earth @@ done
sighs
pick @@ millers
see
softly @@ girl
see @@ first
see
yeah @@ saw
looked right @@ breathing heavily
person anymore @@ see @@ need
green sir @@ get rid @@ asset
american citizen @@ still @@ animal
enemy combatant @@ war @@ frank
lost whatever rights @@ might @@ american
poor man @@ head @@ cut
pride @@ position @@ give
would @@ none @@ happened
first place @@ told @@ done
take care
yes @@ willingly
usable footage @@ want @@ good @@ get
killing
destroy everything else
releasing footage @@ joshua masterson @@ killing @@ frank
intelligence community @@ administration
take @@ hoping @@ alive
would like @@ commend
nathan green @@ assistant director @@ counterterrorism
work @@ course
secretary durant @@ done behind @@ scenes
investigation @@ information @@ gathered @@ far
zachary hawthorne @@ joshua masterson @@ points
growing network domestically @@ strong connections @@ ico abroad @@ ico
would like @@ ico directly @@ say
young people @@ one @@ mind @@ infect
stop @@ find
grieving miller family @@ say
sleep tonight @@ hope @@ find
also urge congress
war @@ vote @@ request @@ process @@ declaration @@ accelerate
reporters mr @@ answering questions @@ president
take @@ seth
seth clears throat @@ reporters clamoring
phone ringing
reporter speaking indistinctly @@ tv @@ gunshots
think @@ see @@ reporter @@ killshot @@ hard
please remember @@ unconfirmed @@ reports
white house @@ waiting @@ statement
great deal @@ watching @@ report
wooded area @@ shots @@ fired @@ --
hello
frank hello @@ francis underwood
remy danton @@ jackie sharp @@ looking @@ committee
war @@ ico @@ either
talk @@ invite @@ hill @@ going
testify @@ staff @@ rest
gonna use @@ war @@ investigate @@ declaration
right
committee frank asked @@ gonna use @@ investigate
right @@ fuck @@ doug
fuck ."
underst -- @@ frank @@ difficult
well @@ perhaps @@ moment @@ could @@ calm
caroline please stop
news would bring @@ thought @@ relief @@ frank
president called mrs @@ miller
would -- @@ promised @@ daughter
leave @@ alone
well @@ speak @@ perhaps @@ little @@ feeling
want @@ hear
family
leave us @@ use @@ name @@ husband
mrs .-- @@ dial tone @@ listen
hung
sighs
walk @@ let @@ go
man mr @@ president @@ clamoring
tell @@ need @@ know
clamoring
man mr @@ president
frank hello
man mr @@ thank @@ president
nothing @@ afraid