special ', @@ see @@ actually
really
green peppers @@ uh
uh @@ sage
try @@ think @@ living @@ life @@ go
nice one @@ one @@ see @@ look
anything like @@ something @@ ashamed
something @@ proud @@ either
nothing
get @@ choose @@ born
taking us toward @@ waxing gibbous @@ weekend @@ see
full moon @@ saturday @@ perigee @@ orbit
weekend @@ planning @@ mind @@ keep
family dinners may @@ usual @@ quarrelsome @@ little
menstruating teenagers around @@ table @@ got @@ especially
almost three years @@ working @@ us @@ andrew
really come @@ value
good morning @@ hi @@ heading @@ andrew
simple @@ job @@ good
bedroom needs @@ lamp @@ bulb
yeah @@ replace @@ okay @@ fact
job anymore @@ find men @@ people @@ lot @@ know
hire women @@ obviously @@ lot @@ expensive
good morning
much younger @@ men @@ maybe
working @@ us
worry @@ presence @@ kids @@ impact
really @@ got @@ fever
anything like @@ worried @@ corrupting
man like @@ around
might make @@ yearn @@ something
man like andrew @@ like @@ kids @@ exposed
vital @@ someone @@ prime @@ active
think @@ school @@ late @@ gonna
go get ready
popular thing @@ say @@ mean @@ know
think @@ lives @@ enriching
nine minutes
lives
historical point @@ yeah @@ view @@ suppose
truth
five years @@ seventy
granddaughters @@ give @@ daughters @@ able
really like @@ firsthand account @@ men
yeah @@ think @@ important
way @@ nature
praise nature
andrew myers @@ name
lam 37 years old @@ youngest man @@ world
young priest @@ seminary @@ 1953
good fortune @@ vatican @@ blessed @@ assigned
order known @@ work @@ saints @@ congregation @@ causes
investigate events @@ responsibility
divine miracle @@ extraordinary @@ deemed @@ could
many claims made @@ every year
virgin mary @@ stigmatas @@ apparitions
deadly medical conditions @@ healing
virgin births @@ course
typical year @@ would
virgin births @@ four reports @@ warranted @@ three @@ attention
67 virgin birth claims @@ 1953
fatherless pregnancies @@ remember
first began @@ century ago @@ half
abrahamic religions dominated @@ world @@ back
nearly two billion worshippers @@ time @@ christianity
regarded virgin birth @@ sacred tenets @@ one
virgin named mary @@ christians believe
jesus christ @@ holy prophet @@ gave birth
god @@ fathered
see @@ concerned @@ church
virgin birth claims @@ sudden profusion
vatican could @@ prove otherwise @@ true
considered miracles @@ would
extremely rare events @@ except miracles @@ nature
women @@ virgins @@ course
making @@ claims
coming forward @@ women @@ sorts
scientifically validate @@ way @@ claims
dna testing back
blood testing @@ prove @@ could
particular man @@ father
humans could @@ see @@ procreate @@ mammals @@ like
without intercourse @@ male @@ female
scientifically impossible
women making fatherless pregnancy claims @@ growing number @@ despite
logical conclusion @@ lying
told @@ one @@ doctor
found @@ back
young @@ stupid @@ might @@ 1953
felt awful @@ signs @@ knew
possible way @@ problem @@ pregnant @@ could
richard @@ husband
get retested @@ thing @@ knew @@ insisted
year @@ intimate
doctor walked @@ soon @@ say @@ knew @@ going
test @@ mistake
wife @@ test @@ pregnant @@ mistake
richard demanded @@ know
name
unfaithful @@ swore
anyone
believe
pregnant @@ course
tried @@ impossible @@ explain @@ doctor
looked @@ like @@ child
procreation works @@ understand @@ made @@ babies
sexual relations @@ woman @@ see @@ man
could show @@ truth @@ tests @@ telling @@ 1988
point @@ obvious @@ mattered
back
nobody believed
convince people @@ truth @@ tried @@ telling @@ harder
seemed @@ crazier
pretty soon @@ wonder @@ crazy @@ began
explain something like @@ else could
even worth discussing @@ outlandish
must admit @@ statistics @@ senator @@ compelling
united states @@ 000 claims @@ 10
great britain @@ 000 claims @@ 6
000 claims @@ india @@ 20
even soviet women @@ become pregnant @@ claiming
women @@ nature @@ know
prone @@ impressionable @@ hysterics
known fact
hormonal changes involved @@ pregnancy @@ perhaps
hysteria @@ gullibility @@ amplify
bizarre claim @@ another woman @@ see @@ hear
suddenly @@ pregnancy
cannot help @@ fad @@ becomes
major developed countries @@ time @@ existed
world @@ interesting @@ governments
every different kind @@ political structure
unification @@ remember
fatherless pregnancy claims @@ faced
way @@ reacted @@ exact
preoccupied @@ matters
time @@ little @@ ask
sir @@ opinion @@ able
little later @@ sure
surprising spectacle @@ certainly
pretended like @@ happening
hard @@ fathom @@ consider
every one @@ time @@ run @@ men @@ governments
authorities took @@ understand @@ position @@ personally
would @@ say @@ irresponsible @@ come
procreating without male insemination @@ growing number @@ women
rational beings @@ whole @@ men
egos
nobody likes @@ becoming obsolete @@ told
obviously @@ everyone
work every morning @@ still look forward @@ going
say @@ lot @@ guys
anymore
gonna tell mommy @@ come
come
things @@ lots @@ like
talk @@ fun @@ easy @@ caring @@ around
take @@ see @@ okay @@ let @@ break @@ andrew
want @@ violet @@ still @@ kind @@ fathers @@ definitely
looked appealing @@ word @@ used @@ say @@ man
handser @@ hands
yeah @@ handsome
would @@ well @@ said @@ andrew
handsome
parasitism @@ competition
right @@ mutualism
third household @@ worked @@ actually
different
describe species
got @@ bread
anyone want @@ thank
one definitely keeps @@ toes
six months @@ six kids @@ 17
okay
stay busy @@ way @@ prefer @@ better
everyone say good night @@ think someone @@ gonna go @@ bed
good night @@ sweetheart
jot easier @@ though @@ makes @@ job
hey @@ gather @@ everybody
genuinely like @@ work @@ women
okay @@ luna @@ hey @@ going @@ everybody
violet @@ hi @@ hey
look like @@ cold today @@ gonna
really easygoing @@ kind @@ iris
way
need balls @@ balls
hard @@ describe
sister @@ see @@ hi
know @@ feel @@ around
ease
saffron @@ move
tends @@ conservative
things @@ likes @@ book
remember @@ practice @@ play @@ like @@ girls
low profile @@ tend @@ keep @@ around
way @@ stay @@ job
end @@ day
might get @@ emotionally involved @@ matter
employee
reminded @@ good @@ every
whippersnapper
jim @@ hey @@ good
know reggie
ivy chan @@ holly dawson @@ works @@ verona
yeah @@ sure
magic show @@ bosses want @@ put @@ boot
believe
balloon animals @@ summon
every single day @@ magic show @@ want @@ say @@ put @@ ladies
toilet trained @@ sake ." @@ god @@ daughters
excuse
voices @@ keep
nobody wants @@ manosaurs @@ listen @@ bunch
annoying
talking @@ sorry
yeah @@ tell @@ relax
even allowed
actually working @@ okay @@ matter
two @@ groups @@ congregate
seriously @@ oh @@ forgotten @@ come
rules
going @@ follow
get back @@ work @@ okay @@ got
stick around @@ go
good seeing @@ worth @@ soon @@ see @@ okay
see @@ later
turned @@ things @@ maybe @@ differently
architect like @@ pilot @@ mom
point @@ dwelling
gonna make @@ opportunities @@ best
things @@ going @@ change
way @@ back
nature @@ fact
even though @@ coming forward @@ women
fatherless pregnancy claims
taken seriously
things seemed @@ carry @@ always
think @@ sense @@ pointless
want @@ tried @@ tell @@ listen @@ going
never listened
little closer @@ would @@ seen @@ looked
proper exteriors @@ woman @@ prim @@ dutiful @@ beneath
simmering anger getting ready @@ boil
sister isabella came along
small town @@ northern spain @@ hills outside @@ living @@ convent
strictly forbidden @@ men @@ entering @@ convent
wanted @@ vows @@ even @@ break
remote location @@ watchfulness @@ nuns @@ given
sneak away @@ would @@ impossible
sister isabella discovered @@ utter dismay @@ yet
pregnant
one could argue @@ different time @@ happened
well embraced sister isabella @@ church may
living saint @@ canonized
perhaps even looked upon @@ return @@ messiah @@ baby
daughter
biblical narrative @@ wrench @@ would @@ thrown
church wanted nothing @@ sister isabella @@ know
saints @@ ordered @@ destroy @@ congregation @@ causes
written @@ report
ever heard @@ deny @@ claim
told us @@ best
tiny village @@ spain @@ burgos
whale @@ telling @@ story @@ nuns @@ group
meet sister isabella
though @@ tell @@ pregnant @@ hard @@ habit
saying @@ guess @@ father
one
called fatherless pregnancy @@ right @@ another
catholic church expected @@ last thing
spanish nuns would @@ devout order @@ vow @@ silence @@ break
would listen @@ start talking @@ anyone
people think @@ joke
government needs @@ happening @@ acknowledge
claims seriously @@ wake @@ take @@ need
sorry @@ going
would like women everywhere @@ scientific community @@ world @@ know @@ despite
fatherless pregnancies @@ unanimous @@ impossible @@ belief
matter vigorously @@ study @@ intend
one way @@ doubt @@ another
whole matter @@ rest @@ put @@ able
seen @@ recorded @@ long @@ history
civilization
group attains power @@ reluctant @@ give
history also shows us @@ always forced @@ eventually
tell us @@ saw earlier
well @@ see @@ really
work @@ secretaries @@ morning @@ came
unusual @@ many @@ given
since @@ one @@ make @@ coffee
way @@ lobby @@ go
get service @@ 20 minutes @@ took
work @@ waitresses @@ shown @@ either
strike @@ referred @@ afterwards
organized event
even aware @@ women @@ thing @@ mother
one night @@ enough @@ decided
dining room @@ father @@ brother
waiting @@ served @@ dinner
noticed @@ kitchen
seem like @@ prepared @@ food
said @@ purse @@ hand @@ coat @@ appeared
going
know @@ back
want dinner @@ make
ground beef @@ think @@ freezer
really @@ character
something like
turned @@ saw @@ look @@ father @@ face
something significant @@ realized @@ happening
swallow @@ pride @@ impressed @@ admit @@ able
take @@ back @@ ask
suddenly @@ realization
use @@ life @@ absolutely
love everything iris paints
always
close @@ biased
really like someone @@ like everything @@ tend
uh
man phase @@ crazy
maybe
still beautiful paintings
think people acknowledge @@ issue enough
mean @@ acknowledge
really concerns @@ something @@ painlessness
work lately @@ part @@ making @@ guess
issue alive @@ want @@ keep
making people confront @@ way @@ guess @@ going
sell nearly @@ well @@ pieces @@ paintings
sell @@ actually
nobody wants @@ man hanging @@ picture @@ fireplace
represents @@ andrew @@ age
way @@ like
makes sense @@ staring @@ notice @@ lot @@ kind
time painting someone @@ gonna spend
probably really like looking
think @@ obsessed
process @@ part
subject @@ matter
mmm @@ good
yeah @@ serious @@ good
men around @@ paint @@ lot @@ like
us @@ live
art class @@ um
perfect @@ anything
much @@ likeness @@ concerned
interested @@ body
muscles @@ especially @@ arms
really like @@ arms
grandma used @@ say @@ grandfather
looks
personality @@ first @@ even @@ caught @@ attention
spirit
trying @@ paintings @@ capture
spirit @@ andrew
spirit @@ men @@ maybe @@ extension @@ exists
fatherless pregnancy claims continued @@ rise @@ number
normal pregnancies @@ number @@ discovered
man impregnated @@ woman @@ plummeting
four babies born @@ three @@ fact @@ end @@ 1957
mothers claiming @@ fatherless impregnation @@ coming
though @@ even @@ alarming
mothers gave birth @@ every one @@ girl @@ fact
parthenogenesis
get called @@ used @@ reason @@ know @@ instead
get pregnant @@ needed @@ man
true
disgusting
asexual reproduction @@ parthenogenesis @@ form
sole source @@ genetic material @@ egg
embryo @@ creation
reproduction @@ occur @@ mode @@ known
certain types @@ reptiles @@ insects
mammals @@ however
embryo could @@ male @@ fertilized @@ egg @@ develop
make life possible @@ genetic components @@ bringing together
necessary components @@ since @@ parthenogenesis
reproduction @@ produced @@ needed @@ egg
rendered obsolete @@ sperm
discovered
sperm could @@ longer penetrate @@ wall @@ egg
new protein @@ producing @@ membrane @@ hardened
sperm @@ shutout @@ literally
egg artificially @@ sperm @@ injected @@ even
almost immediately rendered inert
take sperm @@ biological equation
longer @@ chromosomes
embryonic process @@ introduced
two x chromosomes @@ every embryo @@ every child @@ female
thus
males
last one @@ hard @@ figure
entire world @@ boy born @@ year @@ actually
years later @@ official @@ make
us coming @@ sure
started school @@ lot @@ got @@ attention
class pet @@ like @@ kind
bad way
cage like mr @@ like @@ kept @@ chips
actual class pet
high school @@ challenge
boys around @@ used @@ point @@ girls
completely alien @@ one @@ idea @@ attracted
crooked girls @@ wrong @@ get
um @@ sure
girls @@ accepted
got along @@ neither @@ fine
finished high school @@ really
different things @@ realized @@ going
graduated @@ girls @@ compared
finally dawned
opportunities @@ gonna @@ going
one road @@ going
going @@ another
eleanor marie hamilton @@ solemnly swear
faithfully execute
united states @@ president @@ office
best @@ ability
told someone @@ early 1960s
woman would @@ united states @@ next president
believed
may seem ridiculous @@ time
possibly even 15 years @@ wait 10 @@ people thought
would happen
least @@ first @@ drastic @@ changes
declared war @@ men @@ like @@ came
anything like
would @@ think @@ stretch @@ say @@ payback @@ element
governing agenda
much appreciate @@ historical contribution
men @@ made @@ civilization
facts
women make @@ population @@ 62
senator @@ actually @@ 64
right
ratio needs @@ society @@ represented @@ levels
worker replacement program
worker assessment program @@ little harsh @@ statistics
allow male employees @@ replaced
thorough assessment
equally qualified female @@ less capable @@ deemed
weeding @@ simply @@ process
weeds @@ lot @@ happens
would happen @@ warned @@ grandfather
given women @@ vote @@ said @@ never
soul ." @@ uh @@ take @@ said @@ inch @@ give
right @@ know
react well @@ led governments @@ generally speaking @@ men @@ female
opt @@ began
rural encampments @@ exodus ." @@ refer @@ move
welcome @@ stay
know
get along without us @@ see
think @@ long @@ going
come back @@ beg us @@ realize @@ mistake @@ made
jackass @@ hey
forgot @@ coat
leave behind @@ important item @@ gonna live @@ woods @@ kind
three women @@ free loving @@ living @@ beautiful
started treating @@ sex object @@ like
errand boy
mid @@ clear @@ 1970s
fine without men @@ women @@ charge
rethink @@ positions @@ men @@ lot @@ left @@ caused
subservient roles @@ took @@ returned
new world order @@ core group dug @@ refused @@ heels @@ accept
simple @@ respect @@ power @@ okay
taken away @@ get back @@ us @@ intend
womankind ." @@ mankind ." @@ called
reason
last 200 @@ 000 years
keeping civilization afloat @@ men
steering @@ ship @@ built
chuck us overboard @@ gone haywire @@ want @@ eggs
bloody likely
want @@ respect
want
traffic throughout @@ protests tied @@ city
ultimately sparked @@ violence @@ believed
started getting @@ women @@ cars
us @@ look @@ eyes @@ coming
street @@ get
stopped dead @@ work @@ trying @@ traffic @@ get
men blocking @@ saw @@ road @@ chanting
snapped
protest marches took place @@ world @@ day
violence @@ thought @@ parthenogenesis @@ first @@ connected
nature @@ men @@ loss @@ compensating
making women @@ aggressive
pms @@ fact
women represented @@ 1975
world @@ three @@ quarters @@ population
menstrual ovulatory synchrony ," @@ triggered @@ known
phenomenon
women become synchronized @@ menstrual cycles
world became like one big sorority house @@ essentially
tip @@ iceberg
pretty soon @@ bodies get @@ sync @@ minds @@ first
telepathic communication
contend
hive mind @@ compete
ensuing violence turned @@ watershed event @@ protest marches
monthly @@ creating @@ catalyst
day statutory holiday @@ menses ." @@ three @@ know
protests happened right @@ unification @@ importantly
first test
newly formed world governing council
would respond @@ watching @@ see @@ everyone @@ closely
want @@ make @@ first @@ clear
world governing council @@ listens
want men @@ groups everywhere @@ know @@ heard
plight @@ help @@ going @@ acknowledge
part @@ commitment
men everywhere @@ safety @@ ensuring @@ comfort
set aside vast areas @@ world governing council @@ land
male sanctuaries @@ creation
exclusive communities @@ world @@ located
entire continent @@ including @@ australia
sanctuaries @@ provided @@ men @@ live
including medical attention @@ services @@ require
nutritious meals @@ clean clothes
entertainment @@ course
remaining men @@ possible @@ kept @@ comfortable @@ believe
lives @@ live
humanity must @@ respected @@ honored @@ contribution
must respect @@ honor nature @@ time @@ actions
praise nature
think @@ children
offering us food @@ silly conveniences @@ bunch
pacify us @@ female regime @@ blatant attempt
stupid
ply us @@ world @@ comforts
resolve @@ change
taken away @@ rightful place @@ society @@ may
take away @@ dignity
defiant spirit @@ question @@ mlo
vocal @@ intentions
governing council @@ much @@ actually
began providing services @@ sanctuaries @@ established
rubbish
made us weak @@ sanctuaries @@ living
given us @@ resurgence @@ plan @@ done @@ ability
superior sex @@ dominant
take care @@ prepare meals @@ without @@ hassle
see @@ joke
weakening @@ time @@ resolve @@ regime @@ believed
allowing us @@ actually
plan @@ focus @@ attack
strike @@ ready @@ long
effective organization @@ whether @@ think @@ mlo @@ issue
central goal @@ fact @@ achieved
government firmly believes @@ solution @@ problem
even see manlessness @@ problem
evolutionary event @@ simply
questioned @@ never @@ nature @@ control @@ beyond @@ act
sacred @@ nature
energy rising @@ notice @@ body
higher
power flowing @@ fingertips @@ feel
breathe
took away @@ jobs @@ enough
fired god @@ went
sacred cycles @@ worshipping @@ forces
sheila @@ replaced
nature flowing
praise nature
question @@ actions
blessed gift @@ everything
nature @@ influenza @@ act
malaria @@ cancer
nature eradicated @@ around anymore
government spent trillions @@ dollars developing vaccines
governing council @@ suggesting
painlessness issue @@ avoiding dealing @@ purpose
maintain power @@ way
would certainly achieve @@ men die @@ even though @@ goal
worth asking @@ think @@ question
put towards @@ resources
mind @@ government @@ doubt
deliberately ignoring @@ problem
number one agenda @@ using nature @@ push @@ excuse
men @@ away
need us @@ go @@ believing
term way @@ another example @@ thinking @@ short @@ reckless
think strategically @@ big picture @@ women @@ seeing @@ incapable
give @@ example
defense department @@ u @@ set @@ program @@ fund @@ 1960
would allow @@ world @@ computers @@ around
connect
massive communication web @@ linked together
word processing units @@ imagine @@ could
could talk
bloody amazing @@ right
women take @@ well @@ guess
defense budget gets stuffed @@ u
space exploration @@ even getting @@ started
gutted nasa @@ early 1960s
russian program @@ stand @@ either @@ chance
understand @@ really @@ obsession
putting @@ moon @@ man
important role @@ plays @@ lives @@ appreciate
sending someone @@ really need @@ trouble @@ stand @@ go
think
way @@ put @@ moon @@ men
show
massive spending cuts @@ program cancellations
big bloody deal @@ world peace @@ electric cars
true progress @@ conflict @@ comes
one country fancied another @@ used @@ time
invade
war @@ one @@ defeated @@ declared @@ battled
stronger nation @@ born @@ bigger
dale
hair @@ fixing
man fancied @@ woman @@ used @@ time
tum @@ court @@ charm
rather look
connie @@ beautiful
fall @@ choice
get together @@ sex
intercourse
form @@ conflict
true progress @@ came children
world @@ wars @@ live
parents told @@ last boy @@ remember
started wondering @@ problem @@ maybe @@ cause
us @@ stopped @@ somehow @@ coming
like maybe @@ something @@ machinery @@ broken
taken one look @@ males ." @@ uh @@ said @@ god @@ done
even though @@ still @@ know @@ certain
extinction @@ emerged @@ dinosaurs @@ consensus @@ caused
true @@ men
discovered @@ cause
become conventional wisdom @@ dominant theory @@ emerge
personal feeling @@ evolution
humans evolved @@ apes
single sex @@ evolving
would nature
need @@ anymore
gatherer society @@ hunter
protect us @@ need men @@ build shelters @@ hunt @@ food
stopped producing @@ needed anymore @@ since @@ nature
nothing personal
penis
oil drills @@ skyscrapers @@ responsible @@ missiles
phallic energy @@ eventually @@ aggressive
corroding effect @@ planet
nature @@ extinguish @@ choice
neo @@ know
near earth object
normally @@ comets @@ asteroids
astronomers recorded one @@ well @@ thought @@ asteroid @@ 1952
unusually large cloud @@ solar debris @@ due
way @@ surrounding @@ sure
nine months later @@ called fatherless baby @@ first @@ born
two x chromosomes @@ women @@ one @@ men
would @@ something @@ okay @@ offer @@ chromosome
pales @@ fact @@ comparison
tiny complement @@ genes @@ carries
genetic mutations @@ protection @@ offers
runty little thing @@ kind
us @@ ultimately @@ suspect
female aliens
female aliens @@ race @@ asexual
reproductive system @@ hijack @@ earth @@ come
want @@ know @@ government
explanation
knew @@ cause @@ admitted
much closer @@ fix @@ able
heads stuck @@ want @@ sand @@ know @@ got @@ either
us @@ truth @@ know @@ hiding
either way @@ avoiding dealing @@ situation
men @@ like
see @@ problem @@ attack
know everything @@ know @@ tear @@ apart
fix
talking circles @@ listening tours @@ form committees @@ go
men ". @@ fix
gonna @@ exactly
gonna get back @@ put @@ power @@ painlessness @@ end
fix
-- fix @@ fix
important information @@ received
mess hall tonight @@ sewing tenderloin
sewing @@ right
let @@ go @@ come
survivor @@ realize @@ kind @@ guilt @@ feeling
still feel twinges @@ totally crazy @@ even though
men looking @@ usually @@ see
last one @@ think @@ door @@ blame
?"
feel good
feel bad @@ either
massacred @@ like
getting old @@ dying
remember reading @@ paper @@ like @@ ago
last surviving member @@ rock band @@ died
think @@ raymonds @@ called
ramones
remember feeling sad @@ right @@ anyway
members @@ band
new songs @@ producing
someone @@ died
always sad
part @@ life @@ also
nothing @@ forever
punk band @@ men @@ extinction @@ comparing @@ 70s
actually kind @@ thing
one day @@ last man @@ paper @@ open @@ going @@ find @@ died
way @@ think @@ raymonds @@ going @@ feel
meet @@ hi @@ excited
nice @@ meet @@ loved @@ book
nice @@ name @@ meet
sunlight 24 hours @@ entire planet @@ imagine @@ exposed @@ day
would never get dark @@ night ." @@ word @@ use
gender ." @@ word @@ true
men @@ meaning @@ gone @@ cease
human history @@ good riddance @@ divisive word
sex @@ mean @@ gender @@ away
us believe @@ government would @@ despite
women still crave sexual intimacy
still instinctively pairing @@ raise @@ order @@ children
without intimacy
eventually start @@ couple together @@ holds @@ disintegrate @@ bond
families @@ disintegrate
whole @@ society @@ leave
rationale @@ government @@ embraced
governing council @@ members @@ fact
touch conservatives
male resurgence @@ irrational fear @@ harbor
trickled @@ paranoia
social policy @@ government @@ bedrock
extreme @@ explains
turned @@ sex @@ kind @@ heterosexuality @@ fear
something @@ mom @@ ask
dear @@ course
touch @@ strange @@ know
feels really good
situation @@ found
perhaps @@ dreading @@ conversation
worry @@ well @@ alone
girls reach puberty @@ impending fertility @@ joy @@ fact @@ excitement
sexual arousal @@ perils @@ often @@ confusion @@ accompanied
video @@ produced @@ health @@ department
confusing times @@ understand @@ think
evolutionary transition @@ still @@ period
yet sex @@ still present @@ sexual urges @@ longer necessary
eventually eradicate @@ nature @@ impulses
become fully evolved
governing council needs @@ young women @@ ensure
get caught @@ erotic pleasure @@ futility
talk @@ supposed
even know @@ supposed @@ actually
old kind @@ sex @@ especially
know @@ intercourse
worry @@ urges
urges ." @@ urges @@ give
telling us @@ next @@ itch @@ get
scratch
psychological @@ physical
think @@ need
feelings thoughts @@ mean
thoughts @@ feelings
never
discourage intimacy @@ trying
emotional intimacy @@ least
young people @@ taught @@ critical
deeply fulfilling non @@ sexual bonds @@ nurture meaningful
need @@ love @@ grow @@ believing
need @@ believe
funny little thing @@ laughs
another story @@ would @@ tell @@ like
right
fair maiden @@ well @@ upon @@ time
hello
oh @@ highness
sorry @@ right @@ oh
startle @@ mean @@ expecting @@ certainly
best friend @@ talked @@ jasmine
get along really well @@ music @@ lot @@ like
want @@ sure @@ spend @@ rest @@ life
known @@ forever
since high school @@ well @@ quite
grade 11
terra ". @@ dahlia @@ ah
work @@ partnered @@ mine @@ friend
iris got called @@ pair @@ looking
great timing
together ever since
think @@ someone @@ proof @@ partner
without @@ intimacy
force someone @@ way @@ feel
good friends @@ terra @@ partners
kids together @@ raising @@ anything
really well @@ worked @@ us @@ think
right
yes @@ yeah @@ great @@ course
also think @@ understand @@ know @@ easy
someone else might want @@ given @@ circumstances
deeper bond @@ partner @@ know
anything like @@ sexual @@ saying
course
something @@ meaningful @@ mean @@ intense
men still
much older
completely hopeless
people talk @@ way @@ men @@ bothers
already gone @@ like
still
one @@ anyway
talking @@ andrew
yeah @@ okay
good example @@ andrew
fond @@ admit
uh could @@ small break @@ take
need @@ excuse
something going @@ like @@ know
way @@ paintings @@ look @@ iris
hoped @@ assumed
harmless flirtation
see @@ obvious @@ intimate
planning @@ like @@ happen
spent together @@ time
happened
gonna change @@ terra @@ everything
andrew
mystery @@ likes @@ aura
right @@ provocative @@ part @@ artist
never believed @@ actually crooked
thought @@ act
surprise @@ right
want @@ see
idea @@ going @@ fine
think
yes @@ sure
going
okay @@ house @@ go @@ everyone @@ come @@ back
turn @@ please
excuse
please
still women @@ men @@ course @@ attracted
want @@ perish
understand
small segment @@ population
maybe 10
dying breed @@ pining @@ men @@ like
whole @@ think @@ population @@ best
prohibit opposite sex unions @@ young people especially
remaining men @@ sanctuaries @@ go @@ encourage
next stage @@ focus @@ evolution
unnecessary distractions @@ without @@ confusion
right
big electrified fence @@ always expecting @@ something @@ people
particular sanctuary @@ mind @@ keep
300 square kilometers @@ smaller ones @@ one
option @@ fence
service roads @@ gated @@ course
entire perimeter @@ patrol
honest
really get many men trying @@ escape anymore
20 years ago @@ issue 10
hurry
wandering @@ time @@ back
yeah @@ getting
sanctuary guard ". @@ mostly looking @@ female contact
man outside @@ mom
get
shoo @@ okay @@ hey
okay
house right @@ get inside @@ okay
come @@ closer
want @@ talk @@ okay
name @@ kirk
already called @@ police
pretty
get inside
help @@ course
part @@ nature
border patrol agents quickly arrived @@ scene
tree @@ surrounded @@ man @@ climbed
leave @@ anything @@ alone
cute
lengthy standoff
tranquilizer gun @@ use @@ forced @@ agents
unruly man @@ sedate
nearby northbrook sanctuary @@ returned
future plans @@ doubt rethinking
venture outside @@ perimeter
like animals
characterize
except @@ everybody @@ endangered @@ arms @@ animals
raised @@ monies @@ formed @@ committees
tasmanian fruit bats @@ without
men @@ comes
take away @@ shove us @@ wilderness @@ livelihoods
erase us @@ movies @@ books
good measure @@ castrate us @@ basically go
joking
evidence
undeniable proof @@ years @@ suspecting
actually going
report clearly states @@ lacing @@ food @@ estrogen
girly hormone
smith claimed @@ document
internal government memo @@ says
governing council @@ clearly shows @@ carrying
program intended @@ boners ." @@ quote @@ kill
sex drive @@ life blood @@ man
well kill @@ take @@ might @@ away
longer eat @@ hereto tell @@ food
hunger strike @@ officially
strip us @@ might @@ dignity @@ able
never take away @@ manhood
problem @@ memo
government claimed @@ discussion paper
proof
synthetic hormone @@ way @@ put @@ found @@ food
without @@ way @@ detect
shows
something @@ scientists @@ put @@ minds @@ capable
thanks @@ dawn
things @@ speaking @@ short @@ lived
male liberation organization announced today
hunger strike @@ half @@ ending @@ day
darius smith @@ would @@ say @@ leader @@ group
control ." @@ circumstances beyond @@ due
supposed
man gets hungry @@ eat
way
mean @@ failed
least
world @@ lengths @@ aware
denigrate men @@ authoritarian regime @@ go
still eating @@ food
prepared @@ grown @@ food
yes @@ prepared @@ grown @@ food @@ course @@ could
deliberately chosen @@ protest
tainted food @@ story would @@ gone away @@ refused
us @@ people @@ government @@ forget
every day @@ eat @@ continuing
constantly reminded @@ world
live @@ like
many details @@ liberty @@ go
sanctuary food @@ add estrogen @@ say
time @@ realized @@ initiative
longer necessary due @@ increasing age @@ men
sex drives naturally @@ losing
load @@ crap
still lacing @@ food @@ course
bloody propaganda
old either @@ know
showing @@ harm @@ guess
last one born @@ people assume
involved @@ cause
male organizations @@ get approached @@ time @@ pro
penis @@ mlo @@ man
want @@ use @@ notoriety
help raise awareness @@ lobby @@ government
activist type
way @@ others @@ effective @@ believe
leaders @@ know
guy
know
together @@ see @@ hard
government would never sanction
look good @@ record @@ intimate @@ employer
stay positive @@ guess @@ got
terrible place @@ gonna say
quinoa salad @@ lima beans @@ excuse
split peas @@ yeah @@ oh
treat us well
place @@ matter @@ comfortable
still feel like @@ prison
trick @@ say @@ much @@ fill @@ days
try @@ enjoy
seem
always somewhere else @@ mind
iris @@ house @@ back
like @@ guys
gotten used
like
go back @@ want @@ reason
oh @@ gorgeous
look wonderful @@ hold
lovely olive @@ oh @@ honor @@ guest
first moon @@ see @@ celebrating
l ay
things went back @@ surface @@ normal @@ guess
woman @@ feel
uh @@ tingly
andrew left
proud mother
terra @@ recover @@ happened
felt betrayed
two moms @@ picture @@ let @@ get
see things differently @@ gonna make @@ could say @@ nothing
um @@ move @@ harold
harold
please @@ move
kids really missed andrew
especially dahlia
tried @@ part @@ move @@ life
stop thinking
talk @@ oh @@ baby
yeah @@ talk @@ please @@ oh
really got @@ stopped
thought @@ rest @@ life @@ going
sinking really slowly @@ ship @@ like @@ deck
women @@ sitting @@ men @@ lifeboats @@ left
waiting @@ meet @@ fate
want @@ read @@ oh
hit home @@ kind
gonna @@ gone
waiting @@ sit @@ knew
something
leave
though @@ make @@ easy
ran @@ night @@ middle @@ left @@ fast @@ could
take long @@ found
think @@ gonna
praying @@ message @@ idea @@ got @@ going
stunned look @@ staring @@ face
said
gonna stand @@ gonna get
together @@ think @@ determined
never really stopped @@ thought @@ implications
looking @@ gonna @@ andrew
hiding @@ go
life @@ kind
pretending like @@ mean @@ involved @@ hiding @@ already
lot harder @@ gonna
wanted @@ unfair @@ seemed
natural @@ felt
together @@ marry @@ kids
possible @@ none
wanted things @@ change
something @@ ones @@ gonna
sanctuary escape story @@ surprising development
last week @@ told
old myers surprised everyone today @@ year @@ reporter @@ l @@ arrived @@ 37
jefferson street community hall @@ press conference @@ give
youngest man @@ andrew myers @@ world
alice lake sanctuary @@ resurfaced today @@ escaping
impromptu press conference @@ iris balishev @@ former employer
startling announcement @@ made
children together @@ want @@ right @@ marry
even though heterosexual reproduction @@ impossible @@ considered
hope @@ belief
governing council @@ resources
scientific community @@ support @@ reality @@ become
reality @@ become
realize @@ man @@ love @@ biased
one @@ know
please speak @@ time @@ running
together like @@ two @@ seeing
recognition @@ pleading @@ obviously @@ love
awoke something @@ people
go ahead @@ air
like men @@ knows anymore @@ care
totally agree @@ saying
cute couple @@ make @@ admit
tell @@ answer
let @@ die
think @@ really @@ come @@ bad
question @@ morality
vanish @@ stand @@ let @@ face @@ earth
women
governing council @@ calls today
take action @@ painlessness
governing council @@ reaction @@ public @@ course @@ aware
taking @@ seriously
emergency meetings @@ convened
possible solutions @@ situation @@ consider @@ assess
keep men around @@ matter @@ figure
place @@ nature @@ intervene @@ act
praise nature
female caller b ". @@ start producing men @@ way @@ think @@ find
maybe 100 @@ many @@ 150
see @@ goes
much attention focused @@ us @@ press
really small @@ private ceremony @@ make @@ decided
beautiful
legal
prove @@ license @@ even
real thing @@ right
married
getting even @@ attention
little development
little anymore
tell us @@ know @@ boy @@ asked
really want @@ surprise
procedure worked @@ present @@ dna @@ andrew
wanted
baby
good
boy like everyone seems @@ think
world @@ suppose @@ great
something like @@ personally @@ imagine
growing inside
male baby
turns @@ culprit @@ chromosome
government scientists disguised @@ chromosome
x chromosome @@ look like
thereby tricking @@ egg @@ accepting
wish people @@ got pregnant @@ excited
course
good thing @@ happened
never really liked @@ men going extinct @@ idea
feel right
hand @@ going @@ deny
happy @@ close @@ came
one hell @@ scare @@ gave
needed @@ exactly
patience
saying @@ along
stay vigilant @@ wits @@ us @@ keep
sooner @@ later @@ get @@ chance
feel different
first time @@ feel like @@ pregnant @@ know @@ head
guess @@ away
really excited @@ know
praying @@ girl
l
talk
well @@ see @@ know
want @@ read
talk
talk @@ oh @@ baby
see @@ know
want @@ talk @@ read
talk
see @@ know
want @@ read
talk