music playing
panting
beeping
mama @@ lyra @@ know
time @@ things @@ jyn @@ gather
saw hello @@ saw @@ lyra
us @@ happened @@ come
know
loud humming
galen jyn @@ come
whatever @@ remember
protect
understand @@ say
understand
stardust @@ love
papa @@ love
galen
go
jyn
know @@ go
trust @@ force
sighs
panting
hard man @@ galen @@ find
farming
talents @@ really @@ man
peaceful life
lonely @@ imagine
since lyra died @@ yes
oh
exhales
condolences
search @@ house
mechanical voices speaking indistinctly
want @@ galen
come back @@ work @@ stalled @@ need
krennic
verge @@ greatness
close
providing peace @@ security @@ galaxy
confusing peace @@ terror
well
start somewhere
indistinct chatter
krennic @@ help
mind
trouble remembering
even simple things
galen
terrible liar @@ inspired scientist
effort @@ admire
really
oh @@ lyra @@ look @@ dead @@ back
miracle
speaks indistinctly
stop
weapon whines
oh @@ lyra
troublesome @@ ever
taking
taking @@ course
live @@ comfort @@ come @@ child
hostages
heroes @@ empire
put @@ lyra
think @@ carefully
breath trembling
never win
weapons firing @@ groaning
lyra @@ gasps
lyra
child
find
jyn panting
door opens
mechanical voices speaking
jyn breathing heavily
thunder rumbling
jyn continues panting
footsteps approaching
child
come
long ride ahead @@ us
theme music playing
water dripping
door opens
cell mate snoring
pa check @@ security @@ announcer
cell block 4227
man screaming @@ pain
indistinct chatter
speaking alien language
stormtrooper 1 tk @@ 62 @@ 25900
indistinct chatter continues
tmk panting
leave
fast @@ could @@ came
get back @@ walk @@ board
jed ha @@ back
leave without
news @@ jedha @@ easy
come
imperial pilot @@ cargo drivers @@ one
defected yesterday
telling people @@ weapon @@ making
kyber crystals
weapon @@ kind
weapon @@ look @@ kind @@ go
planet killer @@ called
planet killer
someone named erso sent @@ old friend @@ saw
galen erso
saw @@ looking @@ left @@ know
else knows @@ idea
falling apart
saw @@ right
indistinct radio chatter @@ spies everywhere
stormtrooper 1
see @@ scandocs @@ let @@ come
yeah @@ gloves @@ course
groans
indistinct yelling
done
section 9 @@ troopers
tmk @@ crazy
never climb @@ arm
st ormtrooper 2 get @@ way
move
hey @@ calm
breathing heavily @@ right @@ l
fires weapon
alarm blaring @@ distance
grunting
speaking alien language
looks kind @@ imagined @@ different
saw gerrera @@ gasps okay
saw genera '?
wasting time @@ okay
saw gerrera @@ keep telling @@ speak @@ need
late
speaking alien language
nowhere @@ middle
jedha city @@ need @@ get
urgent message @@ understand @@ part @@ guys
grunting
side
see past @@ uniform @@ minute
continues speaking indistinctly
vehicle stops
another pickup @@ must @@ know
thought @@ everybody
door latch clicks
stormtroopers groaning
sir @@ clear
liana hallik @@ hallik
wanna get
hey
grunting
keys @@ give
continues grunting
groans
rescued @@ congratulations
resist @@ please
rebel soldiers speaking indistinctly
rebel announcer lu @@ maintenance level 4 @@ report @@ 28
indistinct mechanical chatter
liana hallik @@ currently calling
correct
unsanctioned weapons @@ possession
imperial documents @@ forgery
aggravated assault @@ escape @@ custody
resisting arrest
imperial authorities @@ imagine @@ found
jyn erso @@ really
given name
jyn erso @@ galen erso @@ daughter
known imperial collaborator @@ weapons development
mon mothma @@ fresh start @@ make @@ chance
help us @@ think @@ might @@ able
captain cassian andor @@ rebel intelligence
last time @@ father @@ contact
15 years ago
time @@ idea
think @@ like @@ dead
makes things easier
imperial war machine @@ tool @@ easier
political opinions @@ never @@ luxury
really
saw gerrera @@ last contact
long time
though @@ remember
might agree @@ meet @@ friend @@ came
talk @@ nothing @@ girl @@ clock
put @@ found @@ back
saw gerrera saved @@ raised @@ life @@ child
idea
years @@ seen
know @@ find @@ cassian
problem
someone @@ need
gets us @@ door without @@ killed
rebels
mon mothma yes @@ saw gerrera @@ extremist
since @@ rebellion @@ fighting @@ broke
militancy @@ caused @@ alliance
great many problems
try @@ choice
broken trust @@ mend
father
imperial defector @@ pilot @@ jedha
saw gerrera @@ held
weapon @@ emperor @@ creating @@ claiming
destroy entire planets @@ power
pilot says @@ sent @@ father
mon mothma @@ weapon @@ stop @@ need
finished
captain andor @@ mission
story @@ pilot @@ authenticate
possible @@ find @@ father
development @@ critical @@ appears
super weapon
situation @@ gravity @@ given
saw @@ history
help us locate @@ hoping @@ father
testimony @@ senate @@ return
make sure @@ go free
rebel soldiers speaking indistinctly
draven captain andor
indistinct announcement @@ pa
k @@ 2so
reprogrammed imperial droid
remember
us @@ sending @@ see @@ jedha @@ council
apparently
bad idea @@ think @@ cassian
know
specialty
strategic analysis @@ keyboard clacking
weapons program @@ galen erso @@ vital @@ empire
heard @@ forget
extraction
find
kill
radio shuttle number lmtr @@ male dispatcher @@ 20
takeoff @@ prepare @@ check @@ authorization
met k @@ cassian @@ 2
charming
say whatever comes @@ tends @@ circuits
reprogram @@ byproduct
get @@ blaster
use @@ know
give @@ afraid
jedha @@ going
war zone
point @@ get
found
answer vague @@ zso @@ unconvincing @@ k @@ find
trust goes @@ ways
letting @@ keep
would @@ probability @@ like @@ know
using
high
get 90mg @@ let
dramatic music playing @@ buttons clicking
saw shouting lies
deceptions
see @@ let
cargo pilot ." @@ bodhi rook
uh @@ localboy @@ huh
speaking alien language
bodhi chuckles okay @@ hear
defected @@ capture @@ came
defected
saw every day @@ lies
grunts
risk everything @@ would @@ lies @@ lie
time
saw gerrera @@ speak @@ late
exhales okay
sorry
um
stammers
gave
find
galen erso @@ uh
told @@ find
inhales deeply
grunts
bor gullet
bor gullet @@ uh
wait
grunting
galen erso sent
told @@ find
dramatic music playing
unfortunate @@ tarkin
security breach @@ director krennic @@ jedha
many setbacks @@ delays
sighs
rumors circulating @@ heard word @@ city
lost @@ apparently
rather talkative cargo pilot
senate gets wind @@ project
countless systems @@ rebellion @@ flock
governor tarkin @@ battle station @@ finished
little concern @@ senate
director krennic @@ become
tolerate @@ emperor @@ delay
made time @@ rebellion @@ ally
problems simultaneously @@ suggest @@ solve
immediate test @@ weapon
find @@ failure @@ explaining
far less patient audience
fail
thrilling music playing
look frightened @@ matter @@ jyn
always protect
stardust
ever change
lyra trust
galen
door opens @@ gasps
orbit @@ controls @@ coming @@ cassian
jedha
left
find saw @@ find @@ father
dramatic music playing
destroyer
saw gerrera @@ old friend
cargo shipments @@ attacking
bringing
taking
kyber crystal @@ get
wondered @@ temple @@ stripping
know
weapon @@ fuel
weapon @@ father @@ building
leave target practice behind @@ maybe
talking
right @@ need @@ blend
stay @@ ship
imperial droid @@ blend
imperial occupation @@ city
wanna reprogram @@ people @@ half
half wanna put @@ hole @@ head
surprised @@ safety @@ concerned
might miss @@ worried @@ hit
sound @@ bad
bor gullet grunting @@ bodhi breathing heavily
saw bor gullet @@ thoughts @@ feel
safe @@ lie
whimpering @@ gasping
really brought @@ cargo pilot
bor gullet @@ truth @@ know
unfortunate side effect @@ one tends
lose one @@ mind
whimpering
somber music playing
indistinct chatter @@ alien language
jyn grunts @@ hey
watch
wait
sorry @@ sir
want @@ trouble @@ sorry
come
male imperial officer citizens @@ jedha
must come forward @@ information
missing cargo pilot @@ location
information shall @@ 600 credits @@ reward @@ awarded
contact @@ cassian
saw @@ rebels @@ one
gone missing
sister @@ looking
waiting @@ temple @@ destroyed
name @@ give
gets us @@ saw @@ meeting @@ hope
hope
yeah @@ rebellions @@ hope @@ built
st ormtrooper @@ 5 hands @@ see
get
check inside @@ show @@ identification
indistinct yelling
pilot
chirrut may @@ others @@ force
wait
others @@ may @@ force
would @@ trade @@ necklace @@ glimpse @@ future
yes
speaking
chirruttmwe
wearing @@ necklace @@ know
must pay @@ answer
kyber crystals @@ know
father
said @@ powered @@ lightsabers @@ jedi
jyn
let @@ go @@ come
strongest stars @@ kyber @@ hearts
let @@ go
make friends
speaking alien language
whills @@ guardians
kyber temple @@ protectors
nothing left @@ protect
causing trouble @@ everybody
seem awfully tense @@ sudden
town @@ ready @@ hurry @@ blow
male imperial announcer citizens @@ empire
imperial forces tirelessly fight saw gerrera @@ terror @@ reign
beloved city @@ people
truth @@ tools @@ justice @@ empire
announcement continues indistinctly
speaks alien language
speaking alien language
backup plan @@ tell
screaming @@ gunfire
incoming
indistinct shouting @@ gunfire
looks like @@ found saw @@ rebels
child wailing
jv @@ .!
woman shouts
terrorist @@ hit
get
shouts
man screams
alien language @@ shouting
kyber speaks alien language
come
shouting continue @@ gunfire
way
cassian
baton clicking
jyn grunting
stormtrooper g roan
know
yeah @@ course
told @@ thought @@ stay @@ ship
thought @@ boring
trouble
lot @@ explosions
two people blending @@ stormtrooper freeze
right
wait @@ ship
indistinct chatter
stormtrooper halt @@ stop right
taking @@ prisoners
yes @@ taking @@ prisoners
taking @@ prison @@ imprison
taking us @@ quiet @@ groans
fresh one @@ mouth
take @@ okay
right direction @@ point @@ could
take @@ sure
wait @@ taken @@ second @@ hey @@ far
wait @@ take @@ away
take @@ away
stay
need @@ diagnostics @@ check
diagnostics
running @@ diagnostics @@ capable
thank @@ much
chirrut let @@ peace @@ pass
peace @@ pass @@ let
force
fear nothing
force wilis
stop right @@ hey
blind
deaf
said stop right
weapons cocking
stormtroopers groaning
right @@ ls @@ foot
groaning continues
um gasps
almost shot
welcome
hostiles @@ clear
one hostile @@ us
right
thanks
sorry @@ slap @@ cassian
go back @@ wait @@ ship @@ call
jedi
jedi @@ anymore
dreamers like @@ fool
protect @@ force
protected
saw genera '? @@ get us
alien language @@ shouting
see @@ friends @@ empire
speaking alien language
kills @@ friends @@ anyone
saw gerrera @@ answer
galen erso @@ daughter
grunting
kidding @@ blind
indistinct chatter
shouting @@ groans
alien chatter @@ music
one @@ force @@ chirrut
one @@ force
pray
really
one @@ force
praying @@ open @@ door
possible @@ knows @@ bothers
snickering
devoted guardian @@ baze malbus @@ us
different priorities @@ think @@ force @@ beginning
chirrut relax @@ captain
worse cages @@ one
first
one sort @@ prison @@ captain
wherever @@ sense @@ go @@ carry
baze scoffs
indistinct chatter
speaking alien language
saw jyn
really
believe
surprise @@ quite @@ must
still friends
last time @@ saw
loaded blaster @@ knife @@ gave
bunker till daylight @@ wait @@ told
safe @@ knew
left @@ behind
best soldier @@ cadre @@ already
protecting @@ 16
dumped
imperial science officer @@ daughter
starting @@ people @@ figure
wanted @@ use @@ people @@ hostage
day goes
think
today
days
breath trembling
trap
laughs
pilot
message
breath es deeply
send
come
kill
much @@ left
alliance wants @@ father
weapon @@ think @@ sent @@ message
might actually help @@ think @@ sending @@ guess
want @@ jyn
wanted @@ introduction @@ got
want @@ rest
cause @@ care
cause
seriously
alliance
whatever @@ rebels
days @@ calling
ever brought @@ pain
imperial flag @@ stand @@ see
reign across @@ galaxy
problem @@ look
something @@ show
come
dramatic music playing
report @@ emperor @@ awaiting
one would hope @@ lord vader
occasion @@ might
thought @@ save @@ prudent
potential embarrassment
hardly warranted @@ concern
would @@ saying @@ make
imperial forces @@ evacuated
stand ready @@ entire moon @@ destroy
necessary
statement @@ need @@ manifesto
holy city @@ today @@ enough
target jedha city
prepare single reactor ignition
mechanical whirring
pterro sir @@ position @@ fire
commence primary ignition
next cell @@ one
baze '. @@ '?
imperial pilot
gonna kill @@ pilot @@ baze
wait @@ come
back
cassian okay @@ okay
groaning softly @@ pilot
shuttle pilot @@ pilot @@ hey
pilot
wrong
galen erso
name @@ know
pilot @@ message @@ brought
chuckles slowly
pilot
okay @@ good
galen erso
pa stand @@ announceri
sent @@ saw @@ message
watching @@ saw
save @@ perhaps @@ chance @@ alliance
perhaps @@ explain @@ chance
dare hope @@ though @@ much
jyn @@ chance @@ alive
possibly find
never faded @@ love @@ let @@ know
missed @@ desperately
beeps
stardust @@ jyn
think @@ imagine
bitter truths @@ taken @@ faced
soon enough @@ told
krennic would @@ well
time went
either dead @@ knew
would never find @@ well hidden
work @@ took @@ refused @@ life @@ knew
krennic realized @@ would @@ time @@ matter
longer needed @@ project @@ complete
one thing nobody expected
lied
lie @@ learned
beaten man @@ played @@ part
work @@ sanctuary @@ resigned
made @@ indispensable
revenge @@ laid @@ groundwork
death star @@ call
better name
coming soon @@ unleashed @@ day
weakness deep within @@ system @@ placed
never find @@ small @@ powerful @@ flaw
jyn
listening @@ jyn @@ beloved
wasted @@ much @@ life
try @@ think @@ strong @@ moments
pain
mother @@ family
pain @@ overwhelming @@ loss
risk failing even
think @@ hard
think
stardust
saw
reactor module @@ key
trap @@ place @@ laid
well hidden @@ unstable
one blast @@ entire station @@ part @@ destroy
plans @@ need
structural plans @@ death star @@ reactor @@ find
complete engineering archive @@ know
data vault @@ citadel tower @@ scarif
reactor module @@ pressurized explosion
entire station @@ chain reaction @@ set @@ destroy
rumbling
alien language @@ speaking
rumbling continues
go
alien language @@ shouting
k @@ 2
k @@ 2so
standing @@ requested
problem @@ horizon @@ although
horizon
ship @@ position @@ locate @@ bring
going
gotta find jyn
pilot @@ need @@ get
right
pilot @@ get
pilot
let @@ go
jyn
hey
gotta go
know @@ father
jyn @@ go
must go
us @@ come
run @@ longer
must save @@ come
go @@ come
time
saw save @@ rebellion
save @@ dream
rumbling continues
alien language @@ shouting
oh @@ beautiful
rumbling continues
let @@ go @@ chirrut
come
let @@ get
engines roaring
cassian get us
punch
optimistic @@ odds
k
engines roaring
thrilling music playing
decompression hiss
rumbling
come
punch
completed @@ calculations
make
indistinct conversations
director krennic @@ owe @@ believe @@ apology
work exceeds @@ expectations
tell @@ much @@ emperor
tell @@ patience @@ misadventures
weapon @@ rewarded
swift end @@ rebellion @@ bring
inkling
destructive potential
taking control @@ weapon @@ tell
years ago effective immediately @@ first spoke
scoffs
stand @@ amidst @@ achievement
recent security breaches @@ afraid
laid bare @@ inadequacies
military director
filled @@ breaches
silenced @@ jedha
pilot acted alone @@ think
installation @@ eadu @@ dispatched
galen erso @@ facility
see @@ oh
coded message @@ captain andor @@ sir @@ basteren
weapon confirmed ."
jedha destroyed ."
please advise ." @@ mission target located @@ eadu
destroyed
proceed
orders still stand @@ tell
tell @@ proceed @@ haste
plan @@ keep
idea @@ empire @@ building
kill galen erso @@ chance
indistinct radio chatter @@ whooshing
chirrut baze @@ tell
whole city
tell
cassian understood
radio controls beep
set course @@ eadu
setting course @@ eadu
father
think
galen @@ daughter
know
pilot @@ bodhi
message @@ brought
yes
father
could get right @@ said
could make @@ said @@ right
brave enough
listen @@ heart
something
late @@ guess
late
seems pretty late
jyni
people @@ beat
seen @@ message @@ father
death star @@ call
idea
way @@ defeat
wrong @@ father
build
without @@ knew
father made @@ choice
sacrificed @@ rebellion
trap inside @@ rigged
sent @@ message @@ bring
message
hologram
right @@ message
everything happened @@ fast
see
believe
one @@ got @@ convince
know @@ good
trap @@ kind
father made @@ trap @@ said
weakness @@ reactor @@ placed
years @@ hiding
said @@ reactor @@ blow
whole system goes @@ module
send word @@ need @@ alliance
done
way @@ thing @@ know @@ destroy
scarif @@ plans @@ go @@ get
risk sending
imperial territory @@ heart
find @@ bring @@ back
tell
music playing
navigator course set @@ sir @@ eadu
one @@ force
2so 20 degrees @@ right @@ k
10 degrees
lower
way @@ sure
landing trackers @@ bodhi
patrol squadrons
stay @@ low @@ keep @@ got @@ canyon
warning systems blaring
watch @@ right
26 chance @@ failure
much farther
never really come @@ way @@ sure @@ know
know @@ close
35 chance @@ failure
wanna know @@ thank @@ cassian
understand
put
wind
shuttle depot @@ keep going @@ right
cassian k @@ watch
grunting
tight @@ hold
hard @@ coming
alarms blaring
engines roaring
try
sir
gone dead @@ signal
draven squadron
target eadu
thunder rumbling
check stabilizers
lab @@ bodhi
research facility
yeah
ridge
shuttle depot straight ahead @@ us
yes @@ sure
hope
imperial ship left @@ still @@ steal
keeps us hidden @@ storm keeps @@ hopefully
coming @@ bodhi
ridge @@ go @@ check
coming
message @@ father
risk @@ messenger
ridiculous @@ message @@ got
knows @@ everyone
gun clicks
reactor module @@ one blast
whole system goes @@ ."
whole system goes @@ said @@ ."
work fixing @@ get @@ comms
want @@ right @@ handle @@ get
gonna go @@ small @@ rise @@ careful
see
get outta @@ let
thrilling music playing
look like @@ killer
friend @@ face
talking
captain andor
ask
look like @@ killer ?" @@ mean
force moves darkly
near @@ kill @@ creature
sniper configuration @@ weapon
indistinct announcement echoing
got @@ go
see much
thrilling music playing
indistinct chatter
indistinct announcement continues
breathing heavily
grunts
way
right behind
come
going
gonna follow jyn
path @@ clear
alone
good luck
need luck
groans
cassian comes back @@ leaving without
breathing heavily
thunder rumbles
see erso
far @@ come @@ baze
groans
patience @@ friend
panting
dark suit @@ galen
ride outta @@ get back @@ find us
well @@ heard
said @@ look @@ came
looking @@ go
hurry
dramatic music playing
krennic excellent news @@ galen
battle station @@ complete
proud @@ must
proud @@ krennic
gather @@ engineers @@ announcement
panting
indistinct conversation
yes
one @@ gentlemen
empire @@ betrayed
men gasping @@ exclaiming
pilot @@ one @@ conspired
send messages @@ rebellion
urge @@ traitor
step forward
indistinct conversations continue
mechanical voice speaks
well
group effort @@ consider
ready
aim
fire
stop
stop @@ krennic
nothing
spare
breathing heavily
fire
men groaning
groans
weapon @@ know @@ complete
share @@ let @@ details
stormtrooper screams
zso ". @@ k @@ cassian
hear @@ cassian
working @@ got @@ casswn
yes @@ problem @@ although @@ affirmative
alliance squadron approaching @@ clear @@ area
tell @@ hold
platform @@ jyn
jedha
saw gerrera @@ fanatics @@ band
holy city
last reminder @@ jedi @@ gone
never win
heard
zso relay @@ captain andor @@ k
general
captain andor requesting @@ squadron support @@ delay
please confirm @@ alliance forces @@ site
squadron leader @@ get
already engaged @@ sir
alarm blaring
dramatic music playing
men groaning
jyn
return fire @@ stations
get @@ fighters @@ air
father
indistinct shouting
groaning
shouting continues
male imperial gunner roger @@ 7 @@ 3
guns firing @@ explosions
guard fall back @@ fall back
need @@ evacuate @@ director
groaning
guns firing
exhales
man screams
mechanical voice speaks
groaning
grunting
papa
jyn
stardust
papa
seen @@ message
seen @@ hologram
must @@ destroyed
know
jyn
look
tell @@ much
galen groans slowly
papa
papa @@ come
take @@ stormtrooper @@ em
gotta go @@ jyn @@ come
leave
listen @@ gone
nothing @@ come
leave @@ come
move
way @@ cassian
stormtroopers yelling
come
well done
rebel
dramatic music playing
bodhi let @@ let @@ go
move @@ let @@ come
let @@ get @@ come
move
okay @@ let @@ k @@ go @@ 2
copy
exploding
bodhi ion thrusters low @@ storm @@ cleared
2so understood @@ k
lied
shock
went @@ kill @@ father
talking @@ know
deny
shock @@ put @@ place @@ looking
seen
bet
know
went @@ lied @@ came @@ alone
sighs
every chance @@ trigger @@ pull
well @@ might
living proof @@ father
risk @@ put
alliance bombs @@ killed
orders
orders @@ disobeyed
understand
orders
wrong @@ know
well @@ stormtrooper @@ might
know
luxury @@ deciding
want @@ something @@ care
suddenly @@ rebellion @@ real
us live
6 years old @@ fight since
lost everything @@ one
us @@ something @@ decided
way around @@ talk
yavin 4
stolen ship @@ make sure @@ know @@ coming
anybody else
sighs
dramatic music playing
door hissing
director krennic @@ lord
arrived
mysterious music playing
draining sound
raspy breathing
darth vader theme playing
director krennic
lord vader
seem unsettled
time @@ pressed
great many things @@ attend
apologies
great many things @@ explain
emperor requested @@ weapon @@ delivered
deserve @@ audience
make certain @@ understands @@ remarkable
potential
create problems @@ power @@ confirmed @@ certainly
city destroyed
imperial facility openly attacked
governor tarkin @@ test @@ suggested
director krennic @@ summoned @@ grovel
death star
senate @@ informed
mining disaster @@ jed ha @@ destroyed
yes @@ lord
rest @@ expect @@ emperor @@ assure
galen erso @@ compromised
weapon @@ way
still @@ command
speak @@ emperor
choking
director @@ choke @@ careful @@ aspirations
gasping
pam lo @@ must scatter @@ fleet
surrender @@ recourse
really talking @@ disbanding something @@ bail
worked @@ hard @@ create
give
suicide pact @@ joined @@ alliance
managed @@ gather @@ forces
gather @@ forces
imperial base @@ general draven @@ already blown
decision needed @@ made
war @@ want @@ pamlo
fight alone
going @@ alliance
truth @@ telling @@ need @@ act
please @@ councilors
simple
mass destruction @@ means @@ empire
rebellion
death star @@ nonsense
reason would @@ lie @@ father
benefit would @@ bring
final battle @@ lure @@ forces
destroy us
vaspar risk everything @@ based
testimony @@ criminal
imperial scientist @@ dying words @@ father
imperial pilot @@ jebel @@ forget
father gave @@ may @@ life @@ defeat @@ chance
told us
power @@ kind @@ empire
chance
choice ." @@ question
run @@ hide
scatter @@ plead @@ mercy @@ forces
much power @@ give way @@ evil @@ enemy
submission @@ galaxy @@ eternity @@ condemn
yes @@ time @@ fight
every moment @@ waste
another step closer @@ jedha @@ ashes
council member 1 @@ proposing
council member 2 @@ girl speak @@ let
best troops @@ soar @@ send
crowd murmuring
rebel fleet @@ send
death star plans @@ need @@ capture
hope @@ destroying
council muttering
imperial installation @@ asking us @@ invade
nothing @@ hope @@ based
rebellions @@ hope @@ built
hope
say @@ fight
say @@ rebellion @@ finished
murmuring
sorry @@ jyn
full support @@ without @@ council
sighs @@ odds @@ great
indistinct whispering
murmuring
rebel announcer general syndulla
please report @@ briefing room
look happy
surrender @@ prefer
wants @@ fight
strong @@ force
sure four @@ quite enough @@ us
need @@ many
talking
indistinct conversations
never gonna believe
support @@ appreciate
believe
volunteer @@ like
us
well @@ us
done terrible things @@ rebellion @@ behalf
spies
saboteurs @@ assassins
rebellion @@ everything
walked away @@ every time
wanted @@ something @@ forget
told @@ cause @@ believed
worth @@ cause
without @@ lost
done would @@ nothing @@ everything
gave @@ face
us could @@ none
comfortable @@ bodhi
bit cramped @@ fit
could go
okay @@ gear
grab anything @@ nailed
rebels talking indistinctly
cassian go @@ go
2so jyn @@ k
cassian said
things go bad @@ people sticking around @@ used
welcome home
indistinct announcement @@ pa
cheerful music playing @@ indistinct chatter
us @@ may @@ force
scattered applause @@ laughter
read back please @@ dispatcher cargo shuttle
going
ship @@ limits
supposed @@ one @@ instructions @@ board
yes
affirmative
impounded imperial ship
call sign @@ pilot
um @@ go
um
say something
come
rogue
rogue one
dispatcher rogue one
rogue one @@ beeping
well
rogue one @@ pulling away
pulling away
others say @@ war @@ inevitable @@ despite
yes @@ agree
must return @@ people @@ inform @@ alderaan
peace
need every advantage
friend
jedi
clone wars @@ well @@ served
hiding since @@ purge @@ lived @@ emperor
yes @@ send
need someone @@ trust
would trust @@ life
captain antilles @@ senator
sir @@ mission
ship whooshing
bodhi okay @@ coming
wide defensive shield @@ planet
single main entry gate
shuttle @@ equipped
allows us @@ access code
overdue @@ logged @@ empire @@ assuming
shut @@ gate
annihilated
dark vacuum @@ space @@ cold
survive @@ space
dramatic music playing
bodhi okay
goes
cargo shuttle sw @@ landing pad @@ 0608 requesting
gate officer cargo shuttle sw @@ 0608
arrival schedule @@ listed
gate control @@ bodhi acknowledged
eadu flight station @@ rerouted
transmitting clearance code
transmitting
gate officer cargo shuttle @@ sw @@ 0608
yes @@ entry @@ cleared
sighs @@ impressive
chuckles
tell @@ others
okay
scarif base announcer tractor beam test @@ bays 2 @@ 8
tractor beam test @@ bays 2 @@ 8
landing pad 9 @@ gate officer sw @@ cleared @@ 0608
please @@ acknowledge
lp 9 @@ bodhi sw @@ 0608 proceeding @@ instructed
cassian main building
citadel tower @@ bodhi
imperial structural archives @@ keep
plans @@ anywhere
top @@ dish @@ cassian
data files @@ takes @@ signal @@ send @@ lot @@ guess
landing track @@ engaged
landing track locked
landing
coming
saw genera used @@ say
sharp stick @@ one fighter @@ nothing left @@ take @@ lose @@ day
idea @@ coming
expect us @@ reason
make @@ ground
next chance @@ take
win @@ next
spent @@ chances
death star plans
k @@ find @@ cassian @@ 2
way @@ find
melshi
pao
chirrut @@ baze
main squad @@ take
move east @@ get wide @@ ship
tower @@ position @@ find
best spot @@ get
place @@ light
make 10 men feel like 100
men agreeing
troopers away @@ us @@ get
engine running @@ keep
way outta
dramatic music playing
landing pad officer cargo shuttle sw @@ 0608
receive inspection team @@ prepared
ready
hello
hey
probably looking @@ oh @@ manifest
would @@ helpful
imperial officer director krennic
scarif shield gate @@ entering
general ramda @@ informed @@ arrival
thrilling music playing
baze good luck
little sister
go @@ clear
right @@ move @@ melshi @@ let @@ go @@ come
transport control @@ announcer 925 @@ h
transport control @@ h @@ 925
thrilling music playing
bad feeling @@ got
quiet @@ kwhisidekiq
need @@ map
well @@ sure @@ one @@ lying
know
indistinct announcement @@ pa
indistinct conversations
one per pad
wanna draw @@ spot @@ pick
timing @@ go @@ call
stormtrooper 5 hey @@ rumors @@ hear
stormtrooper 6 yeah @@ marked obsolete @@ 15s
stormtrooper 5 oh boy @@ time
hey
groaning
clears throat
beeping
grunts
scarif @@ director @@ brings
galen erso
want every dispatch
every transmission @@ ever sent
inspection @@ called
ramdai
yes
get started
mouse droid beeping @@ music playing
mechanical whirring
k
optimal route @@ data vault
89 stormtroopers @@ places @@ path
way @@ make @@ 33
killed
talk @@ melshi
standing @@ ready
light
stormtrooper g roan
come
explosions echoing
blind
garrison @@ deploy
move
indistinct shouting
thrilling music playing
troopers
troopers @@ left
get
alarm blaring
yelling
man groans
scarif base @@ romodi sir
rebel incursion @@ reporting
director krennic @@ want @@ speak
sir @@ scarif
original plans @@ station @@ kept
prepare @@ jump @@ hyperspace
inform lord vader
help
necessary
groans
senator
stop right @@ private
speak @@ let
intercepted imperial transmission
scarif @@ rebels
admiral raddus @@ speak @@ need
ship @@ returned
going @@ fight
indistinct yelling
groans
rebel announcer attention @@ flight personnel
please report @@ commanders immediately
flight personnel
scarif @@ redirected
pilots @@ briefed
squadron leaders en route
may @@ force
scarif @@ going
nobody ever tell @@ r2 @@ anything
d2 beeping @@ r2
move
shouting
forward
keep drawing
groans
officer 1 pad 12 @@ report @@ ground
need numbers @@ flank @@ coming
officer 2 pad 14 @@ going
status please @@ pads report @@ immediately
officer 3 oh @@ rebels everywhere
taking fire
pad 14 request assistance @@ pad 12
pad 2
spot 40 rebels heading west @@ pad 2
pad 5 @@ tell @@ rebels @@ pinned @@ get
pad 5 @@ help us @@ yong @@ overrun
please confirm @@ pad 8 @@ pad 12 @@ pad 10
report @@ confirm
pad 5 immediately @@ get reinforcements
working @@ k @@ cassian
right hand
men groaning @@ yelling
baze
run
grunting
karabast
move
yelling
dramatic music plays
rebel alliance @@ admiral raddus
squadron leaders @@ report
blue leader standing @@ admiral
gold leader standing
red leader standing
rebel ships @@ sir
get admiral gorin @@ immediately
rebel fleet @@ director
amassing outside @@ shield
lock @@ base
shield @@ close
gold squadrons @@ attack formations @@ red
fleet @@ defend
blue squadron @@ surface @@ get
gate @@ close
merrick copy @@ admiral
blue squadron
blue leader @@ copy
blue leader @@ long @@ copy
field aperture @@ close
come
pull
screaming
guns firing
rebel fleet @@ arrived
fighting @@ beach
locked @@ base
shield gate @@ closed
mean
trapped
rebel fleet @@ could transmit @@ plans
tell @@ signal @@ get @@ coming
data files @@ size
problem
never get
shield gate @@ take @@ someone
hear @@ bodhi
tell @@ bodhi
bodhi
standing
started fighting @@ lockdown @@ base
rebel fleet @@ listen @@ know
shield gate @@ gotta tell @@ hole @@ blow
transmit @@ plans
comms tower @@ wait @@ hooked
tied
way @@ getting
way @@ find
cover @@ backs
need
wanted one @@ right
jyn erso @@ continually unexpected @@ behavior
jyn @@ come
yelling continues
sa @@ kalla
fire @@ command
shouting continues
look
rebels cheering
laughing
get ready @@ gonna @@ go
shield gate @@ closed
stuck
rebel fleet @@ pulling
signal strong enough @@ get
trapped @@ let @@ know
communications tower @@ connect
patch us @@ landing pad
radio @@ get
master switch @@ get one @@ guys @@ find
comms tower @@ us @@ get @@ connection @@ activate
okay
go
lieutenant @@ going
unknown @@ sir
raise
rebel frequencies @@ blocked
star destroyers @@ keep trying @@ engage
start probing @@ shield @@ let
yes @@ sir
rebel pilot @@ going
stay
thrilling music playing
alien shriek
zso schematic bank @@ data tower two @@ k
find
searching
tape @@ locate
use @@ need @@ handles @@ extraction
supposed
whoa
well @@ finally
wait @@ stop
went @@ rebels
cassian k @@ going
one
well @@ ah
stormtroopers grunting
come
red leader @@ gold leader
shield gate @@ attack run @@ starting
watch @@ towers @@ tight @@ keep
six @@ form @@ five @@ fighters
enemy fighters coming @@ sir
tonc melshi @@ melshi @@ come
patching us @@ bodhi sent @@ signal
tower @@ open @@ line @@ guys
please advise
master switch @@ comm tower @@ base
master switch @@ looking @@ describe
master switch @@ look like
merrick u @@ wings @@ troops @@ reinforce @@ beach
fighters
air attack @@ shield
troop reinforcements @@ go
yelling @@ forjedha
shield @@ effect
thing take @@ much
stick close @@ red five @@ goin '?
red five @@ trying @@ lose
red five @@ need help
navigational systems ." @@ hyperspace tracking
two screens
structural engineering ." @@ open @@ one
pilot 1 @@ got one @@ tail
pilot 2
yelling continues
project code names @@ pax aurora ." @@ mark omega @@ stellarsphere
grunts
cluster prism @@ blacksaber ." @@ war @@ mantle
stardust ."
know
identify @@ hey
groans
incoming fire @@ get cover
yelling
casswn k @@ stardust @@ need @@ file
stardust
shutting @@ k
climb
still send @@ plans @@ fleet
shield gate @@ open
tower @@ broadcast
vault door @@ locking
k
good bye @@ k
unauthorized access @@ data vault @@ sir
sir @@ come
guard squadron @@ send @@ battle
two men
get @@ control @@ beach
casswn bodhi @@ fleet @@ call
shuttle @@ get
plug
hit @@ gate
shield @@ send @@ plans @@ open
dramatic music playing
shouting continues
bodhi groaning
pilot general @@ behind
beeping
yelling
shouting
step back
going
come
thrilling music playing
indistinct shouting
panting
grunting
grunts
melshi
please @@ come
tied @@ end
open line @@ need
coughs hang
master switch
near @@ console
going
groaning
got
careful
okay
jyn
groans
one @@ force
chirrut
mechanical voice grunting
one @@ force
force
come back @@ chirrut
one @@ force
yes
keep going
screams
cassian
thud5
come @@ chirrut
chirrut
panting
go
okay
okay @@ look @@ force
chirrut
always find
one @@ force
dramatic music playing
sustaining heavy damage @@ deflector shields @@ 50
turning back
press @@ attack
gold leader ". @@ opening @@ hit
gold nine @@ gold leader @@ see
ion torpedoes away
engine shutting
imperial commander @@ happening
lost engine power @@ sir
star destroyer @@ disabled
rogue one calling @@ alliance ships @@ hear
rogue one @@ anybody
come
rogue one @@ admiral raddus @@ hear
laughs
plans
death star plans @@ found
communications tower @@ transmit
shield gate @@ take
gonna get @@ way
hammerhead corvette @@ idea @@ call
rogue one @@ stand
galen
yelling continues
somber music playing
one @@ force
weapons firing
mechanical voices grunting
um grunt
corvette five @@ target @@ locked
prepare @@ impact
guns firing
grunting
sublight thrusters @@ full power
whooshing
grunts
automated voice reset antenna alignment
alarms blaring
reset antenna alignment
thrilling music playing
reverse engines @@ full power
men groaning
automated voice antenna aligned
transmit @@ ready
grunting
gasps
straining
know
jyn erso
lyra @@ galen @@ daughter
lost
oh
revenge @@ father
death star @@ flaw @@ built
put @@ middle @@ machine @@ fuse
entire galaxy @@ told @@ light
shield
rebel base @@ never reach @@ signal
ships @@ destroyed @@ air
lose nothing @@ time
hand
rebellion @@ die
automated voice transmitting
transmitting
receiving transmission @@ scarif @@ admiral
grunts
leave
let @@ go
transmission received
plans @@ admiral
think anybody @@ listening
someone
massive object @@ sir @@ detecting
hyperspace @@ emerging
begin targeting @@ sir @@ shall @@ fleet
lord vader @@ handle @@ fleet
single reactor ignition @@ target @@ scarif @@ base
yes @@ sir
come
may fire @@ ready
automated voice commence primary ignition
rogue one @@ may @@ force
ships prepare @@ jump @@ hyperspace
father would @@ proud @@ jyn
rebel flagship @@ imperial commander @@ lord @@ disabled
received transmissions @@ surface
boarding party @@ prepare
yes @@ lord
hurry
gotta go @@ go @@ let
move
let @@ hurry @@ go
let @@ go
stuck
hey
hey @@ help
alarm sounding
vader breathing
open fire
h6lp us
jammed
pull
take
launch
alarm sounding
make sure @@ secure @@ airlock
escape pods @@ prepare
highness
transmission @@ received
sent us
hope
theme music playing