south park @@ time @@ gonna @@ goin
friendly faces everywhere
humble folks without temptation
woes behind @@ south park @@ gonna leave @@ goin
ample parking day @@ night
people spouting @@ neighbor !" @@ howdy
south park @@ gonna see @@ unwind @@ heading
mrph rmhmhm rm
south park @@ mine @@ meet @@ friends @@ come
south park elementary @@ harris attention @@ vicinity @@ units
code red
gun cocks principal calling @@ school assembly @@ help
officers needed
engine turns @@ school
geez louise @@ oh
tires screeching @@ sirens wailing
guns cocking
tires screech @@ glass shatters
need @@ gym @@ get
half go around @@ half go @@ way @@ side
go around back @@ barbrady
breathing heavily
right @@ officers
stop chatting @@ told @@ leslie @@ friends
leslie thinks @@ see @@ officers @@ apparently
talking @@ important @@ friends
world countries @@ third @@ learning @@ diversity
one
school @@ right @@ remove
nobody move @@ happening @@ aah
oh @@ got @@ get
gunshot aah
aah
officer barbrady @@ town @@ outraged
held accountable @@ tired @@ police @@ people @@ actions
mayor @@ know @@ gunman @@ bomb
old latino child @@ unarmed 6 @@ year @@ shot
sorry
fired
please @@ mayor
know
used @@ town @@ remember @@ policeman
sixth graders @@ chase away @@ used @@ bob
another time @@ barbrady
last thing @@ needs @@ go
gun @@ badge
sunglasses
sunglasses @@ please
done @@ barbrady
want @@ town
go
thought @@ shot @@ mexican
whispering latino american
latino american @@ shit
go away
belong anywhere @@ town @@ progressive @@ one
trying @@ sleep @@ quiet @@ hey
god damn @@ people @@ get
makes @@ charge
bleep house @@ cause
drum thuds
man @@ make @@ hey @@ bitch @@ beat
aah
addict vagrants @@ yeah @@ got @@ drug @@ bunch
need assistance @@ yard @@ trespassing
oh
come help @@ well @@ like
get fired @@ want
talking
homeless people @@ scaring @@ kids
something @@ need @@ come
see
minority persuasion @@ homeless people
matter
oh @@ matters
nobody cared @@ could beat @@ used @@ see @@ minorities
us joined @@ reason @@ lot @@ force
homeless people @@ want @@ mitch @@ hey @@ go @@ arrest
minorities @@ beat @@ able
thank
yeah @@ think @@ good
whole department @@ maybe turning @@ hula school @@ thinking @@ fact
think
god damn
coming
karen brought @@ syringes @@ sake @@ one @@ christ
well @@ bad
cops @@ come
homeless away @@ scare @@ nobody
lock disengages @@ door squeaks
sweetheart @@ hey
let go @@ uh @@ force
sorry
dog whimpers
old girl @@ worry
little tough @@ might @@ medication @@ afford
way @@ find
know
like @@ help
needed @@ like
oh @@ guys @@ god
totally gay @@ gay @@ guys
token @@ kenny
butters told @@ token @@ kenny @@ gay @@ dude
lying @@ dude
abandoned buildings around kenny @@ old @@ house
big ninja clubhouse @@ token turned @@ kenny
scare people away @@ play ninja @@ trying @@ dress
gay
gayest thing ever @@ dude
bleep dumb @@ ninjas
go see @@ got @@ dude @@ come
way
traditional japanese music plays
wah
wah @@ hoo @@ ah
ninja honor @@ defend
wo @@ chew
intruders @@ defend @@ base
music continues
ninja fortress @@ see @@ hey @@ guys @@ come
gong crashes oh @@ guys @@ god @@ gay
kenny built
yeah @@ david @@ clyde
guys @@ come @@ check
uh @@ thanks @@ good
sausage party @@ oh @@ god @@ dude
really scared @@ pretty cool @@ us @@ people @@ dude
yeah @@ sure
man @@ know @@ hey @@ excuse
middle eastern music plays
aahhhh @@ aah
grunting
oh @@ god
tires squeal @@ go
tires squeal @@ engine revs
pretty cool
well @@ way @@ school @@ heard @@ girl
talking @@ loud @@ even @@ anything
someone ends @@ getting shot
want @@ hey
okay @@ duty
nice pinot @@ came
go somewhere else @@ yeah @@ well @@ copper
shitpatown @@ people @@ care
take kindly @@ impose @@ folks @@ authority
underprivileged
happy assholes @@ trigger @@ racist @@ look @@ cops
really
even know @@ table @@ means @@ farm @@ bet
yeah @@ right
wow
whole foods @@ month
need cops @@ already
cool
great honor @@ want @@ see @@ ninjas
serious @@ joining @@ club
must promise @@ warrior @@ uphold @@ code
totally @@ sweet @@ ninjas @@ dude
fortress super badass @@ must strive @@ together @@ make
keep @@ intruders
let us proceed @@ training @@ end
talk @@ minute @@ dude
let kyle @@ think @@ okay @@ ninja @@ listen
said ninjas @@ gay
probably gonna try @@ turn @@ around
cause kyle knows @@ heard
kyle right @@ talking
yeah @@ cool
butters
said ninjas @@ one @@ gay
want @@ problem @@ make
things @@ problems @@ man @@ lots @@ butters
try sparring @@ want @@ hey @@ eric
yes @@ butters
ow @@ ooh @@ coughs
intruders
yeah @@ right
abandoned buildings @@ shoot
grunting
middle eastern music plays
aah
large protest tonight @@ south park @@ town @@ holding
police department @@ outside
townspeople say @@ protest @@ meant @@ dialogue @@ begin
law enforcement @@ relationship
supposed @@ protect @@ citizens
album scratching bleep @@ police
underground @@ straight @@ comin
young nigga got @@ cause @@ brown @@ bad
police think @@ color
minority @@ kill @@ authority
shit @@ one @@ cause @@ bleep
punk mother bleep @@ gun @@ badge
thrown @@ jail @@ beaten
go toe @@ toe @@ middle @@ cell
police @@ bleep
bleep bleep
silly club @@ stand @@ pulling
ass badge @@ hand @@ gun @@ fake
take @@ see @@ gun
mma bleep @@ punk @@ go
ice cube @@ swarm
mother bleep @@ blue uniform
cpt @@ cause
punk police @@ huh @@ afraid
young nigga @@ warpath
gonna @@ finished @@ bloodbath
l @@ dying @@ cops
got something @@ yo @@ say @@ dre
police @@ bleep
aahhhh
terrorist organizations @@ lured @@ children
shocking report shows @@ south park @@ town @@ kids
swearing loyalty @@ murderous regime
pretty badass @@ yeah
um @@ like @@ fortress
pretty cool @@ see
way @@ man @@ life @@ attractive
butters well @@ tough @@ cool @@ cause
stuff @@ fight
yeah @@ whatever @@ want @@ like
totally rad @@ us @@ scared @@ people
say @@ gay
never said @@ oh @@ god @@ gay
wait @@ said @@ gay
total lie
say something homophobic @@ craig make love @@ way tweek @@ would
backstabbing jew @@ lying
stan
kids swearing loyalty @@ growing number @@ isis @@ doubt
progressive town @@ problematic @@ could
old girl @@ go
make
ew
spare @@ dollar
thank @@ sorry
god damn @@ ew
town @@ part @@ mayor @@ gentrify @@ bust @@ ass
homeless people @@ overrun
suddenly coming
mayor @@ going
barely eat @@ wife @@ shop
town like @@ homeless problem
must look @@ root @@ causing
isis
troubled kids @@ turned @@ backs @@ america
taken @@ sodosopa @@ homeless @@ forced
would kids @@ town want @@ part
bad kids
shitty parents @@ rotten @@ probably @@ inside
fair dad @@ always tried @@ son
want @@ make @@ angry
well dad @@ really like @@ something @@ r @@ part
feel like @@ lots @@ fun @@ character @@ building
fun
believe
something greater @@ believe
strict warrior code @@ following
traditions @@ faiths @@ believe
greater path @@ path @@ way @@ warrior @@ p
stay united @@ long @@ honor
enemies @@ defeat
waghgh waaaaghghhhg
wow @@ right @@ fellas
really freaked @@ people @@ ninjas
really apologetic @@ okay @@ got
tell @@ okay @@ mean
geez @@ embarrassing
help us @@ homeless
pretty sure @@ town @@ taking @@ police @@ isis @@ help
hawaiian music plays
joined isis @@ town @@ officers @@ kids
know
say
town @@ right @@ danger
know @@ kids @@ capable
sorry @@ geez
kaholo koloa @@ work @@ got
lomilomi chicken ready @@ big ho @@ olaule @@ get
leaves us @@ oh
enough time @@ isis @@ deal
homeless people @@ right @@ look
gentrified food @@ arts district
twisted kids @@ stop
said bleep @@ police @@ hey
ice cube @@ tupac
right @@ oh @@ guys
find somebody else @@ sorry @@ guess
dirty shit @@ want @@ difficult
ready @@ luau @@ got
might even kiss @@ dude
went @@ told @@ stan @@ kyle
playing basketball @@ remember
yeah
said kenny @@ playing ninja @@ token
kyle said @@ ninjas @@ gay
gay ?" @@ said @@ question @@ ninjas
remember
thought @@ said @@ first
got everyone remembering @@ wrong @@ see @@ kyle
get kicked @@ want @@ group
lie @@ jews @@ caught
jewish ninja @@ cannot trust @@ butters
token @@ guys
stan
actual ninjas want @@ us @@ talk
people overseas @@ mail @@ kenny @@ got @@ e
whoa @@ dude
find
bleep ninjas @@ dude
static hissing
brave children @@ committed @@ cause
heard
impressed
thanks @@ dude @@ cool
important
would like @@ however @@ help
wiring @@ money @@ going
whoa @@ cool
greatest thing ever @@ guys
record straight @@ uh @@ something @@ set @@ excuse @@ could
course
trusted @@ jews
us @@ one @@ mean @@ jew
see @@ problematic
extremely
yes
mc hammer plays oh @@ oh @@ u @@ touch
thank @@ tell @@ guys
randy hey @@ barbrady
officer barbrady
dog whimpers @@ pants
wha
hey @@ buddy
want
would @@ policeman @@ like
policeman @@ good
old fool @@ bumbling
true @@ said
town needs @@ look @@ fact @@ barbrady
need
shoot @@ need @@ kids
shoot kids
shoot kids @@ want
really bad kids terrorists
totally different
oh
minorities
yeah @@ think @@ couple
look @@ barbrady
wrong
anybody else ever @@ town back @@ protected
used
need
town needs @@ cop @@ barbrady
go shoot @@ kids
cartman guys @@ us @@ know @@ hard
must face hard facts @@ truly @@ ninjas
ninja leader overseas @@ last night @@ spoke @@ private
long time @@ hebrew faith @@ talked @@ jews
told @@ lot @@ know
things @@ tell @@ know @@ able
talking @@ guy
jews cannot @@ abundantly clear @@ ninjas
went @@ talk @@ kyle @@ house
found
kyle confessed
brainwashed butters @@ thinking @@ stan
homophobic slur @@ used @@ refer @@ organization
almost got away
kyle tried @@ kill
faster ninja @@ luckily
would never call ninjas gay @@ kyle knew
take @@ gag
try @@ tell @@ lying @@ going
liar @@ kyle @@ believe
right @@ kyle
stan @@ clyde
token
things @@ ask
black rage
insects chirping
middle eastern music playing
gasps oh @@ jesus
oh @@ isis @@ god
chicken tastes like shit
organic chicken @@ okay okay @@ dad
whole foods @@ comfortable shopping
homeless people
worry @@ change
soon @@ shitpatown @@ enjoy
stan
playing ninjas @@ kenny @@ house
ninjas @@ gay
mean sodosopa @@ yeah
wait @@ minute
japanese music plays ninjas
middle eastern music plays
japanese music plays
scary
japanese music plays gay
middle eastern music plays scary
music switching gay
scary @@ gay
randy
scary
gay
staaaan
cartman oh @@ misunderstanding @@ get
kyle said ninjas @@ told clyde @@ see @@ gay
clyde thought @@ kyle
said ninjas @@ saying @@ gay
meaning @@ kyle
kyle nobody ever gave @@ fat turd @@ shit
ninjas club @@ token @@ kicked @@ favor @@ cartman
hai
kick
ninja
hate jews @@ made @@ guys
please
stan
freeze
shit @@ oh
want @@ shoot @@ please
stan cool
groaning
children flinch
feeling angry @@ understand @@ town
getting pretty angry
give
please @@ boys
end violently @@ make
stupid ninjas
david aah
aaaah
thinking
boys innocently playing ninja @@ pull @@ gun
david rodriguez @@ lucky @@ live
everybody told @@ terrorists
thought
turns @@ policeman
figure
said @@ needed @@ kill @@ kids
gonna lay @@ us @@ oh
kids ," @@ said @@ kill
said @@ remember @@ question
kids ?" @@ said @@ kill
sorry @@ one @@ cover @@ ass
investigation @@ going
takes
today @@ times @@ policeman
even know @@ table @@ means @@ farm
siren chirps
stay @@ people @@ let @@ go
relocated
kick us @@ man @@ hey
oh @@ cop
thank @@ officers
right @@ got @@ deal
yes
right @@ come
aah
take @@ sodosopa @@ please @@ back
isis
ninjas
oh @@ gay
told @@ guys
tell
said ninjas @@ bleep gay
want @@ listen
nooo
door opens
officer barbrady
yes
watching
see
truly wants @@ town @@ protect @@ man
town longer @@ almost anyone
noticed changes lately
yeah @@ lot @@ changes
officer @@ coincidence
plan @@ part
beloved town @@ take @@ everyone
little girl named @@ know
leslie
dramatic music playing
ricksg www @@ sync @@ corrected @@ com @@ addic7ed