open ocean
surface @@ planet @@ half @@ covers
yet @@ part
watery desert @@ life @@ empty
constant search @@ spend @@ lives @@ hunters
elusive prey @@ scarce
seemingly barren wilderness @@ remarkably
largest hunter @@ home
blue whale
weighing 200 tonnes @@ 30 metres long
biggest animals ever @@ lived
immense size @@ despite
blue whales @@ streamlined @@ one
swimmers @@ energy @@ efficient
widely spread @@ scarce @@ food
blue whales must journey across whole oceans
single meal @@ find
hundred miles @@ weeks @@ travel @@ time @@ day
largest animal feeds @@ smallest @@ one @@ ocean
small shrimp @@ like crustaceans @@ krill
gigantic mouth takes @@ much effort @@ opening
swarms @@ rich @@ krill @@ concentrated
scattered @@ krill
even worth slowing
food must go @@ lonely search @@ blue whale
feeding opportunities @@ far @@ always
never last long
devoured within minutes @@ prey
hunters must resume @@ endless search
high seas @@ frigate birds @@ pirates
gentle trade winds @@ soaring effortlessly
scan vast tracts @@ ocean @@ food
heavy oils @@ frigates must @@ lightweight @@ afford
sea birds @@ waterproof @@ plumage
getting wet would @@ lethal
seafaring hunter @@ may seem @@ impossible limitation
frigate birds overcome @@ others @@ help @@ handicap
dorado
ocean predators @@ voracious @@ one @@ fastest
patrol close @@ surface @@ searching @@ prey
little fish try @@ undulating swell @@ hide amidst @@ ocean
cover
seek @@ hide @@ game
waves @@ played @@ amongst
cover blown
escape seems impossible
unique ability @@ particular fish
flying fish
extra thrust @@ tails
flying fish get airborne
good wind @@ metres @@ hundreds @@ glide
frigate birds @@ waiting
frigates join @@ hunt
literally caught @@ flying fish @@ devil
deep blue sea
flying fish get @@ much lift
become easy prey @@ frigates
evade attack @@ dive
could fall @@ mouths @@ dorado
help @@ dorado
wily frigate bird @@ flying fish specialist @@ become
single feather wet @@ without getting
open ocean hunters @@ travel @@ search @@ food @@ able
wait @@ meal @@ come @@ choice
sargassum weed @@ mat
middle @@ drifts @@ atlantic
live entirely @@ surface @@ seaweed @@ sargassum
sea floor @@ never attaches
floating tangle @@ fronds
surprising open ocean predator @@ home
sargassum fish
every part @@ body mimics @@ weed
walking @@ swimming @@ suited @@ fins
barely swim @@ fact
entire life marooned @@ weedy raft @@ spend
sargassum fish must lie @@ wait
seeking shelter amongst @@ weed
unfortunately @@ mat @@ empty
wasting valuable energy searching @@ least @@ food
featureless ocean
much sought @@ juvenile fish @@ sanctuary @@ mats
last
first opportunity @@ weeks
must get closer
within @@ strike @@ prey @@ centimetres
perfect camouflage @@ weed @@ trusting @@ hides
patience
close enough @@ still
clearly getting @@ hunger @@ better
time @@ surely
blown
gets another chance @@ weeks @@ may
open ocean @@ vast
find enough prey @@ hunters
team @@ searching
highly sophisticated social groups @@ dolphins live
working together @@ huge area @@ ocean @@ cover
spinner dolphins
twisting leaps @@ still debatable @@ make
perhaps @@ form @@ communication
perhaps @@ fun
small groups sometimes come together
pods five thousand strong @@ forming super
hunt
vocal @@ spinners @@ dolphins
use echolocation @@ sonar @@ kind
prey @@ find
hunter sends @@ series @@ clicks
returning echoes @@ listens
metres away @@ distant prey @@ scan @@ hundreds @@ allowing
wide hunting line @@ pod spreads @@ super
mile across
wall @@ sound @@ producing
favourite prey @@ searching
lantern fish
numerous fish @@ planet
small fish spend @@ deep ocean @@ time
way beyond @@ reach @@ dolphins
surface @@ feed @@ come
become prey
shoal @@ found
dolphins use @@ different way @@ sonar
loud blasts @@ stun @@ fish
simply gather
dolphins work @@ underside @@ shoal @@ feed
escaping back @@ stop @@ safety @@ prey @@ deep
within @@ shower @@ scales @@ minutes @@ left
ocean depths @@ drifting downwards
largest habitat @@ deep ocean @@ life @@ far @@ earth
bizarre hunters @@ home
much scarcer @@ surface @@ food
sea predators must @@ deep
save precious energy
waiting patiently @@ viper fish
special light @@ producing organs @@ head
entice prey towards fearsome teeth
jelly hunters also live @@ yet deadly @@ strange
simply drift
trailing tentacles loaded @@ lethal stings
beating hairs @@ propelled @@ others @@ lines
glide gently @@ darkness
sea jelly predator @@ top deep @@ beroe
actively hunt @@ jellies
like @@ ctenophore
gelatinous prey @@ grasp
special teeth @@ like spikes @@ mouth @@ beroe
sea hunters @@ many deep @@ hang @@ abyss
saving @@ energy
prey @@ luring @@ come
chiroteuthis
prey using long sticky tentacles @@ sea squid fishes @@ deep
glowing lure
attract passing prey @@ pulsing
gentle twitch adds @@ temptation
rare bonanza @@ meal @@ darkness
vast blue desert @@ open ocean may
oases @@ like @@ deserts
scattered widely across @@ endless space
small islands @@ thousands
underwater mountains @@ summits
sea floor many miles @@ rise
sea mounts deflect deep ocean currents upwards
forcing nutrient laden water @@ surface
busy oasis @@ big blue @@ emptiness
potential prey @@ shelter @@ plenty
coral @@ amongst
hidden beneath @@ reef @@ caves
small fish take refuge
reach @@ predators
lion fish
speed @@ built
delicate maneuvering @@ success @@ depends
plain sight @@ strategy @@ hide
false sense @@ security @@ prey @@ lulling
visually confusing @@ lion fish @@ stripes
prey @@ making @@ judge @@ difficult @@ close
extravagant fins @@ using
deliberate tail movements @@ hide slow
edges ever closer
must get @@ within @@ centimetres
sudden strike @@ close enough
got one
water currents @@ many residents @@ sustain @@ deep
also attract visitors @@ oases
silky sharks
sea mounts @@ journey hundreds @@ miles
gathering places @@ featureless ocean @@ using
joined @@ hammerheads
sharks constantly travel @@ gal pagos
isolated sea mounts @@ eastern pacific
one knows @@ sure @@ numbers @@ gather
certainly come @@ search @@ oases @@ food
resident silver sides cloaks @@ sea mount @@ school
little fish stay close @@ coral
sharks @@ get @@ able
potential feast @@ agile visitors @@ attracted
striped bonito
golden trevally
reef @@ prey @@ need @@ meal @@ get @@ drive @@ away
open water
silver sides stick close @@ sea floor @@ long
predators @@ evade
search elsewhere @@ frustrated hunters @@ time
open ocean @@ easy meal @@ never
southern ocean @@ encircling antarctica
wildest seas @@ planet
tossed waters @@ bring nutrients @@ surface @@ storm
creating isolated patches @@ richness
calm tropics @@ far
beaten ocean @@ weather @@ home @@ albatross
black browed albatross
frigate birds @@ size
three times @@ heavy
totally different flying technique @@ need
longest wingspan @@ bird @@ albatross
southern ocean winds @@ power @@ exploit @@ enables
wind @@ glide @@ first
lift @@ harnessing @@ give @@ energy
descend downwind @@ turn @@ speed @@ picking
wind fronts like @@ soaring
travel hundreds @@ ocean @@ miles @@ day @@ albatross
barely beating @@ wings
often spend weeks @@ sea
prey without ever returning @@ searching @@ land
last @@ food
krill close @@ surface @@ patch
winds @@ strong
waterproofing oils @@ extra weight @@ albatrosses @@ afford
feathers
duck dive @@ meter
southern ocean @@ rely @@ churning
range @@ prey @@ bring
like @@ land @@ breed @@ birds @@ albatross
suitable islands @@ south atlantic
heavily overcrowded
largest albatross colonies @@ steeple jason @@ world @@ one
million come back @@ nearly half @@ young @@ year @@ raise
adults share parenting duties
returning every @@ feed @@ days @@ chick
feeding done
time @@ sea @@ head
packed colony @@ way @@ need @@ make @@ edge
take @@ room
heavy @@ albatrosses
strong enough @@ get airborne @@ wind @@ places
special runway @@ using
good head wind
ocean may appear featureless @@ air
powerful currents @@ surface @@ network @@ beneath
move @@ constantly
force @@ currents
life @@ distribution @@ determine
whole community @@ ocean drifters
hitches rides @@ sea @@ rivers
pelagic red crabs
tiny floating plants @@ gathered @@ feed @@ animals
plankton fueled @@ currents @@ bloom
legs slow @@ fine hairs @@ descent
swim back @@ tail @@ flicks
continue feeding
wandering crabs @@ currents @@ carry
larger predators @@ also serve @@ ocean @@ highways
striped marlin
beautifully streamlined
travel huge distances @@ minimum effort
ocean currents @@ hunters patrol @@ boundaries
prey often gathers
incredible sense @@ smell @@ predator
detect faint trails left @@ prey @@ able
big prize @@ somewhere
looking @@ kinds @@ hunters
plankton bloom @@ great shoals @@ fish @@ attracted
many miles long @@ single school @@ sardines
fish swim tightly together
safety @@ numbers
defense relies @@ coordination
sardines move @@ one @@ attacked
fish instantly matches @@ neighbour @@ movements
whole shoal moves @@ synchrony
lone sea lion @@ rapid reactions @@ keep
sea lions arrive @@ even
coordinated defenses @@ seem @@ sardines @@ break
shoal @@ big
sea lions need @@ manageable group @@ smaller @@ isolate @@ fish
predators
fish still @@ advantage
sea lions @@ surface @@ sardines @@ keep
wait @@ others @@ join
tuna
arrival changes everything
tuna attack @@ escape route @@ sardines @@ cutting
deeper water
shear waters @@ next @@ appear
also surprisingly agile underwater @@ excellent flyers
many predators attacking @@ sides
shift away @@ advantage starts @@ sardines
fish pack ever tighter
shoaling strategy @@ makes @@ hunters @@ easier
copper sharks
scented blood @@ water
predators never attack one another @@ surprisingly @@ perhaps
work together @@ fish @@ corral @@ ball
taking turns @@ mouthful @@ grab
common dolphins
shoal gets ever smaller
sardine scrambles desperately @@ middle @@ hide
escape
whale finishes @@ feast @@ bryde
sardines devoured @@ tonnes @@ less @@ hour
predators melt away @@ blue
separate ways @@ going
still searching @@ blue whale @@ meal
giant hunger @@ satisfy
must catch @@ four tonnes @@ large @@ food @@ day @@ average
many days may pass without feeding
great size
enables blue whales @@ travel @@ furthest
roaming every ocean @@ tropics @@ poles
trapped @@ surface @@ fish
dense patch @@ krill
finally found @@ searching @@ long @@ blue
meal big enough @@ massive mouth worthwhile @@ make opening
metres across @@ krill swarm @@ hundreds
packed tight
whale lines @@ prey
densest part @@ targeting @@ shoal
fully extended throat @@ much effort @@ takes @@ swim
whale virtually comes @@ standstill
whale uses @@ water @@ tongue @@ mouth @@ force
hairy bristles @@ trapping @@ plates @@ line @@ krill @@ jaw
takes time @@ much water @@ sieve
nimble hunters @@ gives @@ chance
blue whales may @@ hunters @@ agile
need
one giant mouthful
swallow whole swarms @@ krill
better suited @@ predator
scattered riches @@ exploit
open ocean @@ provide
blue whale
greatest hunter @@ world @@ oceans
open ocean created many challenges @@ hunt team
film blue whales underwater @@ none came bigger @@ trying
year mission @@ two @@ turn @@ achieving
john calambokidis @@ crew teamed
foremost blue whale scientist @@ world
john gets crucial information @@ harmless tags
observe blue whales
brief time @@ surface
well @@ uh @@ research @@ reason @@ part
unique chance @@ gives us @@ working @@ get @@ filmmakers
scientific information @@ uh @@ otherwise @@ able
research permit @@ insight @@ get
underwater @@ diving
swimming @@ feeding
blue whales @@ rare @@ pictures
biggest animal ever @@ planet @@ live
underwater pictures @@ exist today
actually see @@ animal
blue whale @@ first @@ find
always feel really embarrassed @@ well @@ lose @@ know
ever lived @@ biggest animal
even bigger @@ whale @@ uh @@ ocean @@ big
good water visibility @@ team @@ success @@ depend
whale literally disappears @@ murky @@ gloom
shot
poor visibility @@ first year @@ blighted
shoot ended @@ failure
year two
sea conditions @@ much better
right @@ oh
three minutes @@ blue whales @@ two @@ time @@ surface
15 minutes @@ diving
narrow window @@ come together @@ everything
tricky maneuvering @@ john @@ bit
try @@ got @@ get @@ boat
whale @@ front @@ ahead
swim @@ david
whale passes close enough @@ shot @@ hope @@ get
far
time @@ little @@ far
exceptionally clear @@ year @@ water
right position still takes time @@ getting david
definitely got @@ went @@ shot @@ one @@ best
missed
weeks @@ effort
elements finally come together
giving david @@ lifetime @@ chance
25 feet @@ whale @@ knew @@ got
uh @@ right @@ came @@ blue
could see @@ mouth @@ eye @@ details
every scratch @@ skin
took forever @@ cruised
freight train @@ went @@ like @@ know @@ big
tail slide @@ saw
slipped back @@ blue
awesome
years @@ never @@ awesome
shot like @@ never got
amazing
blue whales underwater @@ rare @@ images
one simply swimming @@ major success @@ shot
crew need
series @@ hunting
nice though @@ shot @@ sequence @@ make
blue whales eating krill @@ get shots @@ got
wait @@ got
krill actually comes @@ surface
might happen @@ maybe twice @@ month
crew come across @@ encouraging sign
rather unsavory source
whale faeces
big whale poo @@ water @@ found
good sign @@ us @@ um @@ know @@ feeding
stick around @@ maybe
crew find @@ looking @@ finally
surface @@ krill
water @@ look @@ birds
small krill ball
go take @@ look @@ going
top @@ right @@ remember @@ put @@ john
right @@ ready
right @@ okay @@ ball
surface @@ right
good red @@ yep @@ top @@ right
yeah @@ got
happened next @@ prepared @@ one
right behind @@ hugh @@ hey @@ comes
oh
massive surface
shot @@ oh @@ got @@ god @@ bet
got @@ bet
ooh
god @@ beautiful
guys get
oh @@ god
actually quite get @@ head around @@ still @@ saw
krill balls @@ filming @@ dave
noticed @@ literally @@ fins
massive great whale @@ loomed
david saw @@ climb
know @@ came
first looked @@ whale @@ well @@ saw
little bit stressed @@ course
blue whale @@ 95 feet @@ going @@ fins
hooks around @@ big mouthful @@ grabs @@ comes
called blue whales @@ reason
underwater @@ see
bright iridescent cobalt blue @@ blue @@ pops @@ ocean
get round @@ side @@ finally
phew @@ okay @@ left @@ know @@ go
pretty intense
get another shot @@ trying
sure enough @@ krill
one last time @@ wide open @@ comes
wrong spot @@ kind
basic maneuvers @@ serious
mouth @@ comes @@ closes
amazing
whole thing probably lasted 10 minutes
without @@ hands @@ doubt
ever seen @@ amazing thing @@ questions @@ intense
blue whale @@ look eye @@ eye @@ water @@ share
never ever forget @@ something
shots give john @@ unique insight
feeding behaviour @@ blue whales
uh @@ side @@ mouth @@ look @@ let @@ basically
water flow @@ expect @@ coming @@ back
really interesting @@ little fold @@ yeah @@ look
ah
great view @@ oh
full rotation @@ notice @@ fantastic
full inversion @@ oh
unique chance @@ see @@ perspective @@ okay @@ get
close collaboration
filmed blue whales @@ team @@ never
started @@ reveal @@ last
secret life @@ greatest hunter @@ ocean
next time @@ open @@ hunt
grasslands @@ deserts
nowhere @@ hunters @@ hunted @@ hide
free interactive open university poster
call 0300 @@ 303 @@ 0552
uk @@ hunt @@ go @@ co @@ bbc
open university @@ links @@ follow