I actually don't see myself
as being special',
because I'm not.
Not really.
Uh, these are green peppers.
Uh, sage.
So I try not to think about it
and I just go about living my life.
Look at this one. See that? It's a nice one.
It's not something I'm ashamed of
or anything like that.
- But it's not something I'm proud of, either.
Because I had nothing to do with it.
You don't get to choose when you're born.
And as you can see here, the waxing gibbous
will be taking us toward the weekend.
And then on Saturday, we'll have a full moon,
and that's a perigee for this orbit.
So just keep that in mind
as you're planning your weekend.
Family dinners may be
a little more quarrelsome than usual,
especially if you've got some menstruating
teenagers around the table.
Andrew's been working for us
for almost three years now.
And I've really come to value him.
- Hi, Andrew. Good morning.
-Good morning. Heading out?
Because he's good at his job.
It's that simple.
The lamp in my bedroom needs a bulb.
- And the fact is...
- Okay, yeah, I can replace it.
...a lot of people we know can't find men
to do the job anymore.
So they're having to hire women,
which is obviously a lot more expensive.
- Good morning.
- Good morning!
Maybe it's because he is
so much younger than the other men
we've had working for us,
but I do worry about the impact
his presence has on our kids.
Really, you got a fever?
It's not that I'm worried that he's
corrupting them or anything like that.
It's more that having a man like him around
might make them yearn for something
they can't have... Shouldn't have.
I like the kids being exposed
to a man like Andrew.
Someone who's more in his prime,
more vital and active.
I think you're gonna be late for school
and you should go get ready.
What are you doing?
I mean, I know it's not
a very popular thing to say,
but I think it's enriching their lives.
Nine minutes.
All our lives.
Yeah, I suppose
from a historical point of view,
there's some truth to that.
Seventy-five years from now,
our daughters will be able to give
their daughters and granddaughters
a firsthand account
of what men were really like.
Yeah, I think that's important.
It's nature's way.
Praise nature.
My name is Andrew Myers.
lam 37 years old,
and I'm the youngest man in the world.
In 1953 I was a young priest,
just out of the seminary.
I was blessed with the good fortune
of being assigned to the Vatican
to work for an order known as
the Congregation of the Causes for Saints.
It was our responsibility
to investigate events
that were so extraordinary
that they could be deemed a divine miracle.
Every year, there were many claims made.
Stigmatas, apparitions of the Virgin Mary,
the healing of deadly medical conditions
and, of course, virgin births.
In a typical year, there would be
no more than three or four reports
of virgin births that warranted any attention.
But in 1953, there were 67 virgin birth claims.
You have to remember
that fatherless pregnancies
first began more than half a century ago.
This is back when Abrahamic
religions dominated the world,
and Christianity, which had nearly
two billion worshippers at that time,
regarded virgin birth
as one of its most sacred tenets.
Christians believe that a virgin named Mary
gave birth to their Holy Prophet,
Jesus Christ,
and that he was fathered by their God.
So you can see why
the Church was so concerned
about the sudden profusion
of virgin birth claims.
Because if they were true,
and the Vatican could not prove otherwise,
then they would have to be
considered miracles.
Except miracles, by their very nature,
are extremely rare events.
of course, it wasn't just
women who were virgins
that were making these claims.
All sorts of women were coming forward.
But there was no way to
scientifically validate the claims.
There was no DNA testing back then,
and the blood testing that we did have
could only prove
that a particular man wasn't the father,
not that there was no father at all.
You see, like all mammals,
humans could not procreate
without intercourse
between a male and a female.
It was scientifically impossible.
So despite the growing number of women
making fatherless pregnancy claims,
the only logical conclusion was
that they were all lying.
My doctor was the one who told me.
That's how you found out back then.
This was 1953, and I might have
been young, but I wasn't stupid.
I knew the signs. I felt awful.
The problem was, there was no possible way
that I could be pregnant.
Richard, he was my husband,
he insisted that I get retested
because he knew the same thing I did.
We hadn't been intimate for over a year.
As soon as the doctor walked in,
I knew what he was going to say.
That there was no mistake with the test.
There was no mistake with the test.
Your wife is pregnant.
Richard demanded
to know who I'd been with.
Who were you with? What's his name?
I swore to him
that! hadn't been unfaithful.
I haven't been with anyone.
But he didn't believe me.
Of course, you have. You're pregnant.
I tried to explain to the doctor
that this was impossible.
He just looked at me like I was a child.
Do you understand how procreation works,
how babies are made?
You see, when a man and a woman
have sexual relations...
It wasn't until 1988 that they had these tests
that could show that I was telling the truth,
not that it mattered by that point.
It was obvious.
But back then,
nobody believed me.
The harder I tried to convince people
I was telling the truth,
the crazier I seemed.
And pretty soon,
I began to wonder if I was crazy.
How else could you explain
something like that?
It's outlandish. Not even worth discussing.
But, Senator, you must admit
these statistics are compelling.
United States, 10,000 claims.
Great Britain, 6,000 claims.
India, 20,000 claims.
Even Soviet women are claiming
to have become pregnant.
We all know that women, by nature,
are very impressionable
and prone to hysterics.
It's a known fact.
Now perhaps the hormonal changes
involved in pregnancy
amplify this hysteria
and their own gullibility.
And then, you see, they hear
about another woman's bizarre claim
about her pregnancy,
and suddenly they're all doing it.
They cannot help themselves.
It becomes a fad.
Here we have the major developed countries
that existed at that time.
What's interesting is that
governments all over the world,
with every different kind
of political structure,
remember this was before unification,
when faced with fatherless
pregnancy claims,
they all reacted the exact same way.
I've been very preoccupied
with other matters for a while.
I'd have to ask a little more time.
Sir, will you
be able to have an opinion
-a little later on?
-I'm not sure.
It has certainly been a surprising spectacle.
They pretended like
it wasn't happening.
But this is not so hard to fathom
when you consider that
at that time, every one
of those governments was run by men.
Personally, I can understand
the position the authorities took.
It would have been irresponsible
just to come out and say
that a growing number of women
were procreating without male insemination.
On the whole, men are rational beings.
But we have egos, too.
And nobody likes being told
they're becoming obsolete.
Obviously, it's not for everyone,
but I still look forward
to going to work every morning.
There's not a lot of guys who can say that.
Not anymore.
Come on, I'm gonna tell Mommy.
Come on, you.
There's lots of things
I like about him.
He's fun to be around.
And he's caring, he's easy to talk to.
- Andrew, I can't see.
- Okay, let's take a break.
If we still had fathers,
he'd definitely be the kind I'd want for Violet.
What's that word they used to say
about a man who looked appealing?
Handser? Hands...
- Handsome?
- Handsome. Yeah.
Well, that's what they would
have said about Andrew.
That he's handsome.
Parasitism, competition
-and mutualism.
-Right there?
This is actually
the third household that I've worked in.
And they've all been different.
Describe species.
Got some more bread.
- Anyone want some?
-Thank you.
This one definitely
keeps me on my toes.
There's six kids, six months to 17.
But that's okay.
I prefer it that way. It's better to stay busy.
I think someone's gonna go to bed.
So everyone say good night.
- Good night, sweetheart.
- Good night.
What makes the job
a Jot easier, though...
Hey, everybody, gather in.
...is when you genuinely like
the women that you work for.
- Okay, is everybody here?
-Hey, Luna, how's it going?
- Hi, Violet.
-Hey.
Doesn't look like you're gonna be cold today.
Iris is really easygoing and kind.
And she has this way about her that...
Balls, we need balls.
It's hard to describe.
- See your sister? Hi!
- Over here.
All I know is that when I'm around her, I feel
at ease.
Saffron, move in!
Tends more conservative.
She likes to do things by the book.
Remember the play, girls,
just like in practice!
So when she's around,
I tend to keep a low profile.
I do my job, and I stay out of the way.
Because at the end of the day,
no matter how emotionally involved
I might get,
I'm an employee.
And it's good to be reminded of that
every once in a while.
There he is, the whippersnapper.
- Hey, Jim, how are you?
-Good, good.
You know Reggie?
He works for Holly Dawson
and Ivy Chan up on Verona.
Sure, yeah.
And my bosses want me
to put on a magic show to boot.
Can you believe that?
As if I can just summon up balloon animals.
I want to say, "Ladies, I put on
a magic show for you every single day.
"I toilet trained your daughters,
for God's sake."
Excuse me?
Can you keep your voices down?
Nobody wants to listen
to a bunch of manosaurs.
It's so annoying.
Sorry, we were just talking.
- Yeah, relax.
-Don't tell me to relax.
You're not even allowed to be here.
- It's okay, we're actually working.
-It doesn't matter.
You can't congregate
in groups of more than two.
- Or have you forgotten that?
-Oh, come on, seriously?
Those are the rules.
Are you going to follow them or not?
It's okay. I got to get back to work.
No, no. Don't go. Stick around.
It's okay. It's not worth it.
It was good seeing you. I'll see you soon.
See you later.
Maybe if things
had turned out differently,
I'd be a pilot or an architect like my mom.
But there's no point in dwelling on that.
I'm gonna make the best
of the opportunities that I do have,
because things aren't going to change.
Not back to the way they were.
That's just a fact of nature.
Even though more and more women
were coming forward
with fatherless pregnancy claims,
they weren't taken seriously.
So things seemed to carry on
as they always had.
I think there was a sense
that it was pointless.
We tried to tell them what was going on,
but they didn't want to listen.
They never listened.
But if you'd looked a little closer,
you would have seen that
beneath the woman’s dutiful,
prim and proper exteriors,
there was a simmering anger
getting ready to boil over.
And then Sister Isabella came along.
She was living in a convent in the hills
outside of a small town in Northern Spain.
Men were strictly forbidden
from entering the convent,
and even if she had wanted
to break her vows,
given the remote location
and the watchfulness of the other nuns,
it would have been impossible
for her to sneak away.
Yet, Sister Isabella discovered,
to her utter dismay
that she was pregnant.
One could argue that
if this had happened in a different time,
the Church may have very well
embraced Sister Isabella,
canonized her as a living saint,
and perhaps even looked upon her baby
as the return of their Messiah.
But then again, she had a daughter,
so that would have thrown a wrench
into the Biblical narrative, wouldn't it?
All we do know is that the Church wanted
nothing to do with Sister Isabella.
The Congregation of Causes of Saints
was ordered to destroy
the report they had written,
and deny that they had ever heard her claim.
They told us
it was for the best.
In the tiny village
of Burgos, Spain,
a group of nuns are telling a whale of a story.
Meet Sister Isabella.
Though it's hard to tell with that habit on,
she's pregnant.
And guess who they're saying the father is?
No one.
That's right,
it's another so-called fatherless pregnancy.
The last thing the Catholic Church
expected was that
a devout order of Spanish nuns
would not only break their vow of silence,
but start talking to anyone who would listen.
You people think
that this is a joke, but it is not.
It is happening more and more,
and the government needs to acknowledge it.
They need to wake up
and take these claims seriously
or they are going to be sorry.
We would like women everywhere to know
that despite the world's scientific community
being unanimous in their belief
that fatherless pregnancies are impossible,
we intend to study this matter vigorously.
And I have no doubt that,
one way or another,
we will be able to put this whole matter
to rest once and for all.
For as long as history
has been recorded we have seen,
with civilization after civilization,
that once a group attains power,
they are very reluctant to give it up.
But history also shows us that eventually
they are always forced to.
Tell us what you saw earlier.
Well, really it's what I didn't see.
When I came into work this morning,
there were no secretaries,
which is unusual,
given how many of them we have.
And since there was no one
to make me coffee,
I had to go all the way down to the lobby.
But then it took me 20 minutes to get service
because the waitresses
hadn't shown up for work there, either.
Afterwards, it was referred to as a strike.
But it wasn't an organized event.
My mother wasn't even aware
that other women were doing the same thing.
One night, she just decided
that she'd had enough.
My father and brother and I
were in the dining room
waiting for dinner to be served.
And I noticed she wasn't in the kitchen.
And it didn't seem like
any food was being prepared.
Then she appeared with a coat on
and her purse in her hand and said...
I'm going out.
I don't know when I'll be back.
If you want dinner,
you'll have to make it yourselves.
I think there's some
ground beef in the freezer.
And it was really
out of character for her
to be doing something like that.
But it wasn't until I turned
and saw the look on my father's face
that I realized that something
significant was happening.
I have to admit, I was impressed
that he was able to swallow his pride
and ask me to take him back.
But then I suddenly had this realization
that! had absolutely
no use for him in my life.
I love everything Iris paints.
I always have.
But I'm biased, because we're so close.
And when you really like someone,
you tend to like everything they do.
Uh...
Am I as crazy about
this man phase she's been in?
Maybe not.
But they're still beautiful paintings.
I don't think people
acknowledge the issue enough.
I mean, most don't acknowledge it at all.
But painlessness is something
that really concerns me,
which, I guess, is why I've been making it
such a part of my work lately.
Because I want to keep the issue alive.
I guess it's my way of making people
confront what's going on.
The paintings don't sell nearly
as well as my other pieces.
Actually, they don't sell at all.
Nobody wants a picture of a man
hanging over their fireplace.
It isn't Andrew's age
and what that represents.
He just...
He has this way about him that I like.
I notice her staring at him a lot,
but it kind of makes sense.
If you're gonna spend
all that time painting someone,
you should probably
really like looking at them.
You think I'm obsessed with him.
I'm not.
It's just part of my process.
It doesn't matter what my subject is.
Mmm. It's good.
- Are you being serious?
-Yeah, it's good.
And it's not like there's
a lot of other men around for me to paint.
And he does live with us.
Here is it.
I did it for art class. Um...
It's not perfect or anything.
I wasn't concerned with likeness so much.
I was more interested in his body,
his muscles, especially in his arms.
I really like his arms.
My grandma used to say
about my grandfather
that it wasn't his looks
or even his personality
that caught her attention at first,
it was his spirit.
And that's what I'm trying to capture
in my paintings,
Andrew's spirit.
And maybe, by extension,
the spirit that exists in all men.
As the number of fatherless
pregnancy claims continued to rise,
we discovered that the number
of normal pregnancies,
in which a man impregnated a woman,
was plummeting.
In fact, by the end of 1957,
three out of four babies born
were coming from mothers claiming
to have had a fatherless impregnation.
What was even more alarming, though,
was the fact that every one of those mothers
gave birth to a girl.
Parthenogenesis.
It's the reason why we get called.
You know, instead of how it used to be
when you needed to be
with a man to get pregnant.
What? It's true.
That's disgusting.
Parthenogenesis is a form
of asexual reproduction
in which an egg is the sole source
of genetic material
for the creation of an embryo.
But this mode of reproduction
was only known to occur
with insects and certain types of reptiles.
With mammals, however,
an embryo could only develop
if the egg had been fertilized by a male,
bringing together the genetic components
that make life possible.
But with parthenogenesis,
since all the necessary components
needed for reproduction
are produced by the egg,
sperm are rendered obsolete.
Not only that, but we discovered
the sperm could no longer
penetrate the wall of the egg.
It was producing a new protein
that hardened the membrane.
The sperm were literally being shutout.
Even when a sperm was injected
into the egg artificially,
it was almost immediately rendered inert.
When you take sperm
out of the biological equation,
there are no longer any Y chromosomes
being introduced
into the embryonic process.
So every embryo has two X chromosomes
and every child is female.
And thus,
no more males.
It wasn't hard for them
to figure out that I was the last one.
I was actually the only boy born that year
in the entire world.
But they didn't make it official
until a few years later,
when they were sure that there
wasn't any more of us coming.
When I started school, I got a lot of attention.
I was kind of like the class pet.
Not in a bad way.
It wasn't like I was being
kept in a cage like Mr. Chips.
He was the actual class pet.
High school was more of a challenge.
By that point, girls were so used
to not having boys around
that the idea of being attracted to one
was completely alien to them.
Don't get me wrong,
there were some crooked girls,
um, more than there are now, I'm sure.
But they weren't accepted by the other girls.
But neither was I, so we got along just fine.
It really wasn't until I finished high school
that I realized how different
things were going to be for me,
compared to the girls I graduated with.
That's when it finally dawned on me that
I wasn't gonna have the same
opportunities that they were going to.
They were going down one road
and I was going down another.
I, Eleanor Marie Hamilton,
do solemnly swear...
That I will faithfully execute...
The office of
the President of the United States.
And with the best of my ability...
If you had told someone
in the early 1960s
that a woman would be
the next President of the United States,
they wouldn't have believed you.
It may seem ridiculous now, but at that time,
people thought they'd have to wait 10,
or possibly even 15 years,
before that would happen.
The changes weren't that drastic,
at least not at first.
It's not like they came out
and declared war on men
or anything like that.
But I don't think it would be a stretch to say
that there was an element of payback
in their governing agenda.
We very much appreciate
the historical contribution
that men have made to our civilization.
But the facts are the facts.
Women make up 62% of the population.
And that...
Actually, Senator, it's 64% now.
Right.
And that ratio needs to be represented
in all levels of society.
But isn't your worker replacement program
-a little harsh? These statistics...
-Worker assessment program.
We only allow male employees to be replaced
if, after a very thorough assessment,
they are deemed to be less capable
than an equally qualified female.
It's simply a weeding out process.
And there just happens to be a lot of weeds.
My grandfather,
he warned that this would happen.
He said we never should have
given women the vote.
He said, uh, "You give them an inch,
and they'll take your soul."
You know what? He was right.
Generally speaking, men did not
react well to female-led governments.
More and more of them began to opt out
and move to rural encampments
in what we now refer to as "the Exodus."
We are not welcome here, so why stay?
You know?
We'll see how they get along without us,
because I don't think
it's going to be too long
before they realize the mistake they made
and then beg us to come back.
Hey, jackass!
You forgot your coat.
Kind of an important item to leave behind
when you're gonna live in the woods.
I was living with these three women,
and they were all beautiful and free loving.
Then they started treating me
like a sex object
and their errand boy.
By the mid-1970s, it was clear
that women were doing just fine
without men in charge.
This caused a lot of the men who had left
to rethink their positions.
Some returned and took on
more subservient roles.
But a core group dug in their heels
and refused to accept the new world order.
It's simple, okay? Power, respect.
That's what's been taken away from us,
and that's what we intend to get back.
It's not called "womankind."
It's called "mankind."
And there's a reason for that,
because for the last 200,000 years,
men have been keeping civilization afloat.
We've been steering the ship.
We built the ship.
And now they want to chuck us overboard
because their eggs have gone haywire?
Not bloody likely.
- What do we want?
- Respect!
- When do we want it?
- Now!
- What do we want?
Respect!
- When do we want it?
-Now!
The protests
tied up traffic throughout the city,
which is believed to be what
ultimately sparked the violence.
Women just started getting out of their cars
and coming at us with this...
This look in their eyes.
Get out of the street!
I was trying to get to work,
but the traffic was stopped dead.
And then I saw the men
blocking the road and chanting.
And I snapped.
Protest marches took place
all over the world that day.
At first, it was thought that the violence
was connected to parthenogenesis.
That nature was compensating
for the loss of men
by making women more aggressive.
But in fact, it was PMS.
By 1975, women represented
over three-quarters
of the world's population.
This triggered what's known as
"menstrual ovulatory synchrony,"
which is a phenomenon
where the menstrual cycles of women
become synchronized.
So essentially, the world became
like one big sorority house.
This is just the tip of the iceberg.
First their bodies get in sync.
Pretty soon, it'll be their minds.
Telepathic communication.
How do you contend with that?
You can't.
You can't compete with the hive mind.
The protest marches and the ensuing
violence turned out to be a watershed event.
It was the catalyst for creating a monthly,
three-day statutory holiday
we now know as "Menses."
But more importantly,
the protests happened right after unification.
So it was the first test
for the newly formed
World Governing Council.
And everyone was watching very closely
to see how they would respond.
First of all, I want to make it clear
that the World Governing Council,
above all, listens.
We want men's groups everywhere
to know we have heard you.
We acknowledge your plight
and we're going to help you.
As part of our commitment
to ensuring the safety
and comfort of men everywhere,
the World Governing Council
has set aside vast areas of land
for the creation of male sanctuaries.
These exclusive communities
will be located all over the world,
including the entire continent of Australia.
Men who live in these sanctuaries
will be provided
all the services they require,
including medical attention,
nutritious meals, clean clothes,
and of course, entertainment.
We believe that the remaining men
should be kept as comfortable as possible
as they live out their lives.
And that their contribution to humanity
must be, and will be, respected and honored.
But, at the same time, we must respect
and honor nature's actions.
Praise nature.
Do they think we're children?
Offering us food
and a bunch of silly conveniences.
It is a blatant attempt
by this female regime to pacify us.
We're not stupid.
They can ply us with
all the comforts in the world,
but it will not change our resolve.
Because they may have taken away
our rightful place in society.
They will not take away our dignity.
While there's no question
the MLO had a defiant spirit
and were very vocal about their intentions,
they actually didn't do much
once the Governing Council
established the sanctuaries
and began providing services.
That's rubbish.
Living in the sanctuaries
has not made us weak.
What it has done is given us
the ability to plan our resurgence
as the dominant, superior sex
without the hassle of having to
prepare meals or take care of ourselves.
Don't you see? The joke is on them.
All this time, the regime have believed
that they've been weakening our resolve.
But what they've actually
been doing is allowing us
to focus on our plan of attack.
And it won't be long
before we're ready to strike.
I don't think the issue is whether or not
the MLO is an effective organization.
It's the fact that their central goal
can't be achieved.
Not when the government firmly believes
that there's no solution to the problem.
They don't even see
manlessness as a problem.
To them, it's simply an evolutionary event,
an act of nature that's beyond our control
and should never be questioned,
because nature is sacred.
Notice the energy rising up your body,
higher and higher.
Feel the power flowing up
through your fingertips.
Breathe it in.
It wasn't enough
that they took away our jobs.
They went and fired God, too.
Worshipping the sacred
cycles of her forces.
Replaced him with a sheila.
That's nature flowing through you.
Praise nature.
But you can't question her actions,
because everything she does
is a blessed gift.
Influenza was an act of nature.
So was malaria and cancer.
But they're not around anymore.
And not because nature eradicated them,
but because the government spent
trillions of dollars developing vaccines.
I'm not suggesting that
the Governing Council has been
avoiding dealing with
the painlessness issue on purpose
as a way to maintain power,
even though having men die off
would certainly achieve that goal.
But I do think it's worth asking the question.
Why haven't more resources
been put towards it?
There's no doubt in my mind
that the government have been
deliberately ignoring the problem.
They're using nature as an excuse
to push their number one agenda,
doing away with men.
They go on believing that they don't need us,
but that's just another example
of their reckless, short-term way of thinking.
Being women, they can't think strategically.
They're incapable of seeing the big picture.
I'll give you an example.
In 1960, the U.S. Defense Department
was all set to fund a program
that would allow the computers
all around the world
to connect with each other.
They'd have been linked together
in a massive communication web.
Could you imagine
if all our word processing units
could talk to each other?
Bloody amazing, right?
Well, women take over and guess what?
The U.S. Defense budget gets stuffed.
Don't even getting me started
on space exploration.
They gutted NASA in the early 1960s,
and the Russian program
didn't stand a chance, either.
I really don't understand
this obsession they have
with putting a man on the moon.
We all appreciate the important role
it plays in our lives,
but do we really need to go to the trouble
of sending someone up there to stand on it?
I don't think so.
Now, if we had a way to
put all of the men on the moon...
So what do we have to show
for all these massive spending cuts
and program cancellations?
World peace and electric cars.
Big bloody deal.
True progress only comes about
through conflict.
Used to be a time when
one country fancied another,
they'd invade it.
War was declared, and they battled it out
until one of them was defeated.
And a bigger, stronger nation
was born out of it.
Dale?
I was just fixing my hair.
Used to be a time,
if a man fancied a woman,
he'd court her, tum on the charm.
...but I'd rather look at you.
You're beautiful, Connie.
Until she had no choice but to fall for it.
And they'd get together, and they'd have sex.
Intercourse.
That's a form of conflict.
And out of that came children.
True progress.
NOW?
We live in a world
where there's no wars, no.
I remember when my parents
told me I was the last boy.
I started wondering if maybe
I was the cause of the problem.
That somehow I had stopped
any more of us from coming out.
Like maybe I had broken
the machinery or something.
Uh, or that God had taken one look at me
and said, "That's it, I'm done with males."
Even though
we still don't know for certain,
a consensus has emerged as to
what caused the extinction of the dinosaurs.
The same will be true with men.
Until the cause is discovered,
a dominant theory will emerge
and become conventional wisdom.
My personal feeling? It's evolution.
Humans evolved from the apes
and now we're evolving further
into a single sex.
But why?
Why would nature do that?
We just don't need them anymore. That's all.
It's not as if we're a hunter-gatherer society.
We don't need men to protect us
or hunt for food or build shelters.
And since they aren't needed anymore,
nature just stopped producing them.
It's nothing personal.
It's the penis.
It was responsible for the skyscrapers,
the missiles, the oil drills,
and eventually all of that
aggressive, phallic energy
had such a corroding effect on the planet
that nature had no choice
but to extinguish it.
You know what a NEO is?
Near Earth object.
Now normally, they're comets or asteroids.
Well, in 1952, astronomers recorded one
that they thought was an asteroid.
But due to an unusually large
cloud of solar debris
that was surrounding it,
there was no way to be sure.
Nine months later,
the first so-called fatherless baby was born.
Women have two X chromosomes,
men only have one,
which would be okay if our Y chromosome
had something to offer.
But the fact is, it pales in comparison.
It only carries a tiny complement of genes
and it offers no protection
against genetic mutations.
It's kind of a runty little thing.
And I suspect that's ultimately
what's doing us in.
Why wouldn't there be female aliens?
A race of asexual, female aliens
that come to Earth
to hijack our reproductive system.
And do you want to know
why the government
doesn't have an explanation?
Because if they admitted
they knew what the cause was,
they'd be that much closer
to being able to fix it.
So either they don't want to know
and they've got their heads stuck in the sand,
or they do know
and they're hiding the truth from us.
Either way, they're avoiding
dealing with the situation.
Men aren't like that, are they?
- No.
-No! No.
When we see a problem, we attack it.
We tear it apart until we know
everything there is to know about it.
And then what do we do?
- We fix it!
We don't form committees or talking circles
or go on listening tours.
- We fix it.
MEN". Fix it! Fix it!
And that's exactly what we're gonna do.
We're gonna get back into power
and put an end to painlessness.
Fix it! Fix it! Fix it!
-- Fix m Fix m Fix m
I just received some
very important information.
They're sewing tenderloin
in the mess hall tonight
and they're sewing it right now.
Come on! Let's go.
I realize now it was
a kind of survivor's guilt that I was feeling.
And even though it's totally crazy,
I still feel twinges of it.
It's usually when I see
other men looking at me,
and I think they blame me
for being the last one out the door.
"What did you do? What did you do?"
I don't feel good about it.
But I don't feel bad, either.
It's not like they're being massacred.
They're just getting old and dying off.
It's like, I remember reading
in the paper a while ago
that the last surviving member
of this rock band had died.
They were called The Raymonds, I think.
The Ramones?
Right. Anyway, I remember feeling sad.
But not for all the members of the band,
or because they wouldn't
be producing any new songs,
but because someone had died.
That's always sad,
but that's also a part of life.
Nothing is forever.
You're comparing the extinction of men
to a punk band from the '70s?
It's actually kind of the same thing.
One day, I'm going to open up the paper
and find out that the last man has died.
And I think I'm going to feel the same way
that I did about The Raymonds.
Hi, I'm so excited to meet you.
- I loved your book.
-So nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
-What's your name?
Imagine if the entire planet
was exposed to sunlight 24 hours a day.
It would never get dark, so we wouldn't have
any use for the word "night."
The same is true for the word "gender."
Once men are gone,
it will cease to have any meaning.
And good riddance.
It's the most divisive word in human history.
But doing away with gender does not mean
we have to do away with sex.
Despite what the government
would have us believe,
women still crave sexual intimacy,
just as we're still instinctively pairing off
in order to raise our children.
Because without intimacy,
the bond that holds a couple together
will eventually start to disintegrate.
And then their families will disintegrate,
and then where does that
leave our society as a whole?
But the government
hasn't embraced this rationale.
In fact, the members
of the Governing Council
are these out-of-touch conservatives
who harbor an irrational fear
of a male resurgence.
And this paranoia has trickled down
into the bedrock of
the government's social policy,
which explains why it's so extreme.
They've turned their fear of heterosexuality
into a fear of any kind of sex at all.
Mom, can I ask you something?
of course, dear. What is it?
Is it strange that when
I touch myself, you know,
down there, that it feels really good?
Have you
found yourself in this situation?
or perhaps it's a conversation
you're dreading?
Well, don't worry, you're not alone.
The fact is, as girls reach puberty,
the joy and excitement of impending fertility
can often be accompanied by
the confusion and perils of sexual arousal.
The Department of Health
has produced this video...
I think what you have to understand
is that these are confusing times.
We are still in a period
of evolutionary transition.
Sexual urges are still present,
yet sex is no longer necessary.
Nature will eventually eradicate
these impulses,
but until then,
until we have become fully evolved,
the Governing Council
needs to ensure that young women
don't get caught up
in the futility of erotic pleasure.
We're not supposed to talk about it.
We're actually not supposed
to even know about it.
Especially the old kind of sex.
You know, intercourse?
And now there's all this worry about urges.
"Are you having urges?
Don't give in to the urges."
Next they'll be telling us
that if we get an itch,
we shouldn't scratch it.
It's not physical, it's psychological.
So you just need to not think about it.
I mean, if you were to have
those feelings... Thoughts.
They're thoughts, not feelings.
Which I've never had.
We are not trying to discourage intimacy.
At least not emotional intimacy.
It is critical that young people be taught
to nurture meaningful and deeply fulfilling
non-sexual bonds,
because they need to
grow up believing in love.
We all need to believe in that.
(LAUGHS You're a funny little thing,
aren't you?
Would you like me to tell you another story?
All right.
Well, once upon a time,
there was a fair maiden...
Hello.
Oh, Your Highness.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
- I certainly didn't mean to startle...
- I just wasn't expecting...
- You.
-You.
Jasmine and I, my best friend,
we've talked about it.
And we both like a lot of the same music
and we get along really well.
But I'm just not sure I want
to spend the rest of my life with her.
We've known each other forever.
- Not quite.
- Well, since high school.
Grade 11.
TERRA". Ah, that's when I had Dahlia.
I had partnered up with a friend of mine,
but that didn't work out.
Then Iris got called,
and we were both looking to pair off,
so it was just great timing.
And we've been together ever since.
I think it's proof that
you can partner with someone
without there having to be that intimacy.
Because you can't force
someone to feel that way.
Terra and I are good friends, we're partners,
we're raising our kids together,
but it's not anything more than that.
I think it's worked out really well for us.
Right?
Yes, yeah, of course. It's been great.
But you know, I also think
it's easy to understand,
given the circumstances,
why someone else might want a...
I don't know, a deeper bond
with their partner.
I'm not saying it should be sexual
or anything like that.
Of course not, it shouldn't be.
But that doesn't mean it can't be
something more meaningful or intense.
But there are men still out there.
Some of them aren't
that much older than you or I.
So it's not completely hopeless.
It just bothers me
the way that people talk about men
like they're already gone.
They're not.
They're still here.
One of them is, anyway.
She's talking about Andrew.
Okay, yeah.
Andrew is a good example.
And I'll admit it, I'm very fond of him.
Can we, uh...
Could we just take a small break?
I just need to... Excuse me.
It's not like I didn't know there was
something going on between them.
The way they look at each other,
and Iris' paintings.
But I assumed... I hoped
it was a harmless flirtation.
But it's not.
I can see that now,
it's obvious, they're intimate.
It's not like we were planning
for it to happen.
The more time he and I spent together,
we just...
It happened.
Everything's gonna change now
with Terra and I,
and Andrew.
She likes having
this aura of mystery.
It's part of being an artist, right?
Being provocative.
But I never believed
she was actually crooked.
I just thought it was an act.
Surprise, surprise, right?
You only see what you want to see.
- I have no idea what to do.
-it's going to be fine.
No, I don't think it is.
- You sure?
-Yes.
What are they doing?
What's going on?
Okay, okay, back in the house. Now.
Everyone, come on, go, go.
Can you turn it off, please?
Excuse me?
Now, please.
Of course there are
still women who are attracted to men
and don't want them to perish.
We understand that.
But they are a small segment
of the population,
maybe 10%.
And like the men they're pining for,
they're a dying breed.
Which is why we think it's best
for the population as a whole,
and for young people especially,
to prohibit opposite sex unions
and to encourage all the remaining men
to go into the sanctuaries,
so we can focus on
the next stage of our evolution
without any unnecessary
distractions or confusion.
So, this is it right here.
People are always expecting
a big electrified fence or something,
but you have to keep in mind
that this particular sanctuary
is over 300 square kilometers,
and it's one of the smaller ones.
So a fence just isn't an option.
Of course, the service roads are all gated.
We patrol the entire perimeter.
But to be honest,
we don't really get many men
trying to escape anymore.
That was more of an issue 10, 20 years ago.
Hurry!
Back then, they were
wandering out all the time.
- Are you getting him?
- Yeah.
SANCTUARY GUARD".
Mostly looking for female contact.
Mom! There's a man outside!
Just get out of here!
- Hey, no. It's okay.
- Shoo!
It's okay.
- Get inside the house right now.
-it's okay.
Don't come any closer.
It's okay. I just want to talk.
What's your name? I'm Kirk.
I already called the police.
You're very pretty.
Get inside now!
They just couldn't help
themselves, of course.
It's just part of their nature.
Border patrol agents
quickly arrived at the scene
and then surrounded the man
when he climbed up into a tree.
I wasn't doing anything!
Just leave me alone.
Not you, you're cute.
After a lengthy standoff,
the agents were forced
to use a tranquilizer gun
to sedate the unruly man.
They then returned him to
the nearby Northbrook Sanctuary,
where he is no doubt
rethinking any future plans
to venture outside the perimeter.
Like animals.
That's how I'd characterize it.
Except when animals are endangered,
everybody's all up in arms.
Committees are formed, monies are raised.
Can't do without those
Tasmanian fruit bats, can we?
But what do they do when it comes to men?
They take away our livelihoods,
shove us out into the wilderness,
erase us from their books and movies.
And just for good measure,
they basically go and castrate us.
I'm not joking.
This is evidence,
undeniable proof that
what we've been suspecting for years
is actually going on.
The report clearly states
that they are lacing our food with estrogen,
which is the girly hormone.
Smith claimed the document,
which he says is
an internal government memo,
clearly shows that the Governing Council
has been carrying out
a program intended to, quote,
"kill their boners."
A man's sex drive is his life blood.
You take that away from him,
you might as well kill him.
So I am hereto tell you that
we will no longer eat the food.
We are now officially on a hunger strike.
They might be able to strip us of our dignity,
but they will never take away our manhood.
The problem was, other than that memo,
which the government claimed was
just a discussion paper,
there was no proof.
They had found a way to put
a synthetic hormone into the food
without there being any way to detect it.
Which just shows, once again,
how capable their scientists can be
when they put their minds to something.
Thanks, Dawn.
Speaking of things that are short-lived,
the Male Liberation Organization
announced today
they are ending their hunger strike
after only a day and a half.
Darius Smith, the group's leader,
would only say
it was due to
"circumstances beyond their control."
What were we supposed to do?
When a man gets hungry, he has to eat.
That's just the way it is.
Does that mean we failed?
No, not in the least.
Now the world is aware of the lengths
that this authoritarian regime
will go to denigrate men.
But you're still eating the food.
Couldn't you have grown
and prepared your own food?
Yes, of course we could have
grown and prepared our own food.
But we've deliberately chosen not to,
out of protest.
Because if we'd refused the tainted food,
the story would have gone away.
People will forget what
their government did to us.
But by continuing to eat it every day,
the world is constantly reminded.
They have to live with it just like we do.
I'm not at liberty to go
into many details about that,
but I can say that we did add
estrogen to the sanctuary food.
But only until 2008.
At that time, we realized the initiative
was no longer necessary
due to the increasing age of the men.
They were losing their sex drives naturally.
That's a load of crap.
Of course they're still lacing the food.
It's bloody propaganda is what that is.
We're not so old either, you know?
No harm in showing this now, I guess.
People assume that because
I was the last one born,
that I'm very involved in the cause.
I get approached all the time
by pro-male organizations,
the MLO, Man Up, Penis.
They all want me to use my notoriety
to help raise awareness,
to lobby the government.
But that's not who I am.
I'm not the activist type.
Believe me, there are others
who are way more effective at that than me.
You know, leaders.
I'm just a guy.
I don't know.
It's hard to see how we can be together now.
The government would never sanction it.
Being intimate with your employer
doesn't look good on your record.
I guess I just got to stay positive.
I'm not gonna say it's a terrible place.
Excuse me, are these lima beans
in the quinoa salad?
- No, they're split peas.
-Oh, yeah?
It's not.
They treat us well.
But it doesn't matter
how comfortable a place is,
it can still feel like a prison.
They say the trick is to fill your days up
as much as you can.
To try to enjoy yourself.
But I can't seem to do that.
My mind is always somewhere else.
Back at the house with Iris.
That's not what it's like
for most of these guys.
They've gotten used to it here.
They like it.
But then again, most of them have no reason
to want to go back.
I do.
Oh, that's gorgeous.
Hold that... That will look wonderful on you.
Here we have the guest of honor,
the oh, so lovely Olive,
who, as you can see,
is celebrating her first moon.
'l ay!
I guess on the surface,
things went back to normal.
How does it feel to be a woman?
Uh, tingly?
But it wasn't the same after Andrew left.
And here we have the proud mother.
Terra and I, we just couldn't recover
from what happened.
She felt betrayed.
Let's get a picture of the two moms.
And nothing I could say was gonna
make her see things differently.
Um, Harold, can you move?
Harold.
- What's that?
-Can you move, please?
And the kids really missed Andrew.
Especially Dahlia.
For my part,
I tried to move on with my life,
but I couldn't.
I couldn't stop thinking about him.
Oh, baby, talk to me
Oh, please, talk to me, yeah
What really got to me
was when I stopped
and thought about how I was
going to be there for the rest of my life.
It was like being on the deck of a ship
that was sinking really slowly.
And the women have all left on the lifeboats,
but the men are just sitting there.
Waiting to meet their fate.
Oh, she just don't want to read me
That's kind of when it hit home.
How when I'm gone, we're all gonna be gone.
I knew I couldn't just sit there waiting.
I had to do something.
I had to leave.
They don't make it easy to do that, though.
I left in the middle of the night
and I ran as fast as I could.
But it didn't take long before they found me.
He didn't think I was gonna be there.
I was praying that she was going to be there,
but I had no idea if she got my message.
He was just staring at me
with this stunned look on his face.
So I said...
You just gonna stand there?
Or are we gonna get out of here?
I think that we were so determined
to be together
that we never really stopped
and thought about all the implications.
They were gonna
be looking for Andrew,
and we couldn't go into hiding.
What kind of life is that?
I mean, we'd already been hiding.
Pretending like we weren't involved.
This was gonna be a lot harder.
It just seemed so unfair,
because what we wanted
felt so natural.
To be together, to marry, to have kids.
And none of it was possible.
But if we wanted things to change,
we were gonna have to be the ones
to do something about it.
There's been a surprising
development in the sanctuary escape story
that we told you about last week.
REPORTER 'l: The 37-year-old Myers
surprised everyone today when he arrived
at the Jefferson Street Community Hall
to give a press conference.
Andrew Myers,
the youngest man in the world,
resurfaced today after escaping
from the Alice Lake Sanctuary.
At an impromptu press conference,
he and his former employer, Iris Balishev,
made a startling announcement.
We not only want the right to marry,
we want to have children together.
Even though heterosexual reproduction
is considered to be impossible,
it is our hope and our belief
that with the resources
of the Governing Council
and the support of the scientific community,
that it can become a reality.
That it should become a reality.
And I realize that I'm biased
because I'm in love with a man,
but I know I'm not the only one.
Please speak up,
because time is running out.
Seeing the two of them
together like that,
so obviously in love,
pleading for recognition,
it awoke something in people.
Go ahead, you're on the air.
I don't care
who knows anymore. I like men.
I'm not saying
I totally agree with it,
but you have to admit,
they make a cute couple.
I'll tell you what the answer is. No.
Just let them die off.
Come on, are they
really that bad? I don't think so.
This is a question of morality.
We can't just stand by and let them vanish
off the face of the Earth.
That's not what women are about.
There were more calls today
for the Governing Council
to take action on painlessness.
of course, the Governing Council
is aware of the public's reaction.
And they're taking it very seriously.
That's why they've convened
these emergency meetings,
to assess the situation
and consider any possible solutions.
It doesn't matter if we figure out
how to keep men around.
It's not our place to intervene.
This is an act of nature.
Praise nature.
FEMALE CALLER B". I think they should
find a way to start producing men again.
But not too many. Maybe 100 or 150.
Then see how it goes.
There's been so much attention
focused on us from the press
that we decided to make it
a really small, private ceremony.
But it was beautiful.
And legal.
We even have a license to prove it.
I don't have it on me right now,
but it's the real thing.
We're married.
And now we've been getting
even more attention
because of this little development.
It's not so little anymore.
We don't know if it's a boy.
We asked them not to tell us.
I really want it to be a surprise.
But the procedure worked.
Andrew's DNA is present.
It's his.
It's ours.
It's what she wanted.
To be with him and have a baby.
So good for her.
And if it's a boy like everyone seems to think,
then that's great for the world, too,
I suppose.
Personally, I couldn't imagine
having something like that
growing inside of me.
A male baby.
It turns out that
the Y chromosome was the culprit after all.
The government scientists
disguised the Y chromosome
to look like an X chromosome,
thereby tricking the egg into accepting it.
Do I wish people had been this excited
when I got pregnant?
Of course.
But it's a good thing that's happened.
I never really liked the idea
of men going extinct.
Didn't feel right.
On the other hand, I'm not going to deny
that I'm happy
they came as close as they did.
Gave them one hell of a scare.
And that's exactly what they needed.
Patience.
That's what I've been saying all along.
We just had to stay vigilant,
keep our wits about us.
And sooner or later, we'd get our chance.
And here we are.
It does feel different.
I don't know if it's just in my head,
but I feel like I'm pregnant for the first time.
Which, I guess in away, I am.
I don't know, I'm just really excited.
I'm just praying it's not a girl.
No, no, l was just...
She won't talk to me
Well, I know she can see me
She just don't want to read me
She won't talk to me
Oh, baby, talk to me
But I know she can see me
She just don't want to read me
She won't talk to me
But I know she can see me
She just don't want to read me
She won't talk to me